ABDERDEEN	O	O

Abidjan	O	LOCATION

ABIDJAN	O	LOCATION

Abu	O	PERSON
Dhabi	O	PERSON

Abuja	O	LOCATION

Acatepec	O	O

Addis	O	LOCATION
Ababa	O	LOCATION

ADDIS	O	O
ABABA	O	O

Adel	O	PERSON

Adige	O	O

Afghanistan	O	LOCATION

Africa	O	LOCATION

African	O	O
Football	O	O
Confederation	O	O

Aguas	O	O
Zarcas	O	O
de	O	O
San	O	LOCATION
Carlos	O	LOCATION

AJACCIO	O	LOCATION

Akron	O	LOCATION

AKRON	O	LOCATION

AL	O	O

Ala	O	PERSON

Al-Aqsa	O	O

Alaska	O	LOCATION

Albania	O	LOCATION

Alberta	O	LOCATION

Aleksandrovac	O	LOCATION

Alexandroupolis	O	LOCATION

ALEXANDROUPOLIS	O	O

Algeria	O	LOCATION

Algiers	O	LOCATION

Alicante	O	LOCATION

Alkhan-Yurt	O	LOCATION

ALKHAN-YURT	O	O

Allenby	O	LOCATION
Bridge	O	LOCATION

ALLENTOWN	O	LOCATION

Almere	O	LOCATION

ALMERE	O	O

AL-MUNTAR	O	O

Alomella	O	PERSON
Robles	O	PERSON

al-Risala	O	O

Alta	O	LOCATION

Altamira	O	LOCATION

Amazon	O	LOCATION

America	O	LOCATION

Amman	O	LOCATION

AMMAN	O	LOCATION

Amsterdam	O	LOCATION

AMSTERDAM	O	LOCATION

Amsterdam-Rotterdam	O	LOCATION

Amsterdam-Rotterdam-Antwerp	O	LOCATION

AMSTETTEN	O	LOCATION

ANCHORAGE	O	LOCATION

Andhra	O	PERSON
Pradesh	O	PERSON

Angola	O	LOCATION

ANGOLA	O	LOCATION

Anhui	O	LOCATION

Ankara	O	LOCATION

ANKARA	O	LOCATION

Antara	O	LOCATION

Antioquia	O	LOCATION

Antwerp	O	LOCATION

Anza	O	LOCATION

Aqaba	O	LOCATION

Arab	O	LOCATION
East	O	LOCATION
Jerusalem	O	LOCATION

Arabised	O	O
north	O	O

Arbil	O	LOCATION

Argentina	O	LOCATION

Arizona	O	LOCATION

Ark	O	O

Arkansas	O	LOCATION

Armenia	O	LOCATION

Ashoknagar	O	LOCATION

Ashta	O	LOCATION

Asia	O	LOCATION

ASIA	O	ORGANIZATION

ASIA	O	LOCATION
PACIFIC	O	LOCATION

Asmara	O	LOCATION

Athens	O	LOCATION

ATHENS	O	LOCATION

Atlanta	O	LOCATION

ATLANTA	O	LOCATION

Atlantic	O	LOCATION

Atlantic	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

ATLANTIC	O	LOCATION
CITY	O	LOCATION

ATLANTIC	O	LOCATION
HIGHLANDS	O	LOCATION

Atlantic	O	LOCATION
Ocean	O	LOCATION

Auckland	O	LOCATION

AUCKLAND	O	LOCATION

Australia	O	LOCATION

AUSTRALIA	O	LOCATION

Austria	O	LOCATION

AUSTRIA	O	LOCATION

Avalon	O	O
Borough	O	O

Azad	O	PERSON
(	O	O
free	O	O
)	O	O
Kashmir	O	LOCATION

Azerbaijan	O	LOCATION

Badi-Tondon	O	O

Baghdad	O	LOCATION

BAGHDAD	O	LOCATION

Bagram	O	LOCATION

Bahamas	O	LOCATION

Bahrain	O	LOCATION

Bailundo	O	LOCATION

Baku	O	LOCATION

Balkan	O	LOCATION

Balkans	O	LOCATION

Balochistan	O	LOCATION

Baltimore	O	LOCATION

BALTIMORE	O	LOCATION

Banat	O	LOCATION

Bandundu	O	LOCATION

Bangkok	O	LOCATION

BANGKOK	O	LOCATION

Bangladesh	O	LOCATION

BANGLADESH	O	LOCATION

Bangui	O	LOCATION

Banja	O	O
Luka	O	O

Barcelona	O	LOCATION

BARCELONA	O	LOCATION

Barentsburg	O	LOCATION

Barnagar	O	O

BARRY	O	PERSON

Basque	O	O
Country	O	O

BATKIVSHCHYNA	O	O
COLLECTIVE	O	O
FARM	O	O

Beijing	O	LOCATION

BEIJING	O	LOCATION

Beirut	O	LOCATION

BEIRUT	O	LOCATION

Beja	O	PERSON

Belarus	O	LOCATION

BELCHATOW	O	O

Belem	O	LOCATION

Belgium	O	LOCATION

Belgrade	O	LOCATION

BELGRADE	O	LOCATION

Bell	O	O
St	O	O
Station	O	O

Benelux	O	LOCATION

Ben	O	PERSON
Gurion	O	PERSON

Benin	O	LOCATION

Bergen	O	LOCATION

Berlin	O	LOCATION

BERLIN	O	LOCATION

Bermuda	O	LOCATION

BERNE	O	PERSON

Berovo	O	O

Bethlehem	O	LOCATION

Bilbao	O	LOCATION

Billings	O	O

Birmingham	O	LOCATION

Birmingham	O	LOCATION
Public	O	LOCATION
Park	O	LOCATION

Birmingham	O	ORGANIZATION
Public	O	ORGANIZATION
Park	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Rec	O	ORGANIZATION

Bistrita	O	PERSON

BISTRITA	O	LOCATION

Black	O	O

Black	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

BLACK	O	O
SEA	O	O

BLANTYRE	O	LOCATION

Boddington	O	LOCATION

Bogota	O	LOCATION

BOGOTA	O	LOCATION

Bogra	O	LOCATION

Bombay	O	LOCATION

BOMBAY	O	LOCATION

Bonn	O	LOCATION

BONN	O	LOCATION

Boo-nee-OL	O	O

Bordeaux	O	LOCATION

Born	O	O

Bosia-Hercegovina	O	PERSON

Bosnia	O	LOCATION

Bosnia-Hercegovina	O	LOCATION

Bosnian-Croat	O	O
Federation	O	O

Boston	O	LOCATION

BOSTON	O	LOCATION

Botswana	O	LOCATION

Bou	O	PERSON
Haroun	O	PERSON

Boulder	O	LOCATION

Brasilia	O	LOCATION

BRASILIA	O	LOCATION

Bratislava	O	LOCATION

BRATISLAVA	O	LOCATION

Brazil	O	LOCATION

BRAZIL	O	LOCATION

Breda	O	PERSON

BREGANCON	O	LOCATION

Bremen	O	LOCATION

Brisbane	O	LOCATION

Bristol	O	LOCATION

Britain	O	LOCATION

BRITAIN	O	LOCATION

British	O	O
Columbia	O	LOCATION

Brussels	O	LOCATION

BRUSSELS	O	LOCATION

Bucharest	O	LOCATION

BUCHAREST	O	LOCATION

Budapest	O	LOCATION

BUDAPEST	O	LOCATION

Buenaventura	O	LOCATION

Buenos	O	LOCATION
Aires	O	LOCATION

BUENOS	O	LOCATION
AIRES	O	LOCATION

Bulgaria	O	LOCATION

BULGARIA	O	LOCATION

Bunol	O	LOCATION

BUNOL	O	LOCATION

Burma	O	LOCATION

Burundi	O	LOCATION

CA	O	O

Caesarea	O	LOCATION

Cairo	O	LOCATION

CAIRO	O	LOCATION

Calcutta	O	LOCATION

CALCUTTA	O	LOCATION

Calcutta	O	LOCATION
hospital	O	O

Calderon	O	PERSON

CALGARY	O	LOCATION

Calif	O	LOCATION

Calif.	O	LOCATION

California	O	LOCATION

CALIFORNIA	O	LOCATION

Cambodia	O	LOCATION

Cambridge	O	LOCATION

Camden	O	LOCATION

Camelot	O	O

Cameroon	O	LOCATION

Canada	O	LOCATION

Canberra	O	LOCATION

CANBERRA	O	LOCATION

Cap	O	O
de	O	O
Villefranche	O	O

Cape	O	LOCATION
Town	O	LOCATION

CAPE	O	LOCATION
TOWN	O	LOCATION

Caracas	O	LOCATION

CARACAS	O	LOCATION

Cardiff	O	LOCATION

Caribbean	O	LOCATION

Caribs	O	O

CARLSBAD	O	LOCATION

Cartagena	O	LOCATION

CATANIA	O	LOCATION

Celopek	O	LOCATION

Central	O	O
African	O	O
Republic	O	O

Central	O	O
Asia	O	O

Central	O	O
Clinical	O	O
Hospital	O	O

Chad	O	LOCATION

Chandigarh	O	LOCATION

Channel	O	LOCATION
Islands	O	LOCATION

Charleroi	O	LOCATION

Charleston	O	LOCATION

CHARLESTON	O	LOCATION

Chavakachcheri	O	LOCATION

Chechnya	O	LOCATION

Chenab	O	LOCATION

Cherbourg	O	LOCATION

CHESAPEAKE	O	O

Chesterfield	O	LOCATION

Chester-le-Street	O	LOCATION

Chiapas	O	LOCATION

Chicago	O	LOCATION

CHICAGO	O	LOCATION

Chihuahua	O	LOCATION

Chile	O	LOCATION

CHILE	O	LOCATION

CHILLICOTHE	O	LOCATION

CHILPANCINGO	O	LOCATION

China	O	LOCATION

Chongqing	O	LOCATION

Chorzow	O	LOCATION

Christchurch	O	LOCATION

CIS	O	ORGANIZATION

Clarksburg	O	LOCATION

CLEVELAND	O	LOCATION

CO	O	O

Col	O	O

Colchester	O	LOCATION

Collingtree	O	O
Park	O	O

Colo	O	PERSON
.	O	O

Cologne	O	LOCATION

Colombia	O	LOCATION

Colombo	O	LOCATION

COLOMBO	O	LOCATION

Colorado	O	LOCATION

COLORADO	O	LOCATION

Columbia	O	LOCATION
Presbyterian	O	LOCATION
Hospital	O	LOCATION

COMMACK	O	LOCATION

Commonwealth	O	O
of	O	O
Independent	O	O
States	O	O

Community	O	O
of	O	O
Madrid	O	LOCATION

Conakry	O	LOCATION

CONAKRY	O	LOCATION

Congo	O	LOCATION

CONGO	O	LOCATION

Constanza	O	PERSON

Coolee	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

Copenhagen	O	LOCATION

COPENHAGEN	O	LOCATION

Corsica	O	LOCATION

Costa	O	LOCATION
Rica	O	LOCATION

COSTA	O	O
RICA	O	O

Costa	O	O
Rica-Nicaragua	O	O

County	O	LOCATION
Antrim	O	LOCATION

County	O	O
Tipperary	O	O

Creedmoor	O	LOCATION

Croatia	O	LOCATION

Croatia-Yugoslavia	O	O

Cuba	O	LOCATION

CUBA	O	LOCATION

Culpepper	O	PERSON

Curitiba	O	LOCATION

Cyprus	O	LOCATION

CYPRUS	O	LOCATION

Czech	O	O

Czech	O	LOCATION
Republic	O	LOCATION

CZECH	O	O
REPUBLIC	O	O

Dahshour	O	LOCATION

Dakar	O	LOCATION

DAKAR	O	LOCATION

Dalian	O	LOCATION

Dallas	O	LOCATION

DALLAS	O	LOCATION

Damascus	O	LOCATION

Dayana	O	PERSON

Dayton	O	LOCATION

Dead	O	O
Sea	O	O

Denmark	O	LOCATION

DES	O	O
MOINES	O	O

Detroit	O	LOCATION

DETROIT	O	LOCATION

Dewas	O	LOCATION

Dhahran	O	LOCATION

Dhaka	O	LOCATION

DHAKA	O	LOCATION

Dhar	O	O

Diyarbakir	O	LOCATION

DIYARBAKIR	O	LOCATION

Doboj	O	LOCATION

DODGE	O	O
CITY	O	O

Doetinchem	O	LOCATION

DOETINCHEM	O	O

Dohuk	O	LOCATION

DOHUK	O	LOCATION

Donje	O	PERSON
Ljupce	O	PERSON

Dresden	O	LOCATION

DRESDEN	O	LOCATION

Dubai	O	LOCATION

DUBAI	O	LOCATION

Dublin	O	LOCATION

DUBLIN	O	LOCATION

Duessseldorf	O	LOCATION

Duluth	O	LOCATION

Dunedin	O	LOCATION

Durban	O	LOCATION

Durres	O	LOCATION

East	O	O
coast	O	O

East	O	LOCATION
Germany	O	LOCATION

East	O	O
Jerusalem	O	O

East	O	O
North	O	O
Central	O	O

E.C.India	O	O

Ecuador	O	LOCATION

Edgbaston	O	LOCATION

Edinburgh	O	LOCATION

Egypt	O	LOCATION

Eindhoven	O	PERSON

ELIZABETH	O	PERSON

Empire	O	O
State	O	O

England	O	LOCATION

ENGLAND	O	LOCATION

Erez	O	O

Eritrea	O	LOCATION

Erzincan	O	LOCATION

Essex	O	LOCATION

ESSEX	O	LOCATION

Estonia	O	LOCATION

Ethiopia	O	LOCATION

ETHIOPIA	O	LOCATION

Etruria	O	LOCATION

Europe	O	LOCATION

Eurotunnel	O	LOCATION

Fairmont	O	O

Fairview	O	LOCATION

Fairview	O	LOCATION
Town	O	LOCATION

Far	O	O
East	O	O

Faroe	O	LOCATION
Islands	O	LOCATION

Finland	O	LOCATION

FINLAND	O	LOCATION

Firestone	O	O
C.C	O	O

Fla.	O	LOCATION

Flora	O	LOCATION

Florence	O	LOCATION

Florentine	O	O
Guelfs	O	O

Florida	O	LOCATION

FLORIDA	O	LOCATION

Florida	O	LOCATION
Straits	O	LOCATION

Flushing	O	LOCATION
Meadows	O	LOCATION

Foindu	O	LOCATION

Former	O	O
Yugoslavia	O	LOCATION

Forth	O	LOCATION
Road	O	LOCATION
Bridge	O	LOCATION

Fort	O	LOCATION
Lauderdale	O	LOCATION

FORT	O	O
LAUDERDALE	O	O

FORT	O	O
WORTH	O	O

FR	O	O

France	O	LOCATION

FRANCE	O	LOCATION

Frankfurt	O	LOCATION

FRANKFURT	O	LOCATION

Franklin	O	PERSON
Roosevelt	O	PERSON

Freetown	O	LOCATION

FREETOWN	O	LOCATION

Freiburg	O	LOCATION

French	O	O
Guiana	O	O

French	O	O
Riviera	O	O

Gabon	O	LOCATION

Gadoon	O	PERSON

Garhi	O	PERSON
Habibullah	O	PERSON

Gatwick	O	LOCATION

Gaza	O	LOCATION

GAZA	O	LOCATION

Gaza	O	LOCATION
Strip	O	LOCATION

Gdansk	O	LOCATION

GDANSK	O	LOCATION

Geneva	O	LOCATION

GENEVA	O	LOCATION

GENOA	O	LOCATION

Georgia	O	LOCATION

germany	O	O

Germany	O	LOCATION

Gisenyi	O	LOCATION

GLASGOW	O	LOCATION

Glenview	O	LOCATION

Glenwood	O	LOCATION

Golan	O	LOCATION

Golan	O	LOCATION
Heights	O	LOCATION

GOLF	O	O

Goma	O	LOCATION

Gorgona	O	PERSON

Gorleben	O	LOCATION

Gothenburg	O	LOCATION

GOTHENBURG	O	LOCATION

Gouda	O	LOCATION

Grande	O	LOCATION
Prairie	O	LOCATION

Great	O	O
Hall	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
People	O	O

Greece	O	LOCATION

GREECE	O	LOCATION

Griqualand	O	LOCATION
West	O	LOCATION

GRIQUALAND	O	LOCATION
WEST	O	LOCATION

Grozny	O	LOCATION

GROZNY	O	LOCATION

Guantanamo	O	LOCATION
Bay	O	LOCATION

Guantanamo	O	LOCATION
Naval	O	LOCATION
Base	O	LOCATION

Guernsey	O	LOCATION

Guerrero	O	LOCATION

Guinea	O	LOCATION

Gujarat	O	LOCATION

Gujar	O	PERSON
Khan	O	PERSON

Gulf	O	O

Haarlem	O	LOCATION

HAARLEM	O	LOCATION

Haiti	O	LOCATION

Hakkari	O	LOCATION

Halle	O	PERSON

Halo	O	O
Trust	O	O

Hamburg	O	LOCATION

HAMBURG	O	LOCATION

Hamilton	O	PERSON

Hampshire	O	LOCATION

Haneda	O	LOCATION

Hanmer	O	PERSON

Hannover	O	LOCATION

HANOVER	O	LOCATION

Harare	O	LOCATION

HARARE	O	LOCATION

HARLEYSVILLE	O	ORGANIZATION

Havana	O	LOCATION

Havre	O	PERSON

Hawaii	O	LOCATION

Headingley	O	LOCATION

Heathrow	O	LOCATION

Hebron	O	LOCATION

HEERENVEEN	O	O

Heidrun	O	LOCATION

Helsinki	O	LOCATION

HELSINKI	O	LOCATION

Hengelo	O	LOCATION

Heysel	O	O

Highland	O	LOCATION

High	O	O
Plains	O	O

HK	O	LOCATION

H.K.	O	O

Hollywood	O	LOCATION

HOLZGERLINGEN	O	O

Honduras	O	LOCATION

HONDURAS	O	LOCATION

Hong	O	LOCATION
Kong	O	LOCATION

HONG	O	LOCATION
KONG	O	LOCATION

Hospital	O	O
No	O	O
31	O	O

Houston	O	LOCATION

HOUSTON	O	LOCATION

Hove	O	PERSON

Hub	O	O

Hungary	O	LOCATION

HUNGARY	O	LOCATION

Hunter	O	O

Huntington	O	LOCATION

Hyderabad	O	LOCATION

IA	O	O

Iceland	O	LOCATION

IL	O	O

Ill	O	O

Illinois	O	LOCATION

IMOLA	O	ORGANIZATION

Inchon	O	LOCATION

India	O	LOCATION

INDIA	O	LOCATION

Indiana	O	LOCATION

Indianapolis	O	LOCATION

Indian	O	LOCATION
Ocean	O	LOCATION

Indonesia	O	LOCATION

Indore	O	O

INDORE	O	O

Indre	O	O

INGOLSTADT	O	O

Inia	O	O

IN-NAZZJON	O	O

Inter-Entity	O	O
Boundary	O	O
Line	O	O

Inverness	O	LOCATION

Iowa	O	LOCATION

Iran	O	LOCATION

Iranian	O	O
Kurdistan	O	LOCATION

Iraq	O	LOCATION

IRAQ	O	LOCATION

Ireland	O	LOCATION

IRVINE	O	LOCATION

Islamabad	O	LOCATION

ISLAMABAD	O	LOCATION

Islamic	O	O
Museum	O	O

Islamic	O	O
Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Iran	O	LOCATION

Island	O	O
Beach	O	O
State	O	O
Park	O	O

Israel	O	LOCATION

Istanbul	O	LOCATION

ISTANBUL	O	LOCATION

Italy	O	LOCATION

Itami	O	LOCATION

Ivory	O	LOCATION
Coast	O	LOCATION

JACKSONVILLE	O	LOCATION

Jacobs	O	LOCATION
Field	O	LOCATION

Jaffna	O	LOCATION

Jakarta	O	LOCATION

JAKARTA	O	LOCATION

Jalalabad	O	LOCATION

Jamaica	O	LOCATION

Jammu	O	LOCATION

Jaora	O	O

Japan	O	LOCATION

Jeddah	O	LOCATION

Jersey	O	O

Jerusalem	O	LOCATION

JERUSALEM	O	LOCATION

Jiangsu	O	LOCATION

Jiangxi	O	LOCATION

Johannesburg	O	LOCATION

JOHANNESBURG	O	LOCATION

Johns	O	PERSON
Hopkins	O	PERSON
Hospital	O	PERSON

Johnson	O	O
Cty	O	O

Jordan	O	LOCATION

JP	O	O

Juan	O	PERSON
Santamaria	O	PERSON

Jumet	O	LOCATION

JYVASKLYA	O	O

Jyvaskyla	O	LOCATION

JYVASKYLA	O	LOCATION

Kabul	O	LOCATION

KABUL	O	LOCATION

Kabul-Salang	O	LOCATION

Kan	O	O

Kandahar	O	LOCATION

Kanie	O	PERSON
Karzhala	O	PERSON

Kansas	O	LOCATION

Kansas	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

KANSAS	O	LOCATION
CITY	O	LOCATION

Kaolack	O	LOCATION

Karachi	O	LOCATION

KARACHI	O	LOCATION

Karak	O	LOCATION

Karin	O	PERSON
Gornji	O	PERSON

Kashmir	O	LOCATION

Kassala	O	LOCATION

Kathmandu	O	LOCATION

KATHMANDU	O	LOCATION

Kazakhstan	O	LOCATION

Keirin	O	LOCATION

Kentucky	O	LOCATION

Kenya	O	LOCATION

Khandwa	O	LOCATION

Khartoum	O	LOCATION

KHARTOUM	O	LOCATION

Kiev	O	LOCATION

KIEV	O	LOCATION

Kigali	O	LOCATION

KIGALI	O	LOCATION

KIMBERLEY	O	O

Kingdome	O	O

Kinshasa	O	LOCATION

KINSHASA	O	LOCATION

KIRKCALDY	O	LOCATION

KIRKLAND	O	LOCATION

Kiryat	O	PERSON
Sefer	O	PERSON

Kishinev	O	LOCATION

Kivu	O	PERSON

Klongprem	O	LOCATION

Knowsley	O	LOCATION
Road	O	LOCATION

Koeln	O	LOCATION

Korea	O	LOCATION

Kosovo	O	LOCATION

Kragujevac	O	LOCATION

Krajina	O	LOCATION

Kremlin	O	LOCATION

KS	O	O

KUALA	O	O
LUMPUR	O	O

Kudapokuna	O	LOCATION

Kunar	O	LOCATION

Kuwait	O	LOCATION

Kwazulu-Natal	O	LOCATION

LAGOS	O	LOCATION

Lahore	O	LOCATION

Lake	O	LOCATION
Maracaibo	O	LOCATION

LANDSKRONA	O	LOCATION

Larnaca	O	LOCATION

LARNACA	O	LOCATION

Las	O	O
Cruces	O	O

LAS	O	O
CRUCES	O	O

Las	O	LOCATION
Vegas	O	LOCATION

Lattakia	O	LOCATION

LATTAKIA	O	LOCATION

Latvia	O	LOCATION

Lausanne	O	LOCATION

Lebanon	O	LOCATION

Leduc	O	LOCATION
Reef	O	LOCATION

LEEDS	O	ORGANIZATION

Lees	O	O
Summit	O	O

Leicester	O	LOCATION

Leipzig	O	LOCATION

Lesser	O	O
Antilles	O	O

Leveilly	O	LOCATION

Lhasa	O	LOCATION

Liaoning	O	LOCATION

Liberia	O	LOCATION

LIBERIA	O	LOCATION

Libya	O	LOCATION

Liechenstein	O	LOCATION

Liechtenstein	O	LOCATION

Liege	O	LOCATION

Lima	O	LOCATION

LIMA	O	LOCATION

Limerick	O	LOCATION

LIMERICK	O	LOCATION

Lincoln	O	PERSON

Linz	O	LOCATION

LINZ	O	LOCATION

Lisbon	O	LOCATION

LISBON	O	LOCATION

Lisheen	O	O

Lithuania	O	LOCATION

Little	O	O
Rock	O	O

LITTLE	O	O
ROCK	O	O

Ljubljana	O	LOCATION

LJUBLJANA	O	LOCATION

Loftus	O	LOCATION
Versfeld	O	LOCATION

Lome	O	O

LOME	O	ORGANIZATION

London	O	LOCATION

LONDON	O	LOCATION

Longchamp	O	LOCATION

Long	O	LOCATION
Island	O	LOCATION

Longyearbyen	O	LOCATION

Lord	O	O
's	O	O

Loretto	O	O
Abbey	O	O

L-ORIZZONT	O	O

Los	O	LOCATION
Angeles	O	LOCATION

LOS	O	LOCATION
ANGELES	O	LOCATION

LUANDA	O	LOCATION

LUSAKA	O	LOCATION

Luxembourg	O	LOCATION

M3	O	O

Macedonia	O	LOCATION

Madagascar	O	LOCATION

Madhumalla	O	LOCATION

Madison	O	O

Madrid	O	LOCATION

MADRID	O	LOCATION

Mae	O	PERSON
Sot	O	PERSON

MAE	O	O
SOT	O	O

Mahala	O	LOCATION

Maine	O	LOCATION

Malawi	O	LOCATION

Malaysia	O	LOCATION

Malta	O	LOCATION

Malta	O	LOCATION
Freeport	O	LOCATION

Managua	O	LOCATION

MANAGUA	O	LOCATION

MANAMA	O	LOCATION

Manchester	O	LOCATION

MANCHESTER	O	O

MANCHESTER	O	O
UNITED	O	O

Mandsaur	O	O

Manhattan	O	LOCATION

Manhattan	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Maniema	O	LOCATION

Manila	O	LOCATION

MANILA	O	LOCATION

Manitoba	O	LOCATION

Mano	O	O
Junction	O	O

Mapourdit	O	LOCATION

Maputo	O	LOCATION

MAPUTO	O	LOCATION

MARACAIBO	O	O

Maribor	O	LOCATION

Mass	O	O

Massachusetts	O	LOCATION

Matagalpa	O	LOCATION

Matuzici	O	LOCATION

MATUZICI	O	LOCATION

Mauritania	O	LOCATION

Mauritius	O	LOCATION

Mecca	O	O

MED	O	O

Medellin	O	LOCATION

Melbourne	O	LOCATION

MELBOURNE	O	LOCATION

Menlo	O	O
Park	O	O

Metropolitan	O	O
Museum	O	O

Mexico	O	LOCATION

Mexico	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

MEXICO	O	LOCATION
CITY	O	LOCATION

Mhow	O	O

Miami	O	LOCATION

MIAMI	O	O

Mich	O	PERSON

Michigan	O	LOCATION

Michigan	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

Middle	O	O

Middle	O	LOCATION
East	O	LOCATION

Middle	O	LOCATION
East	O	LOCATION
Gulf	O	LOCATION

Middle	O	LOCATION
Kingdom	O	LOCATION

Mideast	O	LOCATION

Mideast	O	LOCATION
Gulf	O	LOCATION

MIDEAST	O	O
GULF	O	O

Midwest	O	LOCATION

Milan	O	LOCATION

MILAN	O	LOCATION

MILWAUKEE	O	LOCATION

Minn	O	O

Minnesota	O	LOCATION

MINNESOTA	O	LOCATION

MINNETONKA	O	LOCATION

Minutka	O	LOCATION
Square	O	LOCATION

Mississippi	O	LOCATION

Missouri	O	LOCATION

Mister	O	O
Baileys	O	O

Mo	O	PERSON

Moengo	O	LOCATION

Mohali	O	LOCATION

Moldova	O	LOCATION

Monaco	O	LOCATION

Mongolia	O	LOCATION

Monrovia	O	LOCATION

MONROVIA	O	LOCATION

Montana	O	LOCATION

Monte	O	O
Aperto	O	O

Monte	O	LOCATION
Carlo	O	LOCATION

Montenegro	O	LOCATION

Monterey	O	LOCATION

MONTGOMERY	O	O

Montpelier	O	LOCATION

MONTPELIER	O	LOCATION

Montreal	O	LOCATION

MONTREAL	O	O

Montserrat	O	LOCATION

Mont-sur-Marchienne	O	O

Morinville	O	LOCATION

Morocco	O	LOCATION

Moscow	O	LOCATION

MOSCOW	O	LOCATION

Moslem-Croat	O	O
Federation	O	O

Mother	O	O
House	O	O

Mountain	O	O

MOUNTAIN	O	O
VIEW	O	O

Mount	O	LOCATION
Lebanon	O	LOCATION

Mount	O	O
Zion	O	O
Missionary	O	O
Baptist	O	O
Church	O	O

Mozambique	O	LOCATION

MOZAMBIQUE	O	LOCATION

Mpumulanga	O	LOCATION

MT	O	O

Muenster	O	LOCATION

Munich	O	LOCATION

Muzaffarabad	O	LOCATION

MUZAFFARABAD	O	LOCATION

NABLUS	O	LOCATION

Nagyatad	O	LOCATION

NAGYATAD	O	LOCATION

Nahar	O	LOCATION

Nairobi	O	LOCATION

NAIROBI	O	LOCATION

Nalkhera	O	O

Namibia	O	LOCATION

Narino	O	LOCATION

National	O	O
Tennis	O	O
Centre	O	O

N.C.	O	LOCATION

N'DJAMENA	O	O

Near	O	O
East	O	O

Nebraska	O	LOCATION

Neemuch	O	O

Nelson	O	PERSON

Nepal	O	LOCATION

Netanya	O	LOCATION

Netherland	O	LOCATION

Netherlands	O	LOCATION

Neths	O	LOCATION

NEUFCHATEAU	O	LOCATION

Newark	O	LOCATION

Newbury	O	LOCATION

New	O	LOCATION
Delhi	O	LOCATION

NEW	O	O
DELHI	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
England	O	LOCATION

New	O	O
Haven	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
Jersey	O	LOCATION

Newmarket	O	LOCATION

New	O	LOCATION
Mexico	O	LOCATION

New	O	O
Territories	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
York	O	LOCATION

NEW	O	O
YORK	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
York	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION

NEW	O	LOCATION
ZEALAND	O	LOCATION

Nhamavila	O	LOCATION

Nicaragua	O	LOCATION

NICE	O	O

NICOSIA	O	LOCATION

Nigeria	O	LOCATION

Nirmal	O	LOCATION
Hriday	O	LOCATION

N.J.	O	LOCATION

North	O	O

North	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION

Northampton	O	LOCATION

NORTHAMPTON	O	LOCATION

North	O	LOCATION
Battleford	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
Caucasus	O	O

North	O	LOCATION
Dakota	O	LOCATION

NORTH	O	O
DAKOTA	O	O

Northern	O	LOCATION
Ireland	O	LOCATION

Northfield	O	LOCATION
Mountains	O	LOCATION

North	O	LOCATION
Korea	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
Shore	O	O

North	O	LOCATION
Yemen	O	LOCATION

Norway	O	LOCATION

NORWAY	O	LOCATION

Nottingham	O	LOCATION

Nottingham	O	LOCATION
Forest	O	LOCATION

Nouakchott	O	LOCATION

Novye	O	LOCATION
Atagi	O	LOCATION

NOVYE	O	O
ATAGI	O	O

Nuku'alofa	O	LOCATION

Nuremberg	O	LOCATION

NUREMBERG	O	O

N.Y.	O	LOCATION

NZ	O	LOCATION

Oaxaca	O	LOCATION

Oerlikon	O	LOCATION

OH	O	O

Ohio	O	LOCATION

Okinawa	O	LOCATION

Oklahoma	O	LOCATION

Old	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

Old	O	O
Trafford	O	O

Omaha	O	LOCATION

Oman	O	LOCATION

Omari	O	PERSON

Opera	O	O

OR	O	O

Oran	O	LOCATION

Orvieto	O	LOCATION

ORVIETO	O	LOCATION

Osaka	O	LOCATION

Oslo	O	LOCATION

OSLO	O	LOCATION

Osnabrueck	O	LOCATION

Ottawa	O	LOCATION

OTTAWA	O	LOCATION

Oval	O	O

Oxford	O	LOCATION

Pa	O	O

Pacific	O	LOCATION

PACIFIC	O	LOCATION

Pacific	O	LOCATION
Northwest	O	LOCATION

Padania	O	LOCATION

Pakistan	O	LOCATION

PAKISTAN	O	LOCATION

Pakistani	O	O
Kashmir	O	LOCATION

Palk	O	LOCATION
Strait	O	LOCATION

Panama	O	LOCATION

PAPENDRECHT	O	O

Papua	O	O
New	O	LOCATION
Guinea	O	LOCATION

Para	O	PERSON

Paraguay	O	LOCATION

Paramaribo	O	LOCATION

PARAMARIBO	O	LOCATION

Paramount	O	O

Parc	O	O
des	O	O
Princes	O	O

Paris	O	LOCATION

PARIS	O	LOCATION

Partition	O	O

Pattaya	O	LOCATION

Peace	O	LOCATION
River	O	LOCATION
Valley	O	LOCATION

Pemberton	O	PERSON

PEMBERTON	O	PERSON

Pembroke	O	LOCATION

Pembroke	O	LOCATION
Pines	O	LOCATION

Pendleton	O	PERSON

Pennsylvania	O	LOCATION

Perm	O	LOCATION

Perth	O	LOCATION

PERTH	O	LOCATION

Peru	O	LOCATION

Pesalai	O	LOCATION

Petersburg	O	PERSON

Petrosan	O	O

Philadelphia	O	LOCATION

PHILADELPHIA	O	LOCATION

Phnom	O	LOCATION
Penh	O	LOCATION

PHNOM	O	O
PENH	O	O

PHOENIX	O	LOCATION

Pierina	O	PERSON

Pittsburgh	O	LOCATION

PITTSBURGH	O	LOCATION

Place	O	LOCATION
Beauvau	O	LOCATION

Podujevo	O	LOCATION

Poland	O	LOCATION

POLAND	O	LOCATION

Pontefract	O	LOCATION

PONTIAC	O	LOCATION

Pontiac	O	LOCATION
Osteopathic	O	LOCATION
Hospital	O	LOCATION

Port	O	O
Arthur	O	O

Portland	O	LOCATION

PORTO	O	LOCATION

Portsmouth	O	LOCATION

Portugal	O	LOCATION

Potsdam	O	LOCATION

Prague	O	LOCATION

PRAGUE	O	LOCATION

Prairies	O	O

Preston	O	PERSON

Pretoria	O	LOCATION

PRETORIA	O	LOCATION

Prince	O	O
Rupert	O	PERSON

Prince	O	O
William	O	PERSON
Sound	O	PERSON

Pudong	O	LOCATION
New	O	LOCATION
Area	O	LOCATION

Puertollano	O	LOCATION

Puerto	O	LOCATION
Rico	O	LOCATION

Punjab	O	LOCATION

Qasri	O	O

Queensland	O	LOCATION

Quepos	O	LOCATION

Quetta	O	LOCATION

QUITO	O	LOCATION

Rabat	O	LOCATION

RABAT	O	LOCATION

Ramallah	O	LOCATION

RAMALLAH	O	LOCATION

Rameswaram	O	LOCATION

RAMESWARAM	O	LOCATION

Ramle	O	LOCATION

Rangoon	O	LOCATION

Ransart	O	O

Ratlam	O	O

Ravi	O	PERSON

Rawandouz	O	PERSON

Red	O	O
River	O	O

Red	O	O
Sea	O	O

RED	O	O
SEA	O	O

Republic	O	O

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Ireland	O	LOCATION

Republika	O	LOCATION
Srbska	O	LOCATION

Republika	O	LOCATION
Srpska	O	LOCATION

RICHMOND	O	LOCATION

Riel	O	PERSON

Rio	O	LOCATION

Rio	O	LOCATION
de	O	LOCATION
Janeiro	O	LOCATION

RIO	O	O
DE	O	O
JANEIRO	O	O

Rishon-Lezion	O	O

Riviera	O	LOCATION

Riyadh	O	LOCATION

Robben	O	LOCATION
Island	O	LOCATION

Romania	O	LOCATION

ROMANIA	O	LOCATION

Rome	O	LOCATION

ROME	O	LOCATION

Rotterdam	O	LOCATION

ROTTERDAM	O	LOCATION

Rousse	O	PERSON

ROVERETO	O	LOCATION

Roxbury	O	LOCATION

Rudyard	O	O

Rumbek	O	LOCATION

Russia	O	LOCATION

RUSSIA	O	LOCATION

Russian	O	O
Federation	O	O

Rwanda	O	LOCATION

Saarbruecken	O	LOCATION

Sabourin	O	LOCATION

S.	O	LOCATION
Africa	O	LOCATION

Sakai	O	LOCATION

Salahuddin	O	LOCATION

Salamanca	O	LOCATION

Salang	O	LOCATION

SALANG	O	O

Salvador	O	LOCATION

San	O	LOCATION
Diego	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
DIEGO	O	LOCATION

Sandusky	O	LOCATION

San	O	LOCATION
Francisco	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
FRANCISCO	O	LOCATION

San	O	LOCATION
Jose	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	O
JOSE	O	O

San	O	LOCATION
Marino	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
MARINO	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
MATEO	O	LOCATION

Santa	O	LOCATION
Barbara	O	LOCATION

Santa	O	PERSON
Maria	O	PERSON
de	O	PERSON
Pocosol	O	PERSON

Santiago	O	LOCATION
Bernabeu	O	LOCATION

Sao	O	LOCATION
Paulo	O	LOCATION

Sarajevo	O	LOCATION

SARAJEVO	O	LOCATION

Sardinia	O	LOCATION

Sask	O	O

Saskatchewan	O	LOCATION

Saudi	O	LOCATION
Arabia	O	LOCATION

Saxony	O	LOCATION

S.C.	O	LOCATION

Schoenefeld	O	LOCATION

Scotland	O	LOCATION

SCOTLAND	O	LOCATION

Seaford	O	LOCATION
Union	O	LOCATION

Seattle	O	LOCATION

SEATTLE	O	LOCATION

Sen	O	O

Senegal	O	LOCATION

Seoul	O	LOCATION

SEOUL	O	LOCATION

Serbia	O	LOCATION

Seville	O	LOCATION

Seychelles	O	LOCATION

SEYCHELLES	O	LOCATION

Shaba	O	LOCATION

Shabwa	O	LOCATION

Shanghai	O	LOCATION

SHANGHAI	O	LOCATION

Sharjah	O	LOCATION

Shatoi	O	LOCATION

SHATOI	O	LOCATION

SHEFFIELD	O	LOCATION

Shiraz	O	O

Siauliai	O	LOCATION

Sicily	O	LOCATION

Sierakowice	O	LOCATION

Sierra	O	LOCATION

Sierra	O	LOCATION
Leone	O	LOCATION

Silicon	O	LOCATION
Valley	O	LOCATION

Singapore	O	LOCATION

SINGAPORE	O	LOCATION

Sirnak	O	LOCATION

Sivas	O	O

Skeleton	O	O
Canyon	O	O

Skhirat	O	LOCATION

SKHIRAT	O	LOCATION

Skopje	O	LOCATION

SKOPJE	O	LOCATION

S.	O	LOCATION
Korea	O	LOCATION

Sliema	O	LOCATION

Slovakia	O	LOCATION

Slovenia	O	LOCATION

Sofia	O	LOCATION

SOFIA	O	LOCATION

Sokoto	O	LOCATION

Somalia	O	LOCATION

Son	O	O
Sen	O	O

South	O	O

South	O	LOCATION
Africa	O	LOCATION

SOUTH	O	O
AFRICA	O	O

South	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION

Southampton	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Dakota	O	LOCATION

Southeastern	O	O
Bulgaria	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Island	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Kivu	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Korea	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Miami	O	LOCATION
Hospital	O	LOCATION

South	O	LOCATION
Yemen	O	LOCATION

Soviet	O	LOCATION
Union	O	LOCATION

SPA-FRANCOCHAMPS	O	O

Spa-Francorchamps	O	LOCATION

SPA-FRANCORCHAMPS	O	O

Spain	O	LOCATION

Spitzbergen	O	LOCATION

Split	O	O

Sprague	O	LOCATION

Spring	O	O

Springfield	O	LOCATION

Srebrenica	O	LOCATION

Sri	O	LOCATION
Lanka	O	LOCATION

SRI	O	LOCATION
LANKA	O	LOCATION

Srinagar	O	LOCATION

SRINAGAR	O	LOCATION

Stadium	O	O
Court	O	O

St.	O	LOCATION
Albans	O	LOCATION

St	O	LOCATION
Ansgar	O	LOCATION

Stansted	O	LOCATION

STANSTED	O	LOCATION

STATE	O	O
OF	O	O
OHIO	O	O

St.	O	LOCATION
Christopher	O	LOCATION
Children	O	LOCATION
's	O	LOCATION
Hospital	O	LOCATION

St	O	LOCATION
Croix	O	LOCATION

Steinberg	O	PERSON

Steyr	O	LOCATION

ST	O	LOCATION
HELENS	O	LOCATION

St	O	LOCATION
Louis	O	LOCATION

St.	O	LOCATION
Louis	O	LOCATION

ST	O	LOCATION
LOUIS	O	LOCATION

St.	O	PERSON
Matthew	O	PERSON
's	O	O

Stockholm	O	O

STOCKHOLM	O	LOCATION

Stung	O	O
Treng	O	LOCATION

Stuttgart	O	LOCATION

STUTTGART	O	LOCATION

Sudan	O	LOCATION

SUGO	O	O

Suleimaniya	O	LOCATION

Sullivan	O	PERSON
's	O	O
Island	O	O

Surabaya	O	LOCATION

Surinam	O	LOCATION

Surrey	O	LOCATION

SUZUKA	O	LOCATION

Swe	O	O

Sweden	O	LOCATION

SWEDEN	O	LOCATION

Swerford	O	LOCATION

Switzerland	O	LOCATION

Sydney	O	LOCATION

SYDNEY	O	LOCATION

Syria	O	LOCATION

Taibe	O	LOCATION

TAIBE	O	O

Taipei	O	LOCATION

TAIPEI	O	LOCATION

Taipei	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION
Hospital	O	ORGANIZATION

Taiwan	O	LOCATION

Taiwan	O	LOCATION
Strait	O	LOCATION

Tajikistan	O	LOCATION

TALLINN	O	LOCATION

Tamil	O	LOCATION
Nadu	O	LOCATION

Tampere	O	LOCATION

Tando	O	PERSON
Allahyar	O	PERSON

Tanzania	O	LOCATION

Tartous	O	LOCATION

Tasmania	O	LOCATION

Tatarstan	O	LOCATION

Tauranaga	O	LOCATION

Tauranga	O	LOCATION

Tegel	O	LOCATION

TEGUCIGALPA	O	LOCATION

Tehran	O	LOCATION

TEHRAN	O	LOCATION

Tel	O	LOCATION
Aviv	O	LOCATION

Telfer	O	PERSON

Tempelhof	O	LOCATION

Tender	O	O
Heart	O	O

Texas	O	LOCATION

Texas	O	LOCATION
Panhandle	O	LOCATION

Thailand	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
Netherlands	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
Oval	O	O

Thessaloniki	O	LOCATION

Tianjin	O	LOCATION

Tibet	O	LOCATION

Tijuana	O	LOCATION

Tirana	O	LOCATION

TIRANA	O	LOCATION

Togo	O	LOCATION

TOGO	O	LOCATION

Tokyo	O	LOCATION

TOKYO	O	LOCATION

Tonga	O	LOCATION

Tongo	O	LOCATION
Field	O	LOCATION

Topolcany	O	LOCATION

Toronto	O	LOCATION

TORONTO	O	LOCATION

Torshavn	O	LOCATION

Trax	O	O

Trent	O	LOCATION
Bridge	O	LOCATION

Trepca	O	LOCATION

Trincomalee	O	LOCATION

Trinidad	O	LOCATION

Trinidad	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Tobago	O	LOCATION

Tripoli	O	LOCATION

TRIPOLI	O	LOCATION

Tubmanburg	O	LOCATION

Tunbridge	O	PERSON
Wells	O	PERSON

Tunceli	O	LOCATION

TUNIS	O	LOCATION

Tunisia	O	LOCATION

Turin	O	LOCATION

Turkey	O	LOCATION

Turner	O	O

Turnhout	O	LOCATION

Tuscany	O	LOCATION

Twyford	O	O
Down	O	O

TX	O	O

UAE	O	O

Ubimini	O	LOCATION

Uganda	O	LOCATION

UGANDA	O	LOCATION

Ujjain	O	LOCATION

UK	O	LOCATION

U.K.	O	LOCATION

Ukraina	O	O
Palace	O	O

Ukraine	O	LOCATION

Ulsan	O	LOCATION

Umbria	O	LOCATION

Umm	O	O
Qasr	O	O

United	O	LOCATION
Kingdom	O	LOCATION

United	O	LOCATION
States	O	LOCATION

University	O	ORGANIZATION
Hospital	O	ORGANIZATION

Uppsala	O	LOCATION

Uruguay	O	LOCATION

US	O	LOCATION

U.S	O	LOCATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION

USA	O	LOCATION

USAC	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Gulf	O	LOCATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Middle	O	LOCATION
East	O	LOCATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Midwest	O	LOCATION

Utah	O	LOCATION

Va	O	O

Vaduz	O	LOCATION

Valencia	O	LOCATION

Valletta	O	LOCATION

VALLETTA	O	LOCATION

Van	O	O

Vancouver	O	LOCATION

VANCOUVER	O	LOCATION

Vanderbijlpark	O	LOCATION

Vatican	O	LOCATION

Vavuniya	O	LOCATION

Veliko	O	LOCATION
Tarnovo	O	LOCATION

Venezuela	O	LOCATION

Venray	O	O

VENTURA	O	O

Vermont	O	LOCATION

Vermont	O	LOCATION
Central	O	LOCATION
Hospital	O	LOCATION

Verona	O	PERSON

VERONA	O	LOCATION

Victor	O	PERSON
Babes	O	PERSON

Victoria	O	LOCATION

Victoria	O	LOCATION
Falls	O	LOCATION

Vienna	O	LOCATION

VIENNA	O	LOCATION

Vinnytsya	O	O

Virginia	O	LOCATION

Volendam	O	LOCATION

Vt	O	O

WA	O	O

Waiau	O	PERSON

Wales	O	LOCATION

WALES	O	LOCATION

Wall	O	O
Street	O	O

Warsaw	O	LOCATION

WARSAW	O	LOCATION

Wash	O	O

WASHINGTON	O	LOCATION

Washington	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
D.C.	O	LOCATION

Waterville	O	LOCATION

W.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
India	O	ORGANIZATION

Welikanda	O	LOCATION

Wellington	O	LOCATION

WELLINGTON	O	LOCATION

Wembley	O	LOCATION

Wenatchee	O	LOCATION

West	O	O

West	O	LOCATION
Azerbaijan	O	LOCATION

West	O	LOCATION
Bank	O	LOCATION

West	O	LOCATION
Bengal	O	LOCATION

WESTERN	O	O
HEMISPHERE	O	O

Western	O	O
Ukraine	O	LOCATION

West	O	O
Indies	O	O

Weston-super-Mare	O	O

West	O	O
South	O	O
Central	O	O

West	O	LOCATION
Virginia	O	LOCATION

White	O	O
House	O	O

Whittier	O	LOCATION

Wiltshire	O	LOCATION

Wimbledon	O	O

WIMBLEDON	O	LOCATION

Windhoek	O	LOCATION

WINNIPEG	O	LOCATION

Wis	O	O

Wisc	O	O
.	O	O

Wisconsin	O	LOCATION

Wolf	O	O
Point	O	O

Woodlands	O	O
Nursing	O	O
Home	O	O

Woodridge	O	LOCATION

Worcester	O	LOCATION

Wroclaw	O	O

W.	O	O
Va	O	O

Yemen	O	LOCATION

Yingkou	O	LOCATION

YORK	O	O

Yosu	O	LOCATION

Yugoslavia	O	LOCATION

Zabrze	O	O

Zadar	O	LOCATION

Zagreb	O	LOCATION

ZAGREB	O	LOCATION

Zaire	O	LOCATION

Zambia	O	LOCATION

Zevenaar	O	O

Zimbabwe	O	LOCATION

ZIMBABWE	O	LOCATION

Zurich	O	LOCATION

ZURICH	O	LOCATION

Zvornik	O	LOCATION

10.5	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

103.8	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

104	O	O
43'	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

105	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O

106.3	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

107	O	O
22'	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O

107.9	O	O
-	O	O
108.9	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

109	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O

109.1	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

109.5	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

110.4	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

110.5	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

112.1	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

112.3	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

112.5	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

113	O	O
�	O	O
38'	O	O
West	O	O

114	O	O
04'	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

114	O	O
�	O	O
04'	O	O
West	O	O

115.0	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

118.2	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

118.7	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

119.9	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

12	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

122	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

123.8	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

129.0	O	O
degrees	O	O
east	O	O
longitude	O	O

14.5	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

14.6	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

14.8	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

15	O	O
�	O	O
32'	O	O
North	O	O

15.1	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

16	O	O
�	O	O
58'	O	O
North	O	O

16	O	O
58'	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

16.0	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

17	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

17.2	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

17.6	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

18	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

18.0	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

18.3	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

18.4	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

18.9	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

19.1	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

19.6	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

20.6	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

22.4	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

23	O	O
�	O	O
25'	O	O
34	O	O

5	O	O
degree	O	O
North	O	O

6�	O	O
N	O	O

8�	O	O
33'	O	O
03	O	O

8	O	O
37'	O	O
44	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

8.9	O	O
-	O	O
9.9	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

89	O	O
degrees	O	O
north	O	O
latitude	O	O

Nam	O	O
Quan	O	O
Gate	O	O

Ta	O	O
Coc	O	O
Gate	O	O

Tay	O	O
Ha	O	O
Gate	O	O

Viet	O	O
Bac	O	O
Resistance	O	O
Base	O	O

Fairy	O	O
Pond	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
1	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
1A	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
2	O	O

Hamlet	O	PERSON
20	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
3	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
5	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
6	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
7	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
8	O	O

An	O	O
Phai	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

An	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Bai	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Bau	O	O
Ca	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Bau	O	O
Cap	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Bau	O	O
Trau	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Bau	O	O
Tron	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Bay	O	O
Sang	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Do	O	O
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	O
An	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Dang	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	PERSON
Khuong	O	PERSON
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	O
My	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Ninh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Binh	O	PERSON
Thang	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Buu	O	PERSON
2	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Cay	O	O
Bang	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Cay	O	O
Bang	O	O
2	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Chanh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Chua	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Cu	O	O
Lao	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Dam	O	O
Cung	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Dong	O	PERSON
Ba	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Dong	O	PERSON
Hien	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Dong	O	PERSON
hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Dong	O	PERSON
Tam	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Duong	O	PERSON
Bao	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hai	O	PERSON
Ha	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hai	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hiep	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hoa	O	PERSON
Hinh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hoa	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hoa	O	PERSON
Khanh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Hon	O	PERSON
Goi	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Kakot	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Khai	O	PERSON
Long	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Kinh	O	PERSON
8A	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Long	O	O
An	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Long	O	O
Dinh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Long	O	O
Phu	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Long	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Long	O	O
Thoi	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Lung	O	O
Kon	O	O
Tha	O	O
May	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Mai	O	PERSON
Huong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Minh	O	PERSON
Nghia	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Moi	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Moi	O	PERSON
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Moi	O	PERSON
Mot	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Mu	O	O
U	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Mui	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

My	O	O
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

My	O	O
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

My	O	O
Hue	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

My	O	O
Hung	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

My	O	O
Hung	O	O
2	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

My	O	O
Loi	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

My	O	O
Thanh	O	O
A	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Nam	O	PERSON
Chanh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Noi	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Nui	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Pho	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Phu	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phu	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phu	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phu	O	O
Lam	O	O
2	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Phu	O	O
Loi	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Phu	O	O
Long	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Phu	O	O
Quoi	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Phu	O	O
Son	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phu	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phuoc	O	PERSON
Tho	O	PERSON
Hau	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Phuoc	O	PERSON
Tu	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Rach	O	PERSON
Bao	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Rach	O	PERSON
Cheo	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Tan	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Hamlets	O	O

Rach	O	O
Ham	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Rang	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Ruong	O	O
Lon	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Son	O	O
Ha	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Song	O	O
May	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Suoi	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Suoi	O	PERSON
Da	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Suoi	O	PERSON
Hanh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Suoi	O	O
May	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tam	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Tan	O	O
Dien	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Hanh	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Tan	O	O
Hoi	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Lap	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Long	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Phuc	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Quoi	O	O
Tay	O	O
B	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thuan	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tan	O	O
Tinh	O	O
A	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Tay	O	PERSON
B	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thanh	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
2	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thanh	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thanh	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thanh	O	O
Loi	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Phu	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Thoi	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thoi	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thuan	O	PERSON
Tri	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Thuong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Tien	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Tra	O	O
Quyt	O	O
B	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Trai	O	PERSON
Luan	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Tram	O	O
Bom	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Trung	O	O
Bac	O	O
Hung	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Truong	O	PERSON
hien	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Vinh	O	PERSON
Loi	O	PERSON
1	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Vinh	O	PERSON
Moi	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Vinh	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Xeo	O	O
Ro	O	O
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Xom	O	O
Chua	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Xuan	O	PERSON
Thoi	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

North,	O	O
NorthWest,	O	O
SouthEast	O	O
of	O	O
Ho	O	O
Chi	O	O
Minh	O	O
City	O	O

Northern	O	O
Cam	O	O
Ranh	O	O
Peninsula	O	O

Northern	O	LOCATION
California	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	LOCATION
Carolina	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	O
Europe	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	O
Kavakaz	O	O

Northern	O	O
Kenya	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	O
Laos	O	O

Northern	O	LOCATION
Los	O	LOCATION
Angeles	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	O
Ossetia	O	O

Northern	O	O
Siberia	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
of	O	O
Ben	O	LOCATION
Hai	O	LOCATION
River	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
of	O	O
Gianh	O	LOCATION
River	O	LOCATION

Northern	O	O
Tay	O	PERSON
Nguyen	O	PERSON

Northern	O	O
Thailand	O	LOCATION

North	O	LOCATION
Korea	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
Yorkshire	O	LOCATION

Cat	O	O
Vang	O	O
Beach	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Da	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Dam	O	O
Trau	O	O
Beach	O	O

Duong	O	PERSON
Cam	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Ganh	O	PERSON
Dau	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Me	O	O
Ly	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Nhat	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Quang	O	PERSON
Khanh	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Da	O	O
Phuoc	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Dong	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Efeh	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Khanh	O	O
Son	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Tan	O	O
Lap	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Tay	O	PERSON
Bac	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Da	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
Garbage	O	O
Dumps	O	O

Sao	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Hong	O	LOCATION
River	O	LOCATION
Plain	O	LOCATION

Thuy	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Sai	O	O
Dong	O	O
Parking	O	O
Lot	O	O

Truoc	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Bac	O	O
Lieu	O	O
Beach	O	O

Bahia	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Bao	O	PERSON
Ninh	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Binh	O	LOCATION
Son	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Bondi	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Bournemouth	O	LOCATION
Pier	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Clifton	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Co	O	O
Thach	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Cua	O	LOCATION
Dai	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Do	O	O
Son	O	O
Beach	O	O

Ho	O	O
Tram	O	O
Beach	O	O

Ky	O	O
Tan	O	O
Beach	O	O

Lang	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Beach	O	ORGANIZATION

Lien	O	PERSON
Huong	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Miami	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Myrtle	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Nghia	O	O
An	O	O
Beach	O	O

Nha	O	LOCATION
Trang	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Ninh	O	PERSON
Chu	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Non	O	O
Nuoc	O	O
Beach	O	O

Northern	O	O
French	O	O
Normandy	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Ong	O	O
Dung	O	O
Beach	O	O

Phuoc	O	O
My	O	O
Beach	O	O

Quy	O	LOCATION
Nhon	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Scheviningen	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Tam	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Beach	O	O

Thach	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Lo	O	O
Dieu	O	O
Hamlet	O	O
Beach	O	O

Thuan	O	O
An	O	O
Beach	O	O

Vung	O	O
Tau	O	O
Beach	O	O

Varadero	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Vung	O	O
Bau	O	O
Beach	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Lu	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Cua	O	O
Tung	O	O
Beach	O	O

Dai	O	LOCATION
Lanh	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

My	O	O
Khe	O	O
Beach	O	O

My	O	O
Son	O	O
Beach	O	O

Rang	O	O
Dong	O	O
Beach	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Thuy	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Xuan	O	PERSON
Huong	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Xuan	O	PERSON
Thieu	O	PERSON
Beach	O	PERSON

Nam	O	O
Lo	O	O
Phong	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Ba	O	O
Village	O	O

Bau	O	O
Village	O	O

Cha	O	O
May	O	O
B	O	O
Village	O	O

Chieng	O	O
Di	O	O
village	O	O

Co	O	O
Phat	O	O
village	O	O

Cua	O	O
Rao	O	O
1	O	O
village	O	O

Doi	O	PERSON
2	O	O
village	O	O

Don	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Giang	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Huoi	O	O
La	O	O
village	O	O

Huoi	O	PERSON
Tho	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Ka	O	O
Ai	O	O
village	O	O

Karen	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Khe	O	LOCATION
Bung	O	LOCATION
Village	O	LOCATION

Khe	O	ORGANIZATION
Con	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Phat	O	O
village	O	O

Long	O	O
Luong	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Meo	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Nhap	O	O
highlang	O	O
village	O	O

Goc	O	O
Da	O	O
new	O	O
village	O	O

My	O	O
village	O	O

Nam	O	PERSON
Kha	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Nhap	O	O
village	O	O

Pa	O	O
Ty	O	O
village	O	O

Pam	O	PERSON
Lot	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Pha	O	PERSON
Sac	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Phin	O	PERSON
Ho	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Po	O	O
Lieu	O	O
village	O	O

Poom	O	PERSON
Khuong	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Puc	O	O
village	O	O

Pung	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Pung	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Co	O	O
Phat	O	O
village	O	O

Ruc	O	O
village	O	O

Seo	O	O
Lung	O	O
village	O	O

Ta	O	O
Ghenh	O	O
village	O	O

Ta	O	O
Phin	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Trung	O	PERSON
village	O	O

Tung	O	PERSON
Chin	O	PERSON
1	O	O
village	O	O

Xop	O	O
Mat	O	O
village	O	O

Alaska	O	LOCATION
island	O	O

Camau	O	O
island	O	O

Camranh	O	O
island	O	O

Dongduong	O	O
island	O	O

Hicacos	O	O
island	O	O

Hongom	O	O
island	O	O

Kowloon	O	LOCATION
island	O	O

Linhdam	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Malaysia	O	LOCATION
island	O	O

South	O	O
Pole	O	O
island	O	O

Nhonhoi	O	O
island	O	O

Santubong	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Somalia	O	LOCATION
island	O	O

Sontra	O	O
island	O	O

Thanhda	O	O
island	O	O

Trieutien	O	O
island	O	O

Westerplatte	O	O
island	O	O

Yucantan	O	O
island	O	O

Alabama	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Alaska	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Amazon	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Anambra	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Arkansas	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Arunachal	O	O
Pradesh	O	O
state	O	O

Assam	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Baden	O	PERSON
state	O	O

Bahia	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Baja	O	O
california	O	O
state	O	O

Bihar	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Brandenburg	O	O
state	O	O

Cali	O	O
state	O	O

California	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Chahattisgarh	O	O
state	O	O

Chihuahua	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Chin	O	O
state	O	O

Colorado	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Connecticut	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Delaware	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Durange	O	O
state	O	O

Ebonyi	O	O
state	O	O

Edo	O	O
state	O	O

Falcon	O	O
state	O	O

Florida	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Haryana	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Himachal	O	O
Pradesh	O	O
state	O	O

Idaho	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Illiniois	O	O
state	O	O

Indiana	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Iowa	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Jharkhand	O	O
state	O	O

Kanas	O	PERSON
state	O	O

Karnataka	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Kedah	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Kerala	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Kogi	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Louisiana	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Maine	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Malacca	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Martland	O	PERSON
state	O	O

Massachusetts	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Mato	O	PERSON
Grosso	O	PERSON
do	O	O
Sul	O	O
state	O	O

Michigan	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Northern	O	O
Uttarakhand	O	O
state	O	O

Western	O	O
Jalisco	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Zulia	O	LOCATION
western	O	O
state	O	O

Mid	O	O
Kogi	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Minnesota	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Mississipi	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Missouri	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Montana	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Nebraska	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Nevada	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
Hampshire	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
Mexico	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

New	O	O
Orlean	O	O
state	O	O

New	O	LOCATION
York	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Niedersachsen	O	O
state	O	O

Ohio	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Ontario	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Oregon	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Oyo	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Pennsylvania	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Perak	O	O
state	O	O

Minnesota	O	LOCATION
countryside	O	O
state	O	O

Queenland	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Rajasthan	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Rhineland	O	O
state	O	O

Rhode	O	LOCATION
Island	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Rio	O	LOCATION
de	O	LOCATION
Janeiro	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Sao	O	LOCATION
Paulo	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Saxony	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Schleswing	O	O
holstein	O	O
state	O	O

Selangor	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Sonora	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

South	O	LOCATION
Carolina	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

South	O	LOCATION
Dakota	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Tamil	O	O
Nadu	O	O
state	O	O

Western	O	O
Australia	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Tennessee	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Terengganu	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Texas	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Toronto	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Uath	O	O
state	O	O

Uttar	O	O
pradesh	O	O
state	O	O

Virginia	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Washington	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Wisconsin	O	LOCATION
state	O	O

Champa	O	LOCATION
museum	O	O

The	O	O
southern	O	O
agriculture	O	O
of	O	O
museum	O	O

Seoul	O	LOCATION
national	O	O
museum	O	O

AnSuong	O	O
station	O	O

North	O	O
MyThuan	O	O
port	O	O

BachDang	O	PERSON
port	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Gao	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Tho	O	O
Quang	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

CaTang	O	O
wharf	O	O

Cam	O	PERSON
Lam	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Alexandre	O	PERSON
harbour	O	O

SaKy	O	O
harbour	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Chay	O	O
Tourist	O	O
Wharf	O	O

Dinh	O	O
wharf	O	O

Dinh	O	O
Yen	O	O
wharf	O	O

An	O	O
Phu	O	O
Dong	O	O
wharf	O	O

CaTang	O	O
wharf	O	O

Linh	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O
wharf	O	O

ChomLom	O	O
wharf	O	O

NhonMy-MuongRanh	O	O
wharf	O	O

Nuoc	O	O
Nong	O	O
wharf	O	O

Ong	O	PERSON
Luu	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

RocTruong	O	O
wharf	O	O

PhuocKhanh	O	O
commune	O	O
wharf	O	O

QuangHai	O	O
commune	O	O
wharf	O	O

YenVy	O	O
wharf	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Bo	O	PERSON
Dau	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

HaLong	O	O
station	O	O

Korea	O	LOCATION
wharf	O	O

Ko	O	O
Kong	O	O
hahour	O	O

Nha	O	PERSON
Rong	O	PERSON
wharf/Dragon	O	O
house	O	O
wharf	O	O

Ninh	O	PERSON
Kieu	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Nua	O	O
wharf	O	O

CanTho	O	O
ferry	O	O

CatLai	O	O
ferry	O	O

HamLuong	O	O
ferry	O	O

HauGiang	O	O
ferry	O	O

Rung	O	O
ferry	O	O

ThuThiem	O	O
ferry	O	O

VamSat	O	O
ferry	O	O

Xom	O	O
Chai	O	O
ferry	O	O

Pha	O	PERSON
Den	O	PERSON
port	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Hoai	O	O
river	O	O
wharf	O	O

Roc	O	O
Truong	O	O
river	O	O
wharf	O	O

Thach	O	O
Han	O	O
river	O	O
wharf	O	O

The	O	O
Bund	O	O

Van	O	O
village	O	O
boat	O	O
wharf	O	O

Giai	O	PERSON
Oan	O	PERSON
stream	O	O
boat	O	O
wharf	O	O

Tramen	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Kieu	O	PERSON
wharf	O	O

Vam	O	O
Lung	O	O
wharf	O	O

Van	O	O
boat	O	O
wharf	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
commune	O	O
wharf	O	O

National	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Brighton	O	LOCATION
port	O	O

Can	O	O
Tho	O	O
port	O	O

Ansuong	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Camau	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Caitac	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Cholon	O	LOCATION
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Cholon	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Cuchi	O	O
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Danang	O	LOCATION
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Gialam	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Giapbat	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Hatinh	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Kimlien	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Kimma	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Mien	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Mien	O	PERSON
Tay	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

My	O	O
Dinh	O	O
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Nam	O	O
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Nam	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
bus	O	O
station	O	O

District	O	O
8	O	O
bus	O	O
station	O	O

Quinhon	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Soctrang	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Tayninh	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Coach	O	O
station	O	O
of	O	O
TamBinh	O	O
town	O	O

Coach	O	O
station	O	O
of	O	O
Vinhlong	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O

TraMen	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O

Central	O	O
coach	O	O
station	O	O
of	O	O
Kuala	O	LOCATION
Lumpur	O	LOCATION

Arabic	O	O
sea	O	O

Adriatic	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

Aegean	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

Alabama	O	LOCATION
sea	O	O

Altona	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

An	O	O
Hai	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Andaman	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

BaRia-VungTau	O	O
sea	O	O

Seafront	O	O
Beach	O	O

Baltic	O	O
sea	O	O

Ban	O	O
Than	O	O
sea	O	O

Carlifornia	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

Cambodia	O	LOCATION
sea	O	O

Can	O	O
Gio	O	O
sea	O	O

Caribbean	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

Caribbean	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

Caspian	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

Cham	O	LOCATION
Island	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Cua	O	PERSON
Dai	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
sea	O	O

Atlantic	O	LOCATION
Ocean	O	LOCATION

Con	O	O
Co	O	O
sea	O	O
island	O	O

The	O	O
Mediterranean	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
American	O	O
East	O	O
Sea	O	O

The	O	O
Northeast	O	LOCATION
Brazil	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

Ha	O	O
Tinh	O	O
beach	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
Nam	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Hawaii	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Ho	O	O
Coc	O	O
beach	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Khai	O	PERSON
Long	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Kwazulu-Natal	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Lang	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
beach	O	O

Lien	O	PERSON
Chieu	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Thuan	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Long	O	O
Hai	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Ly	O	O
Son	O	O
beach	O	O

The	O	O
English	O	O
Channel	O	O

My	O	O
Khe	O	O
beach	O	O

The	O	O
South	O	O
China	O	LOCATION
Sea	O	LOCATION

Antarctica	O	LOCATION
Ocean	O	LOCATION

Ngu	O	PERSON
Hanh	O	PERSON
Son	O	PERSON
sea	O	O
beach	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Tat	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
sea	O	O

Nha	O	O
Mat	O	O
beach	O	O

Nha	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Ninh	O	PERSON
Chu	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Normandy	O	LOCATION
Beach	O	LOCATION

Padang	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Pas-de-lais	O	O
beach	O	O

Cuba	O	LOCATION
North	O	O
coast	O	O

North	O	O
Korea's	O	O
East	O	O
sea	O	O

East	O	O
Korean	O	O
sea	O	O

East	O	O
Idonesian	O	O
sea	O	O

NorthEast	O	O
Philippine	O	O
sea	O	O

West	O	O
Java's	O	O
South	O	LOCATION
sea	O	LOCATION

South	O	O
Africa's	O	O
West	O	O
sea	O	O

Hainan	O	LOCATION
Island's	O	O
SouthWest	O	O
sea	O	O

Phu	O	O
Yen	O	O
beach	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Ngai	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Quy	O	PERSON
Nhon	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Rio	O	LOCATION
de	O	LOCATION
Janeiro	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Sa	O	PERSON
Huynh	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Sa	O	O
Ky	O	O
beach	O	O

Sam	O	PERSON
Son	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Senegal	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Somalia	O	LOCATION
sea	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thanh	O	O
beach	O	O

Tasman	O	O
beach	O	O

Pacific	O	LOCATION
ocean	O	O

Thien	O	PERSON
Cam	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Tho	O	O
Quang	O	O
beach	O	O

Thua	O	O
Thien-Hue	O	O
beach	O	O

Thuan	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
beach	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
city	O	O
beach	O	O

China	O	LOCATION
sea	O	O

Vietnamese	O	O
sea	O	O

Xuan	O	O
Ha	O	O
beach	O	O

Egyptian	O	O
border	O	O

England-France	O	O
border	O	O

Border	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
state	O	O
of	O	O
Michoacan	O	LOCATION

Border	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
state	O	O
of	O	O
Washington	O	LOCATION

Cambodian	O	O
border	O	O

Canadian-US	O	O
border	O	O

Cau	O	O
Treo	O	O
border	O	O

Chechnya	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Ingushetia	O	LOCATION
border	O	O

Colombia	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Venezuela	O	LOCATION
border	O	O

Thai's	O	O
SouthEast	O	O
border	O	O

Iran	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Pakistan	O	LOCATION
border	O	O

Laos-Thailand	O	O
border	O	O

US-Mexico	O	O
border	O	O

Pakistan-Afghanistan	O	O
border	O	O

French	O	O
border	O	O

France-Spain	O	O
border	O	O

France-Swiss	O	O
border	O	O

Thailand-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

Thailand-Myanmar	O	O
border	O	O

Thailand-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

China-Laos	O	O
border	O	O

China-North	O	LOCATION
Korea	O	LOCATION
border	O	O

Vietnam-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-Laos	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-China	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-Laos	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-China	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

Vietnam-Cambodia	O	O
border	O	O

South	O	O
Bolivia	O	LOCATION
plain	O	O

The	O	O
South	O	O
bank	O	O
of	O	O
Gianh	O	O
river	O	O

Sunshine	O	O
Beach	O	O

Brazil	O	LOCATION
beach	O	O

Cua	O	PERSON
Dai	O	PERSON
coast	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
coast	O	O

East	O	O
coast	O	O

East	O	O
Taiwan	O	O
coast	O	O

Guatemala	O	LOCATION
coast	O	O

South	O	O
Philippine	O	O
coast	O	O

France	O	LOCATION
coast	O	O

France	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Portugal	O	LOCATION
coast	O	O

Philippine	O	O
East	O	O
coast	O	O

Somalia	O	LOCATION
East	O	O
coast	O	O

Somalia	O	LOCATION
coast	O	O

Pacific	O	O
coast	O	O

Catanduanes	O	O
provine	O	O
coast	O	O

China	O	LOCATION
coast	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Tu	O	PERSON
Long	O	PERSON
Bay	O	PERSON

Dak	O	O
Rang	O	O
Village	O	O

D'Ha	O	O
Village	O	O

M'Lieng	O	O
Village	O	O

Ndrung	O	LOCATION
Village	O	LOCATION

Ru	O	O
Village	O	O

Darahoa	O	LOCATION
Mountain	O	LOCATION
Village	O	LOCATION

Thuan	O	PERSON
An,	O	O
Chan	O	O
May,	O	O
Lang	O	O
Co	O	O
Beaches	O	O

Assam,	O	O
Nagaland,	O	O
Manipur	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Arunachal	O	LOCATION
Pradesh	O	LOCATION
States	O	LOCATION

Karnataka	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Andhra	O	LOCATION
Pradesh	O	LOCATION
States	O	LOCATION

SouthWest	O	O
American	O	O
States	O	O

Pennsylvania,	O	O
Maryland,	O	O
Virginia,	O	O
West	O	O
Virginia,	O	O
Kentucky	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Delaware	O	LOCATION
States	O	LOCATION

Mien	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Mien	O	O
Tay	O	O
Inter-provincial	O	O
Coach	O	O
Stations	O	O

Nuoc	O	O
Len,	O	O
Lo	O	O
Gom	O	O
bridges	O	O

Phu	O	O
My,	O	O
Thu	O	O
Thiem	O	O
bridges	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Trieu,	O	O
Giong	O	O
Ong	O	O
To	O	O
Bridges	O	O

Toji,	O	O
Kiyomizu,	O	O
Enryaku,	O	O
Daigo,	O	O
Nima,	O	O
Byodo,	O	O
Kozan,	O	O
Saiho,	O	O
Tenryu,	O	O
Kinkaku,	O	O
Ginkaka,	O	O
Ryoan,	O	O
Hongwan	O	O
Pagodas	O	O

Vu	O	O
Gia,	O	O
Thu	O	O
Bon	O	O
Rivers	O	O

Long	O	O
Van,	O	O
An	O	O
Duong	O	O
Vuong,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Tai	O	O
Parks	O	O

Gac	O	O
Ma,	O	O
Co	O	O
Lin,	O	O
Chau	O	LOCATION
Vien	O	LOCATION
Islands	O	LOCATION

Phu	O	O
Quy,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Quoc	O	O
Islands	O	O

Song	O	O
Tu	O	O
Tay,	O	O
Son	O	O
Ca,	O	O
Nam	O	O
Yet,	O	O
Sinh	O	O
Ton,	O	O
Truong	O	LOCATION
Sa	O	LOCATION
Islands	O	LOCATION

Kamigamo,	O	O
Shimogamo,	O	O
Ujigami	O	O
Temples	O	O

Thu	O	O
Bon,	O	O
Vu	O	O
Gia	O	O
Rivers	O	O

Dang	O	O
Thai	O	O
Mai,	O	O
Hoang	O	O
Van	O	O
Thai,	O	O
Le	O	O
Trong	O	O
Tan	O	O
Streets	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Huy	O	PERSON
Luong,	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
An	O	O
Ninh,	O	O
Tran	O	O
Van	O	O
Ky,	O	O
Le	O	PERSON
Quang	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
Streets	O	PERSON

Phan	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
Phung,	O	PERSON
Nguyen	O	PERSON
Trong	O	PERSON
Tuyen,	O	O
Nguyen	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Troi	O	PERSON
Streets	O	PERSON

Thuan	O	PERSON
Kieu,	O	PERSON
Tran	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Trong,	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
Bieu,	O	O
Le	O	O
Hong	O	LOCATION
Phong	O	LOCATION
Streets	O	LOCATION

Prince	O	O
George	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Montgomery	O	O
Counties	O	O

An	O	O
Diem	O	O
1,	O	O
An	O	O
Diem	O	O
2	O	O
Reservoirs	O	O

An	O	O
Minh,	O	O
An	O	O
Bien,	O	O
Hon	O	PERSON
Dat	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Chau	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Districts	O	O

An	O	O
Nhon,	O	O
Hoai	O	PERSON
An,	O	O
Tuy	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
Phu	O	O
My,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Cat	O	O
Districts	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Son,	O	O
Tu	O	O
Nghia	O	O
Districts	O	O

Chau	O	PERSON
Thanh,	O	O
Lai	O	O
Vung,	O	O
Lap	O	O
Vo,	O	O
Tam	O	O
Nong	O	O
Districts	O	O

Chau	O	PERSON
Thanh,	O	O
Long	O	O
My,	O	O
Vi	O	O
Thuy	O	O
Districts	O	O

Cu	O	O
Chi,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Chanh	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Hoc	O	O
Mon	O	O
Districts	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
Loc,	O	O
Dien	O	O
Ban	O	O
Districts	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
Loc,	O	O
Dien	O	O
Ban,	O	O
Duy	O	O
Xuyen,	O	O
Thang	O	O
Binh	O	O
Districts	O	O

Dien	O	O
Ban,	O	O
Duy	O	O
Xuyen	O	O
Districts	O	O

Don	O	PERSON
Duong,	O	PERSON
Duc	O	PERSON
Trong,	O	O
Lac	O	O
Duong	O	O
Districts	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Xuan,	O	O
Tuy	O	O
An,	O	O
Song	O	O
Cau	O	O
Districts	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Vang,	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
Chau,	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Khe	O	O
Districts	O	O

Ia	O	O
Grai,	O	O
Duc	O	O
Co,	O	O
Chu	O	O
Prong	O	O
Districts	O	O

Huong	O	PERSON
Khe,	O	O
Ky	O	O
Anh,	O	O
Vu	O	O
Quang	O	O
Mountain	O	O
Districts	O	O

Ky	O	O
Son,	O	O
Tuong	O	O
Duong,	O	O
Que	O	O
Phong,	O	O
Quy	O	O
Chau	O	O
Mountain	O	O
Districts	O	O

Quang	O	O
Ngai's	O	O
Mountain	O	O
Districts	O	O

Nam	O	O
Tra	O	O
My	O	O
and	O	O
Bac	O	O
Tra	O	O
My	O	O
Districts	O	O

Ngu	O	PERSON
Hanh	O	PERSON
Son,	O	O
Son	O	O
Tra	O	O
Districts	O	O

Nhon	O	O
Trach,	O	O
Trang	O	O
Bom,	O	O
Long	O	O
Thanh,.	O	O
Long	O	O
Khanh	O	O
Districts	O	O

Nui	O	O
Thanh,	O	O
Hoi	O	O
An,	O	O
Dai	O	O
Loc,	O	O
Thang	O	O
Binh	O	O
Districts	O	O

Phu	O	O
Vang,	O	O
Quang	O	O
Dien,	O	O
Huong	O	O
Tra	O	O
Districts	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Dien,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Vang,	O	O
Huong	O	O
Tra,	O	O
Phong	O	O
Dien	O	O
Districts	O	O

Quy	O	O
Chau,	O	O
Quy	O	O
Hop,	O	O
Nghia	O	O
Dan	O	O
Districts	O	O

Quy	O	O
Hop,	O	O
Nghia	O	PERSON
Dan	O	PERSON
Districts	O	PERSON

Sa	O	O
Pa,	O	O
Van	O	O
Ban	O	O
Districts	O	O

Son	O	O
Ha,	O	O
Ba	O	O
To,	O	O
Duc	O	O
Pho	O	O
Districts	O	O

Son	O	O
Tra	O	O
and	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Khe	O	O
Districts	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Phu,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Dai,	O	O
Ba	O	O
Tri	O	O
Districts	O	O

Tu	O	O
Nghia,	O	O
Son	O	O
tinh,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Son	O	O
Districts	O	O

Tuyphuoc,	O	O
Annhon,	O	O
Phucat	O	O
districts	O	O

Tuyphuoc,	O	O
Annhon,	O	O
Phucat,	O	O
Phumy,	O	O
Hoaian,	O	O
Anlao	O	O
districts	O	O

Xuanloc	O	O
and	O	O
Hiepthanh	O	O
districts	O	O

Channels	O	O
of	O	O
C16,	O	O
C14	O	O

The	O	O
areas	O	O
of	O	O
D3,D5,D6,D7,D9	O	O

Dung	O	O
Quat	O	O
resettlement	O	O
zones	O	O

The	O	O
quarter	O	O
of	O	O
6,7,8,9	O	O

The	O	O
areas	O	O
of	O	O
Azamiyah,	O	O
Karradah	O	O

The	O	O
areas	O	O
of	O	O
14	O	O
Ward	O	O

The	O	O
villages	O	O
of	O	O
Diem,	O	O
Noi	O	O
Due,	O	O
Hien	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON

The	O	O
mine	O	O
villages	O	O
of	O	O
Nong	O	O
Son,	O	O
Trung	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON

Po	O	PERSON
Ko	O	PERSON
riverside	O	O
villages	O	O

Vugia-Thubon,	O	O
Ba,	O	O
Con,	O	O
Sesan	O	O
rever	O	O
valleys	O	O

Europe	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Africa	O	LOCATION

European	O	O
countries	O	O

European	O	O
and	O	O
American	O	O
countries	O	O

American	O	O
countries	O	O

African	O	O
countries	O	O

European	O	O
countries	O	O

European	O	O
union	O	O

East	O	O
Asian	O	O
countries	O	O

East	O	O
Euroupean	O	O
countries	O	O

East	O	O
Euroupean	O	O
countries	O	O
and	O	O
soviet	O	O
union	O	O
countries	O	O

Northeast	O	O
Asia	O	O
nation	O	O

Southeast	O	LOCATION
Asia	O	LOCATION
nation	O	O

East	O	O
africa	O	O
countries	O	O

Laos,	O	O
Thailand	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Campuchia	O	O
countries	O	O

Mekong	O	O
valley	O	O

USA,	O	O
Australia,	O	O
Canada	O	LOCATION

Latin	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION

Peru	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Chile	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Argentina	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Paraguay	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Brazil	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
countries	O	O
of	O	O
Mekong	O	O
headwaters	O	O

Western	O	O
countries	O	O

Western	O	O
Europe,	O	O
easten	O	O
europe	O	O

Mid	O	O
asia	O	O
countries	O	O

The	O	O
mid	O	O
European	O	O
and	O	O
east	O	O
European	O	O
countries	O	O

China,	O	O
india	O	LOCATION
countries	O	O

Pacific	O	O
rim	O	O
countries	O	O

Vietnam,	O	O
Laos,	O	O
Cambodia,	O	O
Myanmar,	O	O
Thailand,	O	O
China	O	LOCATION
countries	O	O

Southeast	O	O
asia	O	O
countries	O	O

The	O	O
countries	O	O
of	O	O
Far	O	O
east	O	O
area	O	O

The	O	O
streets	O	O
of	O	O
Da	O	O
Nang,	O	O
Le	O	O
Loi,	O	O
Le	O	O
Lai,	O	O
Nguyen	O	ORGANIZATION
Trai	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
streets	O	O
of	O	O
Hang	O	O
Ma,	O	O
Luong	O	O
Van	O	O
Can,	O	O
Kim	O	PERSON
Ma	O	PERSON

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
1	O	O
,	O	O
2	O	O
,	O	O
3	O	O
,	O	O
4	O	O
,	O	O
5	O	O
,	O	O
6	O	O

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
5	O	O
,	O	O
11	O	O
,	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
13	O	O
,	O	O
15	O	O

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
5	O	O
,	O	O
12	O	O
,	O	O
13	O	O
va	O	O
14	O	O

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Phu	O	O
Dong,	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Loc,	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Xuan	O	O

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
Son	O	O
Ky,	O	O
Hoa	O	LOCATION
Thanh	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
Tay	O	O
Thanh,	O	O
Son	O	O
Ky,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Tho	O	O
Hoa	O	O

The	O	O
ward	O	O
of	O	O
Thuan	O	O
Loc,	O	O
Huong	O	O
So,	O	O
An	O	O
Hoa,	O	O
Xuan	O	O
Phu,	O	O
An	O	O
Dong	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
1,	O	O
3	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
1,	O	O
3,	O	O
11	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
2,	O	O
4,	O	O
6,	O	O
8,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON

District	O	O
of	O	O
2,	O	O
7	O	O
and	O	O
8	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
8	O	O
,	O	O
Tan	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON

District	O	O
of	O	O
Go	O	O
Vap,	O	O
Tan	O	O
Binh	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
Hai	O	O
Ba	O	O
Trung,	O	O
Dong	O	O
Da,	O	O
Ba	O	O
Dinh	O	O

District	O	O
of	O	O
Phu	O	PERSON
Nhuan	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
,	O	O
4	O	O

American	O	O
nations	O	O

The	O	O
nations	O	O
of	O	O
Balkan	O	LOCATION
area	O	O

The	O	O
airport	O	O
of	O	O
Narita	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Chubu	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Kansai	O	ORGANIZATION
,	O	O
Nagoya	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Fukuoka	O	LOCATION

My	O	O
Tho	O	O
-	O	O
Ba	O	O
Lai	O	O
-	O	O
Ham	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
rivers	O	O

Urgup,	O	O
Goreme,	O	O
Uchisar,	O	O
Avanos,	O	O
Mustafapasa	O	O
towns	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
of	O	O
6	O	O
and	O	O
16	O	O

Tan	O	O
Phu	O	O
and	O	O
Phu	O	O
Dong	O	O
hamlets	O	O

A	O	O
Vuong	O	O
hydropower	O	O
,	O	O
Dak	O	O
Mi	O	O
4	O	O
hydropower,	O	O
Song	O	O
Tranh	O	O
2	O	O
hydropower	O	O
and	O	O
Song	O	O
Bung	O	O
4	O	O
hydropower	O	O

The	O	O
state	O	O
of	O	O
Wisconsin	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
IOWA	O	LOCATION

United	O	LOCATION
Arab	O	LOCATION
Emirates	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
and	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
Gia	O	O
Lai,	O	O
Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
and	O	O
city	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
middle	O	O
area	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Giang,	O	O
Dong	O	O
Thap,	O	O
Vinh	O	O
Long,	O	O
Tien	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Giang,	O	O
Kien	O	O
Giang,	O	O
Dong	O	PERSON
Thap	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
north	O	O
Vietnam	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Ben	O	PERSON
Tre,	O	O
Tra	O	O
Vinh,	O	O
Long	O	O
An,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
Tay	O	O
Ninh,	O	O
BA	O	ORGANIZATION
Ria-Vung	O	ORGANIZATION
Tau,	O	O
Hai	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Ha	O	O
Nam	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	O
Duong,	O	O
Dong	O	O
Nai,	O	O
Tay	O	O
Ninh,	O	O
Long	O	O
An	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Duong,	O	O
Ba	O	O
Ria-Vung	O	O
Tau	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Ca	O	O
Mau,	O	O
Bac	O	O
Lieu	O	O
and	O	O
Soc	O	O
Trang	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Dac	O	O
Nong,	O	O
Dac	O	O
Lac,	O	O
Kontum	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Dien	O	O
Bien,	O	O
Lai	O	O
Chau,	O	O
Lao	O	O
Cai,	O	O
Yen	O	O
Bai	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Son	O	O
La	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
north	O	O
Vietnam	O	LOCATION
delta	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Mekong	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O

The	O	O
provineces	O	O
of	O	O
Northern	O	O
midland	O	O
and	O	O
north	O	O
Vietnam	O	LOCATION
delta	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
southeast	O	O
Cambodia	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
South-eastern	O	O
region	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
South-eastern	O	O
region	O	O
and	O	O
Mekong	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O

the	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
South-eastern	O	O
region	O	O
and	O	O
central	O	O
costal	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Dong	O	PERSON
Thap	O	PERSON
and	O	O
An	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
central	O	O
costal	O	O
provinces	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Gia	O	O
Lai,	O	O
Kontum,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Gia	O	O
Lai,	O	O
Kontum,	O	O
Quang	O	O
Nam	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Jiang	O	PERSON
Su	O	O
and	O	O
Shandong	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Hu	O	O
Nan,	O	O
Ha	O	O
Nam	O	O
and	O	O
Shandong	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Mekong	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O
area	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Red	O	O
river	O	O
delta	O	O
area	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O
area	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Lai	O	O
Chau,	O	O
Son	O	O
La,	O	O
Ha	O	O
Giang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
North	O	O
region	O	O

Eastern	O	O
provinces	O	O

Eastern,	O	O
western,	O	O
and	O	O
southwest	O	O
provinces	O	O

South	O	O
eastern	O	O
and	O	O
southwest	O	O
provinces	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
southern	O	O
Philippines	O	LOCATION

Southwest	O	O
provinces	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
midlands	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
southern,	O	O
northern,	O	O
western	O	O
and	O	O
middle	O	O
Czech	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
southern	O	O
region	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Nam	O	O
Dinh,	O	O
Thai	O	O
Binh	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Ninh	O	O
Thuan,	O	O
Khanh	O	O
Hoa,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Yen	O	O
and	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Ninh	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Fukijan	O	O
,	O	O
HuNan	O	O
and	O	O
Yunan	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Soc	O	O
Trang,	O	O
Vinh	O	O
Long,	O	O
Dong	O	O
Thap,	O	O
Tien	O	O
Giang,	O	O
Tay	O	O
Ninh,	O	O
Long	O	O
An	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Son	O	O
La,	O	O
Lang	O	PERSON
Son,	O	O
Bac	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Quang	O	PERSON
Ninh	O	PERSON

the	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Shanxi,	O	O
Shandong,	O	O
Hebei	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Beijing	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
northwestern	O	O
region	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O
and	O	O
southern	O	O
region	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Tay	O	O
Ninh,	O	O
Dong	O	PERSON
Nai	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Thai	O	O
Nguyen,	O	O
Ha	O	O
Tay	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Thanh	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Nghe	O	O
An	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
Tien	O	PERSON
Giang,	O	PERSON
Ben	O	PERSON
Tre,	O	O
Vinh	O	O
Long,	O	O
Dong	O	O
Thap	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
of	O	O
central	O	O
coast	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
Danang	O	LOCATION
to	O	O
Binhdinh	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
Quang	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
to	O	O
Quang	O	PERSON
Ngai	O	PERSON

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
Thai	O	O
Binh	O	O
to	O	O
Thua	O	O
Thien	O	O
Hue	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
Thanh	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
to	O	O
Thua	O	O
Thien	O	O
Hue	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
Thua	O	O
Thien	O	O
Hue	O	O
to	O	O
Kien	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON

Central	O	O
coastal	O	O
provinces	O	O

Central	O	O
coastal	O	O
provinces	O	O

The	O	O
provinces	O	O
from	O	O
southeastern	O	O
region	O	O

Group	O	O
of	O	O
3,	O	O
4	O	O

The	O	O
population	O	O
groups	O	O
of	O	O
34-39,	O	O
61	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Au	O	O
Co,	O	O
Luy	O	O
Ban	O	O
Bich,	O	O
Ba	O	O
Hom	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Bach	O	LOCATION
Dang	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Thanh	O	PERSON
Da,	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Quoi	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Lai	O	PERSON
Thieu	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Mieu	O	PERSON
Noi	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Ben	O	PERSON
Duoc	O	PERSON
temple	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Cach	O	O
mang	O	O
thang	O	O
tam,	O	O
Le	O	O
Van	O	O
Sy,	O	O
Phan	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
Phung	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Dinh	O	LOCATION
Tien	O	LOCATION
Hoang	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Ly	O	O
Thai	O	O
To	O	O
-	O	O
Hang	O	O
Khay	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Le	O	LOCATION
Quang	O	LOCATION
Dinh,	O	O
Tran	O	O
Quoc	O	O
Tuan,	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
Hong,	O	O
Tran	O	O
Quy	O	O
Cap	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Trung	O	LOCATION
Luong	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
My	O	O
Thuan,	O	O
My	O	O
Thuan	O	O
-	O	O
Can	O	O
Tho,	O	O
Bien	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Vung	O	PERSON
Tau,	O	PERSON
Noi	O	PERSON
Bai	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Ha	O	O
Long	O	O
and	O	O
Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Quang	O	PERSON
Ngai	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Vo	O	PERSON
Truong	O	PERSON
Toan,	O	O
Ly	O	PERSON
Thuong	O	PERSON
Kiet,	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
Cong	O	O
Tru	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Ha	O	O
Noi,	O	O
Yen	O	O
Bai,	O	O
Lao	O	O
Cai	O	O

The	O	O
iirigational	O	O
channel	O	O
of	O	O
TC18A	O	O
,	O	O
TC18	O	O
,	O	O
TC17	O	O

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
Xuan	O	O
Thuy,	O	O
Kim	O	PERSON
Ma,	O	O
Giang	O	PERSON
Vo	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
from	O	O
Sai	O	LOCATION
Gon	O	LOCATION
to	O	O
Hue,	O	O
Quy	O	O
Nhon	O	O
and	O	O
Nha	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC,	O	O
Bien	O	O
Hoa,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON

The	O	O
road	O	O
line	O	O
from	O	O
Mekong	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O
to	O	O
My	O	O
Tho	O	O

Coastal	O	O
Pacific	O	O
ocean	O	O

The	O	O
regions	O	O
of	O	O
Cabramatta	O	LOCATION
,	O	O
Bankstown	O	LOCATION
and	O	O
Marrickville	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
regions	O	O
of	O	O
Dai	O	PERSON
Loc,	O	O
Hoi	O	O
An	O	O

The	O	O
Dung	O	O
Quat	O	O
industrial	O	O
zone	O	O
of	O	O
neighboring	O	O
regions	O	O

Hanoi	O	LOCATION
suburbs	O	O

The	O	O
area	O	O
of	O	O
northwest,	O	O
northeast,	O	O
central	O	O
highland,	O	O
and	O	O
Mekong	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O

Asia	O	LOCATION
territorial	O	O
water	O	O

Territorial	O	O
water	O	O
of	O	O
Pacific	O	LOCATION
ocean,	O	O
Indian	O	O
ocean	O	O

Vietnamese	O	O
territorial	O	O
water	O	O

National	O	O
garden	O	O
of	O	O
Tam	O	O
Dao,	O	O
Cuc	O	O
Phuong,	O	O
Bach	O	O
Ma,	O	O
Cat	O	O
Tien	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Dinh	O	O
and	O	O
An	O	O
Nghiep	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	O
Dao,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Trieu	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	O
Phan,	O	O
Long	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	O
Thoi,	O	O
Binh	O	O
Minh,	O	O
Binh	O	O
My,	O	O
Binh	O	PERSON
Chuong	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Ia	O	O
Lop,	O	O
Ia	O	O
Loi	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Ia	O	O
Rve,	O	O
Ia	O	O
Lop,	O	O
Cu	O	O
Kbang	O	O
and	O	O
Ea	O	O
Roc	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Nghia	O	LOCATION
Hiep,	O	O
Nghia	O	LOCATION
Trung	O	LOCATION

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
northern	O	O
Cu	O	O
Chi	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
eastern	O	O
Tuy	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
An	O	O
Nhon	O	O
and	O	O
Phu	O	O
Cat	O	O
district	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
southern	O	O
Mang	O	LOCATION
Yang	O	LOCATION
district	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Que	O	O
Lam,	O	O
Que	O	O
Trung,	O	O
Que	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
Que	O	O
Minh	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Tan	O	O
Cong	O	O
Sinh,	O	O
Hoa	O	O
Binh,	O	O
Phu	O	O
Duc	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Thuy,	O	O
Phuong	O	O
Tien,	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Duc,	O	O
Xin	O	O
Chai,	O	O
Lao	O	O
Chai,	O	O
Phong	O	PERSON
Quang	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Vinh	O	O
Kim,	O	O
Song	O	O
Thuan,	O	O
Kim	O	PERSON
Son	O	PERSON

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
western	O	O
Que	O	O
Son	O	O
district	O	O

The	O	O
county	O	O
town	O	O
of	O	O
Nhon	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Nhon	O	PERSON
Ly	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Arabia	O	O
and	O	O
north	O	O
Africa	O	LOCATION
counties	O	O

Western	O	O
countries	O	O

Phuong	O	PERSON
Nam	O	PERSON
book	O	O
coffee	O	O

Base	O	O
of	O	O
No5	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Du	O	PERSON
base	O	O

The	O	O
USA	O	LOCATION
military	O	O
base	O	O

Amsterdam	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Ba	O	O
Cap	O	O
habour	O	O

Batam	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Thuy	O	PERSON
seaport	O	O

Busan	O	O
habour	O	O

Ca	O	O
Mau	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Ly	O	O
Son	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Sa	O	O
Ky	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Tho	O	O
Quang	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Tuan	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Tran	O	O
De	O	O
fishing	O	O
port	O	O

Cai	O	PERSON
Cui	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Calais	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Can	O	O
Tho	O	O
habour	O	O

Cao	O	O
Hung	O	O
habour	O	O

Cat	O	O
Lai	O	O
habour	O	O

Cat	O	O
Lo	O	O
habour	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon	O	O
center	O	O
container	O	O
habour	O	O

Cua	O	O
Lo	O	O
habour	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Phu	O	O
Dinh	O	O
wholesale	O	O
habour	O	O

Dinh	O	O
Vu	O	O
habour	O	O

Dung	O	O
Quat	O	O
habour	O	O

El	O	PERSON
Mann	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Gdansk	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Go	O	O
Dau	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Gwadar	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Ha	O	O
Loc	O	O
habour	O	O

Hai	O	PERSON
Phong	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Harlingen	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Hoi	O	O
An	O	O
habour	O	O

ICD	O	O
Phuoc	O	O
Long	O	O
2	O	O
habour	O	O

Karachi	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Khanh	O	O
Hoi	O	O
habour	O	O

Kismayu	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Klang	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

La	O	O
Gi	O	O
habour	O	O

Lido	O	O
habour	O	O

Long	O	O
Binh	O	O
habour	O	O

Lotus	O	O
habour	O	O

Maizuruhabour	O	O

Makinohara	O	O
habour	O	O

Markah	O	O
habour	O	O

The	O	O
south	O	O
Busan	O	O
habour	O	O

My	O	O
Thoi	O	O
habour	O	O

Noi	O	PERSON
Bai	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Habour	O	O

My	O	O
Thuy	O	O
water	O	O
port	O	O

Phnom	O	O
Penh	O	O
habour	O	O

Phu	O	O
My	O	O
habour	O	O

Phu	O	O
Quy	O	O
habour	O	O

Phuoc	O	O
Long	O	O
1	O	O
habour	O	O

Posco	O	O
habour	O	O

Cai	O	O
Mep	O	O
international	O	O
habour	O	O

Quy	O	O
Nhon	O	O
habour	O	O

Sa	O	O
Ky	O	O
habour	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon	O	O
-	O	O
Hiep	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

San	O	LOCATION
Martin	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Sihanoukville	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Singapore	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Sokcho	O	O
habour	O	O

Ta	O	O
Hoc	O	O
habour	O	O

Table	O	O
Bay	O	O
habour	O	O

Tan	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Thailand	O	LOCATION
habour	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Ha	O	O
habour	O	O

Thi	O	PERSON
Vai	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Tien	O	PERSON
Sa	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
habour	O	O

Tru	O	O
Cau	O	O
habour	O	O

Vung	O	PERSON
Ang	O	PERSON
habour	O	O

Vung	O	O
Ro	O	O
habour	O	O

Zanjiba	O	O
habour	O	O

Cam	O	O
Ranh	O	O
airport	O	O

Noi	O	PERSON
Bai	O	PERSON
airport	O	O

Noi	O	PERSON
Bai	O	PERSON
international	O	O
airport	O	O

Vinh	O	O
airport	O	O

Go	O	O
Ma	O	O
field	O	O

Al-Jol	O	O
centrel	O	O
highland	O	O

Golan	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

La	O	O
Paz	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Lang	O	PERSON
Bian	O	PERSON
central	O	O
highland	O	O

M'Nong	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Moc	O	O
Chau	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Pleiku	O	LOCATION
central	O	O
higland	O	O

Scotland	O	LOCATION
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Tagaytay	O	O
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Tibet	O	LOCATION
central	O	O
higland	O	O

Tibet-Thanh	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
central	O	O
higland	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Tang	O	PERSON
central	O	O
highland	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
ferry-bridge	O	O

Bridge	O	O
of	O	O
No	O	O
14	O	O

Bridge	O	O
of	O	O
30-4	O	O

Bridge	O	O
of	O	O
38	O	O

An	O	O
Ha	O	O
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Hoa	O	O
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Hoi	O	O
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Huu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Long	O	O
-	O	O
An	O	O
Linh	O	O
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Phu	O	O
Dong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Chiem	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Hong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Lang	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Lat	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Tang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ba	O	O
Tong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Bach	O	O
bridge	O	O

Bach	O	O
Yen	O	O
bridge	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Chay	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Dau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Nay	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Thuy	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Tre	O	PERSON
1	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Tre	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
Tay	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Tay	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Thuy	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Trieu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Trieu	O	PERSON
1	O	O
bridge	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Trieu	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Blackfriars	O	O
bridge	O	O

Blue	O	O
bridge	O	O

Bong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Buu	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

C247	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ca	O	O
Toi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ca	O	O
Tre	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cai	O	O
Rang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cai	O	O
Son	O	O
bridge	O	O

Calmette	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cam	O	PERSON
Nam	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Can	O	O
Giuoc	O	O
bridge	O	O

Can	O	O
Tho	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cao	O	O
Lanh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cha	O	O
La	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cha	O	O
Va	O	O
bridge	O	O

Charles	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Chau	O	PERSON
Kim	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Chau	O	PERSON
Tien	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Chiec	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cho	O	PERSON
Cau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Chom	O	PERSON
Lom	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

U-shape	O	O
bridge	O	O

Y-shape	O	O
bridge	O	O

Chuong	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Co	O	O
Co	O	O
bridge	O	O

Co	O	O
May	O	O
bridge	O	O

Coc	O	O
Leu	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cong	O	O
Ly	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cua	O	PERSON
Dai	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Da	O	O
Rang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Dai	O	O
Yen	O	O
bridge	O	O

Dak	O	PERSON
Bla	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Dat	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Dau	O	PERSON
Sau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Day	O	O
Oc	O	O
bridge	O	O

Den	O	O
bridge	O	O

Dien	O	O
bridge	O	O

Dien	O	PERSON
Bien	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Dinh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Do	O	O
bridge	O	O

Don	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Nai	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Duc	O	PERSON
Nho	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Duoi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Duy	O	PERSON
Tan	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Gia	O	PERSON
Lam	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Gia	O	PERSON
Rai	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Gian	O	PERSON
Khau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Gianh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Gie	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Giong	O	O
Ong	O	O
To	O	O
bridge	O	O

Giong	O	O
Ong	O	O
To	O	O
1	O	O
bridge	O	O

Giong	O	O
Ong	O	O
To	O	O
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Go	O	O
Dua	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Duc	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Rong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Hau	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hien	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hiep	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Xuan	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Dieu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Tham	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Huong	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Huu	O	PERSON
Nghi	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Mea	O	PERSON
Sai	O	PERSON
friendship	O	O
bridge	O	O

Karl	O	O
bridge	O	O

Kenh	O	PERSON
Hau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Kenh	O	PERSON
Moi	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Kenh	O	O
Te	O	O
bridge	O	O

Kenh	O	PERSON
Xang	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Khanh	O	O
Hoi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Khe	O	O
Sung	O	O
bridge	O	O

Kieu	O	O
bridge	O	O

Kinh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Kinh	O	PERSON
Nhanh,	O	O
Song	O	O
Kien	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ky	O	O
Ha	O	O
1	O	O
and	O	O
Ky	O	O
Ha	O	O
4	O	O
bridge	O	O

La	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Hong	O	PERSON
Phong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Lien	O	PERSON
Danh	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Lo	O	O
Gom	O	O
bridge	O	O

Lo	O	O
Pang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Long	O	O
Bien	O	O
bridge	O	O

Long	O	ORGANIZATION
Bien	O	ORGANIZATION
-	O	O
Gia	O	PERSON
Lam	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Long	O	O
Sa	O	O
bridge	O	O

Luzhkow	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ly	O	O
Son	O	O
bridge	O	O

Mat	O	O
bridge	O	O

May	O	O
Ruou	O	O
bridge	O	O

An	O	O
Long	O	O
-	O	O
An	O	O
Linh	O	O
new	O	O
bridge	O	O

Mong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Mong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Monivong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Muong	O	PERSON
Chuoi	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

My	O	O
Thuan	O	O
bridge	O	O

Nang	O	PERSON
Ren	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nga	O	O
Thu	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Toan	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Tri	O	PERSON
Phuong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Trung	O	PERSON
Truc	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Cu	O	O
bridge	O	O

Nhat	O	O
Tan	O	O
bridge	O	O

Nhi	O	PERSON
Thien	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nhi	O	PERSON
Thien	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
1	O	O
bridge	O	O

Nhu	O	PERSON
Gia	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ninh	O	PERSON
Kieu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Nong	O	O
Son	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	O
Bo	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	O
Bo	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	O
Buong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	PERSON
Dau	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	PERSON
Doi	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	O
Ho	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ong	O	O
Lanh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Penang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
Cuong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
Long	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
My	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
Qui	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
Vinh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phu	O	O
Xuan	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phung	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Phung	O	O
Hung	O	O
bridge	O	O

Phuoc	O	PERSON
Kieng	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Quang	O	O
Hue	O	O
bridge	O	O

Quay	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rac	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Cay	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Chiec	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Dia	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Lat	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Mieu	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Ngong	O	O
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
No	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Ong	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Soi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Tra	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rach	O	O
Vam	O	O
bridge	O	O

Ranh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Rau	O	O
Ram	O	O
bridge	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon	O	O
bridge	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon,	O	O
Rach	O	O
Chiec,	O	O
Nguyen	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Canh	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon	O	O
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Sang	O	O
Trang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Sat	O	O
bridge	O	O

Sim	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

No	O	O
9	O	O
bridge	O	O

Han	O	O
river	O	O
bridge	O	O

Lieng	O	O
river	O	O
bridge	O	O

Suoi	O	O
Cat	O	O
bridge	O	O

Suoi	O	PERSON
Chinh	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Suoi	O	PERSON
Linh	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Suoi	O	PERSON
Vang	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Y	O	O
shape	O	O
bridge	O	O

Cong	O	O
Ly	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Khanh	O	PERSON
Du	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
An	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
My	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
Tao	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thuan	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thuan	O	O
1	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thuan	O	O
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thach	O	O
Han	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thai	O	O
Son	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thang	O	O
Long	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Hoi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Tri	O	O
bridge	O	O

The	O	O
Huc	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Thi	O	O
Nghe	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thot	O	O
Not	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thu	O	O
Thiem	O	O
bridge	O	O

Thuan	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Tower	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tra	O	O
Noc	O	O
bridge	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Thi	O	PERSON
Ly	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Trang	O	O
bridge	O	O

Trang	O	PERSON
Tien	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Charles	O	PERSON
celebrated	O	O
bridge	O	O

Trung	O	O
Ha	O	O
bridge	O	O

Truong	O	PERSON
Tien	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Tu	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Tu	O	O
Muoi	O	O
bridge	O	O

Vam	O	O
Sat	O	O
bridge	O	O

Van	O	O
Thanh	O	O
bridge	O	O

Van	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Vinh	O	PERSON
Tuy	O	PERSON
bridge	O	O

Xo	O	ORGANIZATION
Viet	O	ORGANIZATION
Nghe	O	ORGANIZATION
Tinh	O	ORGANIZATION
bridge	O	O

Ly	O	O
Son	O	O
quay	O	O

Sydney	O	LOCATION
quay	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Trieu	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O

Han	O	O
river	O	O
swing	O	O
bridge	O	O

Carrick-a-Rede	O	O
chain	O	O
bridge	O	O

Chau	O	PERSON
Hoi	O	PERSON
chain	O	O
bridge	O	O

Olimpico	O	O
rectify	O	O

An	O	O
Suong	O	O
flyover	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

Go	O	O
Dua	O	O
flyover	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Cam	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

Linh	O	PERSON
Xuan	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

Tan	O	PERSON
Thoi	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Canh	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Trung	O	PERSON
flyover	O	O

91B	O	O
highway	O	O
flyover	O	O

Song	O	O
Than	O	O
flyover	O	O

Thu	O	O
Duc	O	O
flyover	O	O

Thuy	O	O
duong	O	O
flyover	O	O

Van	O	O
Thanh	O	O
market	O	O
nad	O	O
flyover	O	O

Milestones	O	O
11	O	O

Milestones	O	O
12	O	O

Milestones	O	O
2	O	O

Cau	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
petro	O	O
station	O	O

Long	O	O
Hoa	O	O
petro	O	O
station	O	O

Tran	O	O
Phu	O	O
No1	O	O
petro	O	O
station	O	O

Tan	O	O
Hiep	O	O
petro	O	O
station	O	O

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Cyprus	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Czech	O	O

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Czech	O	O

Pacific	O	LOCATION
Asia	O	LOCATION

Oceania	O	LOCATION

America	O	LOCATION

Latin	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION

Latin	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION

Antartica	O	LOCATION

Australia	O	LOCATION

Niger	O	LOCATION
delta	O	O

Niger	O	LOCATION
river	O	O
delta	O	O

Republic	O	O
Democratic	O	O
of	O	O
Congos	O	O

Republic	O	O
Democratic	O	O
of	O	O
German	O	O

Republic	O	O
Democratic	O	O
of	O	O
Laos	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
Democratic	O	O
of	O	O
Korea	O	LOCATION

D	O	O
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Sac	O	O
forest	O	O
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Sac	O	PERSON
forest	O	O
and	O	O
Dong	O	PERSON
Thap	O	PERSON
Muoi	O	PERSON
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Sakonr	O	O
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Tan	O	O
Trao	O	O
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Viet	O	O
Bac	O	O
war	O	O
zone	O	O

Vietnam	O	LOCATION
battlefield	O	O

Federal	O	O
republic's	O	O
Germany	O	LOCATION

3-2	O	O
market	O	O

An	O	O
Binh	O	O
market	O	O

An	O	O
Dong	O	O
market	O	O

An	O	O
Lo	O	O
market	O	O

An	O	O
Nhon	O	O
market	O	O

Ba	O	O
Cang	O	O
market	O	O

Ba	O	O
Chieu	O	O
market	O	O

Ba	O	O
Don	O	O
market	O	O

Ba	O	O
Vat	O	O
market	O	O

Ban	O	O
Co	O	O
market	O	O

Bang	O	O
market	O	O

Hoc	O	O
Mon	O	O
market	O	O
of	O	O
corn	O	O

Bat	O	O
Trang	O	O
market	O	O

Bau	O	O
Cat	O	O
market	O	O

Ben	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
market	O	O

An	O	O
Dong	O	O
market	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Tay	O	PERSON
market	O	O

4	O	O
tigers	O	O
market	O	O

Buoi	O	O
market	O	O

Tinh	O	O
Hoa	O	O
market	O	O
of	O	O
fish	O	O

Cai	O	O
Be	O	O
market	O	O

Cai	O	O
Von	O	O
market	O	O

Cau	O	O
Muoi	O	O
market	O	O

Cau	O	O
Ong	O	O
Lanh	O	O
market	O	O

Chau	O	O
Long	O	O
market	O	O

Cherkizov	O	O
market	O	O

Cherkizovsky	O	O
market	O	O

Chim	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thanh	O	O
boder	O	O
gate	O	O
market	O	O

Cua	O	O
Nam	O	O
market	O	O

Da	O	O
Lat	O	O
market	O	O

Bat	O	O
Trang	O	O
market	O	O

Dat	O	PERSON
Mui	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Dau	O	PERSON
Bo	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Dien	O	PERSON
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Den	O	O
Lu	O	O
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Den	O	O
Lu,	O	O
Xuan	O	O
Dinh	O	O
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Wholesale	O	O
market	O	O
of	O	O
Otachi	O	O
farm	O	O
product	O	O

Wholesale	O	O
market	O	O
of	O	O
Xuan	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
agricultural	O	O
food	O	O
product	O	O

Tam	O	O
Binh	O	O
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Thu	O	O
Duc	O	O
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Xuan	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
wholesale	O	O
market	O	O

Dem	O	O
market	O	O

Do	O	O
market	O	O

Dong	O	O
Ba	O	O
market	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Dai	O	PERSON
Mon	O	O
market	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Dang	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Kinh	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Tam	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Xuan	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Dongdae-Mon	O	O
market	O	O

Duong	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Ea	O	O
Kao	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Ea	O	O
K'tua	O	O
market	O	O

Ea	O	O
Toh'	O	O
market	O	O

Gioi	O	O
market	O	O

Go	O	O
market	O	O

Go	O	O
Vap	O	O
market	O	O

Bat	O	O
Trang	O	O
pottery	O	O
market	O	O

Ha	O	O
Dong	O	O
market	O	O

Ha	O	O
Vi	O	O
market	O	O

Han	O	O
market	O	O

Hang	O	O
Da	O	O
market	O	O

Hang	O	O
Luoc	O	O
market	O	O

Hang	O	O
Phan	O	O
market	O	O

Ho	O	O
Thi	O	O
Ky	O	O
flower	O	O
market	O	O

Quang	O	O
Ba	O	O
flower	O	O
market	O	O

Quang	O	O
Ba	O	O
fresh	O	O
flower	O	O
market	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Hoa	O	PERSON
Tham	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Hoc	O	O
Mon	O	O
market	O	O

Hoi	O	O
Yen	O	O
market	O	O

Hom	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Huu	O	PERSON
Nghi	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Kacha	O	O
Pakha	O	O
market	O	O

Kham	O	PERSON
Thien	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Kim	O	PERSON
Bien	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Lagos	O	LOCATION
market	O	O

Lai	O	PERSON
Thieu	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Linh	O	PERSON
Nam	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Lon	O	O
market	O	O

Long	O	O
Dinh	O	O
market	O	O

Long	O	O
Ho	O	O
market	O	O

Long	O	O
Thanh	O	O
market	O	O

Long	O	O
Xuyen	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Nhan	O	O
drug	O	O
market	O	O

Moscow	O	LOCATION
market	O	O

Mo	O	O
market	O	O

Moi	O	O
market	O	O

Moon	O	O
market	O	O

Spring	O	O
market	O	O

Nan	O	O
Lerng	O	O
market	O	O

Quach	O	O
Lieu	O	O
T-junction	O	O
market	O	O

Nghe	O	O
market	O	O

Ngo	O	O
Si	O	O
Lien	O	O
market	O	O

Bat	O	O
Trang	O	O
person	O	O
market	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Troi	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Nha	O	O
Be	O	O
market	O	O

Nhat	O	PERSON
Tao	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Market	O	O
of	O	O
Da	O	O
Lat	O	O
agricutural	O	O
product	O	O

Market	O	O
of	O	O
Thu	O	O
Duc	O	O
agricutural	O	O
product	O	O

O	O	O
Russei	O	O
market	O	O

Pham	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Hai	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Phan	O	PERSON
Chu	O	PERSON
Trinh	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Phan	O	PERSON
Rang	O	O
market	O	O

Phu	O	O
Lam	O	O
market	O	O

Phu	O	O
Thu	O	O
market	O	O

Phung	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Quang	O	PERSON
Chau	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Quincy	O	O
market	O	O

Rach	O	O
Gia	O	O
market	O	O

Go	O	O
Quan	O	O
vegetable	O	O
market	O	O

San	O	O
Van	O	O
Dong	O	O
market	O	O

Sapa	O	O
market	O	O

Sat	O	O
market	O	O

So	O	O
Rac	O	O
market	O	O

Soc	O	O
Trang	O	O
market	O	O

Suoi	O	PERSON
Meo	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Tam	O	O
Binh	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Binh	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Dinh	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Huong	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Phu	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Quy	O	O
market	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thanh	O	O
market	O	O

Thach	O	O
Tru	O	O
market	O	O

Thai	O	O
Binh	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Cong	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Son	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Vinh	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Xuan	O	O
market	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Xuan	O	PERSON
Bac	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Hat	O	O
Lot	O	O
town	O	O
market	O	O

Khau	O	PERSON
Vai	O	PERSON
love	O	O
fair	O	O

Moc	O	O
Chau	O	O
love	O	O
fair	O	O

Sapa	O	O
love	O	O
fair	O	O

Tong	O	O
market	O	O

Tran	O	O
Binh	O	O
market	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Chau	O	O
Doc	O	O
cattle	O	O
market	O	O

Truong	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
market	O	O

Truong	O	O
Mit	O	O
market	O	O

Vinh	O	O
Hoi	O	O
Dong	O	O
market	O	O

Vinh	O	O
Long	O	O
market	O	O

Vinh	O	O
Tre	O	O
market	O	O

Vom	O	O
market	O	O

Xanh	O	O
market	O	O

Xuan	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
II	O	O
market	O	O

Cai	O	O
Be	O	O
Floating	O	O
market	O	O

Cai	O	O
Rang	O	O
Floating	O	O
market	O	O

Phung	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
Floating	O	O
market	O	O

Nilai	O	O
village	O	O
fair	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Bao	O	O
An	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Bao	O	O
Son	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Bo	O	PERSON
De	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	PERSON

But	O	O
Thap	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Cam	O	O
Phong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Canh	O	O
Thai	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Cau	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Yen	O	O
Lac	O	O
old	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
Bi	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Dau	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Dau	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Doi	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Ba	O	O
Da	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Duc	O	O
Son	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Giai	O	PERSON
Oan	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Gwanyum-Sa	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Hai	O	PERSON
Tang	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Hang	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Ho	O	O
Phap	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Hien	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Hoa	O	O
Long	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Phap	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Huong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Huong	O	O
Son	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Kandal	O	LOCATION
pagoda	O	O

Khai	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Khleang	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Ky	O	O
Quang	O	O
pagoda	O	O

La	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Long	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Me	O	O
Xi	O	O
Muong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Mot	O	O
Cot	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Mot	O	O
Mai	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Naga	O	PERSON
Vann	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Ngoc	O	O
Son	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Ong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Ong	O	O
Nui	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Phap	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Phap	O	PERSON
Vo	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Phat	O	O
Lon	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Phat	O	O
Quang	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Pho	O	O
Minh	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Pho	O	O
Quang	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Phuc	O	PERSON
Hung	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Phuc	O	PERSON
Lam	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Quan	O	O
Am	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Quan	O	O
Su	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Quan	O	PERSON
Thuong	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Tay	O	PERSON
Phuong	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Thai	O	O
Cam	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Hoa	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Thuy	O	O
pagoda	O	O

That	O	O
Luang	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thay	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thay	O	O
Tho	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thien	O	O
Mu	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thien	O	O
Tru	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Thuong	O	O
Lam	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Tran	O	O
Quoc	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Tu	O	O
Duc	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Tuong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Tuong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Unalong	O	O
pagoda	O	O

Wat	O	PERSON
Phai	O	PERSON
Khiew	O	PERSON
pagoda	O	O

Xa	O	O
Loi	O	O
pagoda	O	O

27	O	O
Le	O	O
Tan	O	O
Ke	O	O
apartment	O	O

368	O	O
Phan	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Tri	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

40	O	O
Go	O	O
Vap	O	O
apartment	O	O

47/57	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
Thai	O	O
Binh	O	O
apartment	O	O

727	O	O
apartment	O	O

86	O	O
Tran	O	O
Huy	O	O
Lieu	O	O
apartment	O	O

Bau	O	O
Cat	O	O
2	O	O
apartment	O	O

Bui	O	PERSON
Vien	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Cao	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Chu	O	O
Van	O	O
An	O	O
apartment	O	O

Conic	O	O
apartment	O	O

Dinh	O	PERSON
Khiem	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Eden	O	O
apartment	O	O

Gia	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Hai	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
1	O	O
apartment	O	O

Hiep	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
Chanh	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Hung	O	O
Vuong	O	O
apartment	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Thi	O	PERSON
Rieng	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Ly	O	PERSON
Thuong	O	PERSON
Kiet	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Man	O	O
Thien	O	O
apartment	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Pham	O	PERSON
Viet	O	PERSON
Chanh	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Quoc	O	O
Thanh	O	O
apartment	O	O

Sacomreal	O	O
apartment	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Da	O	O
apartment	O	O

Thanh	O	O
My	O	O
Loi	O	O
apartment	O	O

Thuan	O	O
Phuoc,	O	O
Thanh	O	O
Loc	O	O
Dan	O	O
apartment	O	O

Trump	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Trung	O	O
Van	O	O
apartment	O	O

Truong	O	O
An	O	O
apartment	O	O

Xom	O	O
Cai	O	O
apartment	O	O

Xuan	O	PERSON
Mai	O	PERSON
apartment	O	O

Cities	O	O
of	O	O
Hoa	O	PERSON
Lac-Xuan	O	PERSON
Mai-Mieu	O	PERSON
Mon	O	PERSON

Cusco	O	LOCATION
acient	O	O
capital	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Lu	O	PERSON
acient	O	O
capital	O	O

Hue	O	O
acient	O	O
capital	O	O

Kyoto	O	LOCATION
acient	O	O
capital	O	O

Indochina	O	LOCATION

Au	O	O
hillock	O	O

Cai	O	PERSON
Ga	O	O
hillock	O	O

Cai	O	O
Khe	O	O
hillock	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
hillock	O	O

Dam	O	O
hillock	O	O

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Austria	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Bashkortostan	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Chad	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Cuba	O	LOCATION

Dominican	O	LOCATION
Republic	O	LOCATION

Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Hungary	O	LOCATION

Federal	O	O
Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Germany	O	LOCATION

French	O	LOCATION
Republic	O	LOCATION

Czech	O	LOCATION
Republic	O	LOCATION

Czech	O	LOCATION
Republic	O	LOCATION

Central	O	O
African	O	O
Republic	O	O

Autonomous	O	O
Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Chechnya	O	LOCATION

Autonomous	O	O
Republic	O	O
of	O	O
Ingushetia	O	LOCATION

Principality	O	O
of	O	O
Asturias	O	LOCATION

Principality	O	O
of	O	O
Liechstenstein	O	PERSON

9th	O	O
construction	O	O
site	O	O

Lam	O	O
Son	O	O
construction	O	O
site	O	O

23-9	O	O
park	O	O

29.3	O	O
park	O	O

29-3	O	O
park	O	O

30/4	O	O
park	O	O

30-4	O	O
park	O	O

An	O	O
Duong	O	PERSON
Vuong	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Ba	O	O
Thang	O	O
Hai	O	O
park	O	O

Bai	O	PERSON
Truoc	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Bercy	O	LOCATION
park	O	O

Big	O	O
Apple's	O	O
Bryant	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Dam	O	O
Sen	O	O
park	O	O

Disney	O	O
Land	O	O
park	O	O

Gia	O	PERSON
Dinh	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Hluhluwe	O	O
Umfolozi	O	O
park	O	O

Ho	O	PERSON
Khanh	O	PERSON
Hoi	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Ho	O	PERSON
Thuy	O	PERSON
Tien	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Hoang	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Thu	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Hyde	O	O
Park	O	O
park	O	O

Juvet	O	PERSON
park	O	O

La	O	PERSON
Fontaine	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Lac	O	O
Hong	O	O
park	O	O

Lam	O	O
Son	O	O
park	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Hong	O	PERSON
Phong	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Thi	O	PERSON
Rieng	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Tam	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Lumpini	O	O
park	O	O

Luu	O	PERSON
Huu	O	PERSON
Phuoc	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Ly	O	O
Thai	O	O
To	O	O
park	O	O

Ly	O	PERSON
Tu	O	PERSON
Trong	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Nghia	O	O
Do	O	O
park	O	O

Nghia	O	PERSON
Tan	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Water	O	O
park	O	O

Ha	O	O
Noi	O	O
waterpark	O	O

Ho	O	O
Tay	O	O
waterpark	O	O

Rong	O	PERSON
Bien	O	PERSON
waterpark	O	O

Phu	O	O
Lam	O	O
park	O	O

Quach	O	PERSON
Thi	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON
park	O	O

American	O	O
Samoa	O	LOCATION
island	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Grand	O	O
Canyon	O	O
Yellowstone	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Khao	O	PERSON
Phra	O	PERSON
Wihan	O	PERSON
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Komodo	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Pilanesburg	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Pilannesburg	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Preah	O	PERSON
Vihear	O	PERSON
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Addo	O	PERSON
elephent	O	O
national	O	O
gardern	O	O

Rizal	O	O
Park	O	O
park	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
Suoi	O	O
Tien	O	O
park	O	O

Tao	O	PERSON
Dan	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Nien	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Thanh	O	PERSON
Quang	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Thien	O	O
An	O	O
park	O	O

Thong	O	O
Nhat	O	O
park	O	O

Thu	O	O
Le	O	O
park	O	O

Thuong	O	O
Bac	O	O
park	O	O

Tokyo	O	LOCATION
park	O	O

Tu	O	PERSON
Tuong	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Dam	O	O
Sen	O	O
culture	O	O
park	O	O

Western	O	O
region	O	O
culture	O	O
park	O	O

Van	O	PERSON
Lang	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Vo	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Ky	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Walt	O	PERSON
Disney	O	PERSON
park	O	O

Yen	O	O
Phi	O	O
park	O	O

Hien	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
flagpole	O	O

Lung	O	O
Cu	O	O
flagpole	O	O

Bac	O	O
Phuoc	O	O
island	O	O

Cau	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Cham	O	O
island	O	O

Dai	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Du	O	O
lich	O	O
Thoi	O	O
Son	O	O
island	O	O

Dung	O	O
island	O	O

Ho	O	O
island	O	O

Loi	O	O
Quan	O	O
island	O	O

Ong	O	O
Xa	O	O
island	O	O

Tan	O	O
Loc	O	O
island	O	O

Tan	O	O
Phong	O	O
island	O	O

Thoi	O	O
Son	O	O
island	O	O

304	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

30-4	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Thoi	O	PERSON
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Chu	O	O
Van	O	O
An	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Duong	O	PERSON
Sat	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Lu	O	PERSON
Gia	O	PERSON
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Ly	O	PERSON
Thuong	O	PERSON
Kiet	O	PERSON
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Banking	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Banking	O	O
of	O	O
ward	O	O
1	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Trung	O	PERSON
Truc	O	PERSON
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Phan	O	PERSON
Dang	O	PERSON
Luu	O	PERSON
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Phu	O	O
Lam	O	O
A	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Da	O	O
housing	O	O
easte	O	O

Eo	O	O
seaport	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Duan	O	PERSON
seaport	O	O

Sa	O	O
Can	O	O
seaport	O	O

Cai	O	O
Cam	O	O
seaport	O	O

Dinh	O	O
An	O	O
seaport	O	O

Gach	O	PERSON
Goc	O	PERSON
seaport	O	O

Ganh	O	O
Hao	O	O
seaport	O	O

Ham	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
seaport	O	O

My	O	O
A	O	O
seaport	O	O

Sa	O	O
Can	O	O
seaport	O	O

Sa	O	PERSON
Huynh	O	PERSON
seaport	O	O

Sa	O	O
Ky	O	O
seaport	O	O

Thien	O	O
Cam	O	O
seaport	O	O

Thuan	O	O
An	O	O
seaport	O	O

An	O	O
Giang	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Giang	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Sai	O	O
Gon	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Cau	O	O
Treo	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Chang	O	PERSON
Riec	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Dang	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Duong	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Ha	O	O
Tien	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Tan	O	O
Son	O	O
Nhat	O	O
aviation	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Huu	O	PERSON
Nghi	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Lao	O	PERSON
Bao	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Lao	O	O
Cai	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Lao	O	O
Cai	O	O
�	O	O
Ha	O	O
Khau	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Moc	O	O
Bai	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Mong	O	PERSON
Cai	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Mukdahan	O	LOCATION
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Nam	O	PERSON
Giang	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Dak	O	O
Ta	O	O
Ooc	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Bo	O	O
Y	O	O
international	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Cau	O	O
Treo	O	O
international	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Lao	O	O
Bao	O	O
international	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Nam	O	O
Can	O	O
international	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Tan	O	O
Son	O	O
Nhat	O	O
airport	O	O
international	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Tan	O	O
Son	O	O
Nhat	O	O
airport	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Singapore	O	LOCATION
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Tan	O	O
Thanh	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Thanh	O	O
Thuy	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Tinh	O	O
Bien	O	O
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Vinh	O	PERSON
Xuong	O	PERSON
border	O	O
gate	O	O

Bac	O	O
Luan	O	O
estuary	O	O

Cai	O	O
Lon	O	O
estuary	O	O

Duong	O	PERSON
Dong	O	PERSON
estuary	O	O

Hat	O	O
estuary	O	O

Nhat	O	O
Le	O	O
estuary	O	O

Vam	O	O
Co	O	O
estuary	O	O

North	O	O
pole	O	O

Group	O	O
of	O	O
No2	O	O

Group	O	O
of	O	O
No4	O	O

Group	O	O
of	O	O
No9	O	O

Buckingham	O	O
palace	O	O

Cach	O	O
mang	O	O
palace	O	O

Caserta	O	PERSON
palace	O	O

Gyeongbok	O	O
ancient	O	O
palace	O	O

Dusit	O	PERSON
palace	O	O

Gyeongbok	O	O
palace	O	O

Harald	O	PERSON
palace	O	O

Kyong	O	PERSON
Bok	O	PERSON
palace	O	O

Kyongbuk	O	LOCATION
palace	O	O

Summer	O	O
palace	O	O

Schoenbrunn	O	LOCATION
palace	O	O

St.James	O	O
palace	O	O

Michigan	O	LOCATION
university	O	O

3-2	O	O
highway	O	O

5	O	O
highway	O	O

Binh	O	PERSON
Duong	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Broadway	O	O
highway	O	O

Highway	O	O
of	O	O
Ho	O	LOCATION
Chi	O	LOCATION
Minh	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION
-	O	O
Trung	O	PERSON
Luong	O	PERSON
-	O	O
Can	O	O
Tho	O	O

Champs	O	O
Elysees	O	O
highway	O	O

Walk	O	O
of	O	O
fame	O	O

Walk	O	O
of	O	O
fame	O	O

Walk	O	O
of	O	O
fame	O	O

Doc	O	O
Lap	O	O
highway	O	O

East-west	O	O
highway	O	O

East-west	O	O
highway	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
East-west	O	O
highway	O	O

Foch	O	O
highway	O	O

Hanh	O	PERSON
Phuc	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Hoa	O	PERSON
Binh	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

III	O	O
highway	O	O

La	O	O
Reforma	O	O
highway	O	O

Lane	O	PERSON
Xang	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Nguyen	O	O
Hue	O	O
highway	O	O

Nguyen	O	O
Tat	O	O
Thanh	O	O
highway	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Linh	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Pennsylvania	O	LOCATION
highway	O	O

Ratchadamnoen	O	O
Nok	O	O
highway	O	O

Rivoli	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Number	O	O
5	O	O
highway	O	O

Thong	O	O
Nhat	O	O
highway	O	O

Tran	O	PERSON
Phu	O	PERSON
highway	O	O

Amatani	O	PERSON
island	O	O

American	O	O
Samoa	O	LOCATION
island	O	O

Bach	O	PERSON
Long	O	PERSON
Vi	O	PERSON
island	O	O

Baffin	O	LOCATION
island	O	O
