1860	O	O
Munich	O	LOCATION

2000	O	O
Games	O	O

3M	O	O

Aalst	O	O

Aarau	O	O

Aaxis	O	ORGANIZATION

Aaxis	O	ORGANIZATION
Limited	O	ORGANIZATION

ABC	O	ORGANIZATION

ABC	O	O
News	O	O

Aberdeen	O	LOCATION

ABERDEEN	O	ORGANIZATION

ABN	O	ORGANIZATION
AMRO	O	ORGANIZATION

ABN-AMRO	O	ORGANIZATION
Hoare	O	ORGANIZATION
Govett	O	ORGANIZATION

Academic	O	O
Staff	O	O
Union	O	O
of	O	O
Universities	O	O

ACC	O	O

ACES	O	O

AC	O	ORGANIZATION
Milan	O	ORGANIZATION

AC	O	ORGANIZATION
Sparta	O	ORGANIZATION
Praha	O	ORGANIZATION

Action	O	O
Against	O	O
Hunger	O	O

AD	O	O

Add	O	O
Hapoel	O	O
Ironi	O	O

AD-DIYAR	O	O

AD	O	O
DUSTOUR	O	O

Adelaide	O	LOCATION

Admira	O	PERSON
/	O	O
Wacker	O	LOCATION

AdOn	O	O

AdOn	O	O
GmbH	O	O

ADV	O	O

Advanced	O	O
Medical	O	O

Advanced	O	ORGANIZATION
Medical	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Aegon	O	ORGANIZATION

AEI	O	O

AEI	O	O
Iberfreight	O	O

AEK	O	O

AEK	O	ORGANIZATION
Larnaca	O	LOCATION

Aerostan	O	LOCATION

AFL	O	ORGANIZATION

African	O	O
National	O	O
Congress	O	O

A.G.	O	ORGANIZATION
Edwards	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Sons,	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

AGF-IART	O	O

Agir	O	ORGANIZATION
Ensemble	O	ORGANIZATION
pour	O	O
les	O	O
Droits	O	O
de	O	O
l'Homme	O	O

Agricultural	O	O
Statistics	O	O
Service	O	O

Agriculture	O	O
Ministry	O	O

AGROTONZ	O	O
TLUMACOV	O	O

AHOLD	O	ORGANIZATION

Air	O	ORGANIZATION
Cargo	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Air	O	O
Corps	O	O

Airdrieonians	O	O

Air	O	O
Express	O	O
International	O	O

Air	O	O
Force	O	O

Airport	O	O
Facilities	O	O

Airport	O	ORGANIZATION
Facilities	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Ajaccio	O	LOCATION

Ajax	O	ORGANIZATION

AJAX	O	ORGANIZATION

Ajax	O	ORGANIZATION
Amsterdam	O	ORGANIZATION

Aki	O	PERSON

Akron	O	LOCATION

al-Akhbar	O	O

Alania	O	PERSON
Vladikavkaz	O	PERSON

Alaniya	O	PERSON
Vladikavkaz	O	PERSON

AL-ANWAR	O	O

Alarm	O	O
UK	O	O

Alaska	O	ORGANIZATION
Milk	O	ORGANIZATION

AL	O	O
ASWAQ	O	O

Alba	O	PERSON

Albion	O	LOCATION

Alcan	O	O

Alcatel	O	ORGANIZATION
Alsthom	O	ORGANIZATION

Aldi	O	ORGANIZATION

Algeria	O	LOCATION
TV	O	O

al-Ingaz	O	ORGANIZATION
al-Watani	O	ORGANIZATION

All	O	O
Blacks	O	O

Allensbach	O	PERSON

All	O	O
Fishermen	O	O
's	O	O
Association	O	O

Alliance-Menatep	O	O

Alloa	O	LOCATION

Alpha	O	ORGANIZATION
Technologies	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Alpha	O	O
Techs	O	O

AL	O	O
RAI	O	O

al-Tadamun	O	O

Alucasa	O	PERSON

Amazon	O	ORGANIZATION
Affairs	O	ORGANIZATION
Department	O	ORGANIZATION

America	O	LOCATION

American	O	O

American	O	ORGANIZATION
Airlines	O	ORGANIZATION

American	O	O
Names	O	O
Association	O	O

American	O	O
Stock	O	O
Exchange	O	O

American	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

America	O	O
Online	O	O

America	O	ORGANIZATION
Online	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Americast	O	LOCATION

Ameritech	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

Amica	O	ORGANIZATION
Wronki	O	ORGANIZATION

Amoco	O	ORGANIZATION

Amoco	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

AMR	O	O

AMR	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Amsterdam	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Amtrak	O	ORGANIZATION

AMTRAK	O	O

Anatolian	O	O

ANC	O	ORGANIZATION

Anderlecht	O	O

Angels	O	O

ANGELS	O	O

AN-NAHAR	O	O

ANP	O	O

ANSA	O	ORGANIZATION

Antwerp	O	LOCATION

Anyang	O	LOCATION

AOL	O	ORGANIZATION

AOL	O	O
Europe	O	LOCATION

AOL	O	O
Germany	O	LOCATION

APA	O	O

Apex	O	O
Tannery	O	O

AP	O	O
Moller	O	PERSON

Apple	O	O

Apple	O	ORGANIZATION
Computer	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Arbroath	O	O

ARC	O	O

Arch	O	O

Archaeological	O	ORGANIZATION
Society	O	ORGANIZATION

Archives	O	O

Arch	O	ORGANIZATION
Petroleum	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Arequipa	O	LOCATION

Arequipa	O	ORGANIZATION
Resources	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Arkansas	O	ORGANIZATION
State	O	ORGANIZATION
Police	O	ORGANIZATION

Arminia	O	O
Bielefeld	O	O

Army	O	O

Aronkasei	O	O

Aronkasei	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Arrows	O	O

Arsenal	O	O

Arthur	O	PERSON
Yates	O	PERSON

Arthur	O	PERSON
Yates	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Co	O	O

Artmedia	O	ORGANIZATION
Petrzalka	O	ORGANIZATION

ASARCO	O	ORGANIZATION

A.S.	O	O
Bacau	O	O

ASEC	O	ORGANIZATION

Asian	O	O
Star	O	O
TV	O	O

AS-SAFIR	O	O

Assembly	O	O

Association	O	O
of	O	O
Lloyd	O	ORGANIZATION
's	O	ORGANIZATION

Aston	O	LOCATION
Villa	O	LOCATION

Astros	O	O

ASUU	O	ORGANIZATION

Atalanta	O	LOCATION

Athens	O	ORGANIZATION
Metro	O	ORGANIZATION

Athens	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Athletics	O	O

Atlanta	O	LOCATION

ATLANTA	O	LOCATION

Atlanta	O	ORGANIZATION
Braves	O	ORGANIZATION

Atlante	O	LOCATION

Atlas	O	O

Atletico	O	LOCATION

ATLETICO	O	ORGANIZATION

Atletico	O	ORGANIZATION
Madrid	O	ORGANIZATION

Atletico	O	ORGANIZATION
Mineiro	O	ORGANIZATION

Atletico	O	ORGANIZATION
Paranaense	O	ORGANIZATION

ATP	O	O

Atria	O	LOCATION

ATRIA	O	ORGANIZATION

Atria	O	ORGANIZATION
Oy	O	ORGANIZATION

Auchan	O	O

Auckland	O	LOCATION

Audi	O	ORGANIZATION

Audi	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Australian	O	O
Democrats	O	O

Australia	O	LOCATION
Senate	O	O

Austria	O	LOCATION
Vienna	O	LOCATION

Auth	O	O
.	O	O

Authority	O	O

Auxerre	O	O

AUXERRE	O	ORGANIZATION

Avellino	O	LOCATION

AVIA	O	ORGANIZATION

Avianca	O	O

Awami	O	O
League	O	O

Ayr	O	O

AZ	O	LOCATION
Alkmaar	O	LOCATION

BABEL	O	O

Baby	O	O
Bells	O	O

Bahia	O	LOCATION

Bailard	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Biehl	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Kaiser	O	PERSON

Balkan	O	ORGANIZATION
Airlines	O	ORGANIZATION

Bally	O	O

Ballybunion	O	LOCATION

Baltika	O	LOCATION
Kaliningrad	O	LOCATION

Baltimore	O	LOCATION

BALTIMORE	O	LOCATION

Baltimore	O	ORGANIZATION
Orioles	O	ORGANIZATION

Bamerindus	O	O

Banco	O	ORGANIZATION
de	O	ORGANIZATION
Mexico	O	ORGANIZATION

Bancomext	O	ORGANIZATION

Banc	O	O
One	O	O
Capital	O	O
Corporation	O	O

Banco	O	ORGANIZATION
Santander	O	ORGANIZATION

Banespa	O	LOCATION

Banfield	O	PERSON

Banglabazar	O	ORGANIZATION
Patrika	O	ORGANIZATION

Bangladesh	O	LOCATION
Nationalist	O	O
Party	O	O

Banik	O	PERSON
Ostrava	O	PERSON

Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
Duta	O	ORGANIZATION

Bank	O	O
Indonesia	O	LOCATION

Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Finland	O	ORGANIZATION

Bank	O	O
of	O	O
France	O	LOCATION

Bank	O	O
of	O	O
Israel	O	LOCATION

Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Japan	O	ORGANIZATION

Bank	O	O
of	O	O
New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION

Bank	O	O
of	O	O
Spain	O	LOCATION

Barcelona	O	LOCATION

BARCELONA	O	LOCATION

Bari	O	ORGANIZATION

Barnet	O	O

Barnsley	O	LOCATION

Barrick	O	ORGANIZATION

Barrick	O	ORGANIZATION
Gold	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Barrington	O	ORGANIZATION
Research	O	ORGANIZATION
Associates	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

BARUM	O	O
HOLDING	O	O

Basle	O	LOCATION

Basque	O	O
Homeland	O	O
and	O	O
Freedom	O	O

Bastia	O	LOCATION

Battle	O	O
Mountain	O	O

Battle	O	O
Mountain	O	O
Gold	O	O

Batumi	O	LOCATION

Baxter	O	ORGANIZATION
International	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

BAYERISCHE	O	ORGANIZATION
VEREINSBANK	O	ORGANIZATION

Bayer	O	ORGANIZATION
Leverkusen	O	ORGANIZATION

Bayern	O	LOCATION

BAYERN	O	ORGANIZATION

Bayern	O	ORGANIZATION
Munich	O	ORGANIZATION

BayerVB	O	O

BBC	O	ORGANIZATION
radio	O	O

BCH	O	O

Becej	O	O

Bedibunder	O	O

Beirut	O	LOCATION
Secondary	O	O
Market	O	O

Beirut	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Bekescsaba	O	LOCATION

Belenenses	O	O

Belga	O	O

Belgrade	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

BellSouth	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

Benetton	O	PERSON

Benevolent	O	ORGANIZATION
Assoc	O	ORGANIZATION
.	O	O

Benfica	O	LOCATION

Berkshire	O	ORGANIZATION
Hathaway	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Berkshire	O	ORGANIZATION
Wood	O	ORGANIZATION
Elves	O	ORGANIZATION

Berlex	O	ORGANIZATION

Berlex	O	ORGANIZATION
Laboratories	O	ORGANIZATION

Bernama	O	LOCATION

Bertelsmann	O	ORGANIZATION

Bertelsmann	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Berwick	O	LOCATION

Besiktas	O	LOCATION

Bessemer	O	O

Bessemer	O	ORGANIZATION
Venture	O	ORGANIZATION
Partners	O	ORGANIZATION

Best	O	O

Bestop	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Best	O	O
Products	O	O
Co	O	O

Betar	O	O

Betar	O	LOCATION
Jerusalem	O	LOCATION

Bhattarai	O	PERSON

Bhavnagar	O	LOCATION

Bild	O	O
am	O	O
Sonntag	O	O

Billa	O	LOCATION

Biogen	O	ORGANIZATION

Biogen	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

BioVest	O	ORGANIZATION
Research	O	ORGANIZATION
,	O	O
Inc	O	O

Birmingham	O	LOCATION

Blackburn	O	LOCATION

BLACKBURN	O	ORGANIZATION

Blackpool	O	LOCATION

Bloomsbury	O	ORGANIZATION
Minerals	O	ORGANIZATION
Economics	O	ORGANIZATION

BME	O	O

BNP	O	O

BNZ	O	O

Board	O	O

Board	O	O
of	O	O
Control	O	O
for	O	O
Cricket	O	O
in	O	O
India	O	LOCATION

Boavista	O	LOCATION

Boby	O	PERSON
Brno	O	PERSON

Boca	O	O
Juniors	O	O

Bochum	O	O

Bodo	O	O
/	O	O
Glimt	O	O

Boeing	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

BOJ	O	ORGANIZATION

Boland	O	LOCATION

BOLAND	O	PERSON

Bold	O	O
/	O	O
Ogilvy	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Mather	O	PERSON

BOLD	O	O
/	O	O
OGILVY	O	O
,	O	O
MATHER	O	O

Bollore	O	ORGANIZATION

Bologna	O	LOCATION

BOLSWESSANEN	O	ORGANIZATION

Bolton	O	PERSON

Bombay	O	ORGANIZATION
Commodities	O	ORGANIZATION

Borac	O	O

Bordeaux	O	LOCATION

Borussia	O	ORGANIZATION
Dortmund	O	ORGANIZATION

Borussia	O	O
Moenchengladbach	O	O

Boskalis	O	PERSON

Boston	O	LOCATION

BOSTON	O	LOCATION

Boston	O	ORGANIZATION
Red	O	ORGANIZATION
Sox	O	ORGANIZATION

Botafogo	O	LOCATION

Bournemouth	O	LOCATION

BP	O	O

Bradford	O	LOCATION

Braga	O	PERSON

Bragantino	O	O

Brann	O	PERSON

Brann	O	PERSON
Bergen	O	PERSON

Braves	O	O

BRAVES	O	O

Breakfast	O	O
Soybean	O	O
Procurement	O	O
Assn	O	O

Brechin	O	LOCATION

Bremen	O	LOCATION

Brent	O	O

Brentford	O	LOCATION

Brewers	O	O

Brighton	O	LOCATION

Brisbane	O	LOCATION

BRISBANE	O	O

Bristol	O	LOCATION

Bristol	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

Bristol	O	ORGANIZATION
Rovers	O	ORGANIZATION

British	O	O
Airways	O	O

British	O	O
Broadcasting	O	ORGANIZATION
Corporation	O	ORGANIZATION

British	O	O
Data	O	O

British	O	O
Data	O	O
Management	O	O

British	O	O
Heart	O	ORGANIZATION
Foundation	O	ORGANIZATION

British	O	O
Land	O	O

British	O	O
Lions	O	O

British	O	O
Petrolem	O	O

British	O	ORGANIZATION
Securities	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Investments	O	ORGANIZATION
Board	O	ORGANIZATION

Brotherhood	O	O
of	O	O
Nations	O	O

Broward	O	ORGANIZATION
County	O	ORGANIZATION
Sheriff	O	ORGANIZATION
's	O	ORGANIZATION
Office	O	ORGANIZATION

Brush	O	O
Wellman	O	O

Brush	O	ORGANIZATION
Wellman	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

BSM	O	O

Bucharest	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Buducnost	O	O

Buducnost	O	O
(	O	O
P	O	O
)	O	O

Buducnost	O	O
(	O	O
V	O	O
)	O	O

Buenos	O	ORGANIZATION
Aires	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Buffalo	O	O
Bills	O	O

Building	O	O

Bulatka	O	O

Bundesbank	O	ORGANIZATION

Bunge	O	O

Bureau	O	ORGANIZATION
Veritas	O	ORGANIZATION

Burnley	O	LOCATION

Bury	O	O

BUSINESS	O	O
RECORDER	O	O

BVSC	O	O

Cabinet	O	O

Caen	O	ORGANIZATION

CAF	O	O

Cagliari	O	LOCATION

Caja	O	ORGANIZATION
de	O	ORGANIZATION
Madrid	O	ORGANIZATION

California	O	LOCATION

CALIFORNIA	O	LOCATION

California	O	ORGANIZATION
Angels	O	ORGANIZATION

Caltex	O	ORGANIZATION

CAMAT	O	O

Cambridge	O	LOCATION

Canberra	O	LOCATION

Cannes	O	LOCATION

Cardiff	O	LOCATION

Cardinals	O	O

Career	O	O
Horizons	O	O

Career	O	ORGANIZATION
Horizons	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Cargill	O	PERSON

Cargill	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Carlisle	O	PERSON

Carlton	O	PERSON

Carrefour	O	O

Casino	O	O
Graz	O	O

Castilla	O	PERSON

Castleford	O	LOCATION

Catholic	O	O
Information	O	O
office	O	O

Catholic	O	ORGANIZATION
Information	O	ORGANIZATION
Office	O	ORGANIZATION

CBI	O	O

CBOE	O	ORGANIZATION

CBSA	O	ORGANIZATION

CDU	O	O

CDU	O	ORGANIZATION
3	O	O

CDU	O	ORGANIZATION
/	O	ORGANIZATION
CSU	O	ORGANIZATION

CDU	O	O
No	O	O
.	O	O

CDU	O	O
No.3	O	O

Ceahlaul	O	PERSON
Piatra	O	PERSON
Neamt	O	PERSON

Celaya	O	PERSON

Celtic	O	O

Central	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Central	O	O
European	O	O
Free	O	O
Trade	O	O
Area	O	O

Centre	O	O
for	O	O
Sociological	O	O
Studies	O	O

CentrInvest	O	O
Securities	O	O

Cercle	O	PERSON
Brugge	O	PERSON

Cesena	O	PERSON

CESKA	O	PERSON
SPORITELNA	O	PERSON

CFDT	O	O

CGT	O	O

Chamber	O	O
of	O	O
Economy	O	O

Channel	O	O
Two	O	O

Charleroi	O	LOCATION

Charlton	O	PERSON

Chart	O	O
Thai	O	O

Chase	O	ORGANIZATION
Securities	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Checker	O	O
's	O	O

CheckFree	O	ORGANIZATION

CheckFree	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Chelsea	O	PERSON

Chemlon	O	PERSON
Humenne	O	PERSON

Chernomorets	O	O
Novorossiisk	O	LOCATION

Chesapeake	O	ORGANIZATION
Police	O	ORGANIZATION
Department	O	ORGANIZATION

Chester	O	PERSON

Chesterfield	O	LOCATION

Cheuvreux	O	PERSON
de	O	PERSON
Virieu	O	PERSON

Cheveley	O	O
Park	O	O
Stud	O	O

Chevron	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Chicago	O	LOCATION

CHICAGO	O	LOCATION

Chicago	O	ORGANIZATION
Board	O	ORGANIZATION
Options	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Chicago	O	ORGANIZATION
Cubs	O	ORGANIZATION

Chicago	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsdesk	O	ORGANIZATION

Chicago	O	LOCATION
White	O	O
Sox	O	O

Chievo	O	LOCATION

China	O	LOCATION
Daily	O	O

China	O	LOCATION
Securities	O	O

Chindia	O	LOCATION
Tirgoviste	O	LOCATION

Chiron	O	O

Chiron	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Chisinau	O	LOCATION

Chonan	O	LOCATION

Chonbuk	O	O

Chonnam	O	LOCATION

Chornomorets	O	O

Chornomorets	O	O
Odessa	O	LOCATION

Ciments	O	O
Blancs	O	O

Cincinnati	O	LOCATION

CINCINNATI	O	LOCATION

Cincinnati	O	ORGANIZATION
Reds	O	ORGANIZATION

CINCO	O	O
DIAS	O	O

Ciputra	O	O
Development	O	O

CIS	O	ORGANIZATION

City	O	O

Civil	O	O
Defence	O	O
and	O	O
Coast	O	ORGANIZATION
Guard	O	ORGANIZATION

Civil	O	O
War	O	O
Conservation	O	O
Corps	O	O

CKD	O	O
PRAHA	O	O
HOLDING	O	O

Cleveland	O	LOCATION

CLEVELAND	O	LOCATION

Cleveland	O	O
Indians	O	O

Cleveland	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsdesk	O	ORGANIZATION

CLINTON	O	PERSON
AND	O	O
CEDAR	O	O
RAPIDS	O	O

Club	O	O
Brugge	O	O

Clyde	O	PERSON

Clydebank	O	O

CME	O	O

CNB	O	O

CNE	O	O

CNIEC	O	ORGANIZATION

CNN	O	ORGANIZATION

CNR	O	O

Coalition	O	O

Coast	O	O
Guard	O	O

Codelco	O	ORGANIZATION

Cofinec	O	ORGANIZATION

COFINEC	O	ORGANIZATION

Cofinec	O	ORGANIZATION
S.A.	O	ORGANIZATION

Colchester	O	LOCATION

Collingwood	O	PERSON

Collstrop	O	O

Cologne	O	LOCATION

Colon	O	O

Colorado	O	LOCATION

COLORADO	O	LOCATION

Colorado	O	ORGANIZATION
Christian	O	ORGANIZATION
Home	O	ORGANIZATION

Colorado	O	ORGANIZATION
Health	O	ORGANIZATION
Fac	O	ORGANIZATION
.	O	O

Colorado	O	ORGANIZATION
Rockies	O	ORGANIZATION

Columbia	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

COMEX	O	O

Commission	O	O

Commodity	O	ORGANIZATION
Credit	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
USDA	O	ORGANIZATION

Commonwealth	O	O

Communist	O	O
United	O	O
Marxist-Leninist	O	O

Companion	O	O
Building	O	O
Material	O	O

Companion	O	O
Marble	O	O

CompuServe	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Confederation	O	O
of	O	O
British	O	O
Industry	O	O

Conference	O	O
Board	O	O

Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Conservative	O	O
New	O	O
Democracy	O	O

Consolidated	O	ORGANIZATION
Financial	O	ORGANIZATION
Data	O	ORGANIZATION

Constitutional	O	O
Rights	O	O
Project	O	O

Construction	O	O
Industry	O	O
Council	O	O

Constructorol	O	O

Constructorul	O	O

Constructorul	O	O
Chisinau	O	LOCATION

Continental	O	O

Continental	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Cooperative	O	O

Cooperative	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Cooperative	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Taiwan	O	ORGANIZATION

Coopers	O	O
and	O	O
Lybrand	O	PERSON

Coordinate	O	O
of	O	O
Ecumenical	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION

Corinthians	O	O

Coritiba	O	LOCATION

Corporacion	O	PERSON
Venezolana	O	PERSON
de	O	PERSON
Guayana	O	PERSON

Correction	O	O
Department	O	O

Cosenza	O	PERSON

Costain	O	O

Costain	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Council	O	O

Council	O	O
of	O	O
Europe	O	LOCATION

Coventry	O	O

Cowdenbeath	O	O

Credit	O	O
Rating	O	O
and	O	O
Information	O	ORGANIZATION
Systems	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Credit	O	O
Suisse	O	O

Cremonese	O	LOCATION

Crewe	O	LOCATION

CRH	O	O

Criciuma	O	O

Cricuma	O	O

Criminal	O	O
Investigation	O	O
Department	O	O

Cronulla	O	LOCATION

CRP	O	O

Cruz	O	PERSON
Azul	O	PERSON

Cruzeiro	O	LOCATION

Crvena	O	ORGANIZATION
zvezda	O	O

Crystal	O	O
Palace	O	O

Csepel	O	O

CSKA	O	ORGANIZATION

CSKA	O	ORGANIZATION
Kiev	O	ORGANIZATION

CSKA	O	ORGANIZATION
Moscow	O	LOCATION

Cubs	O	O

CUBS	O	ORGANIZATION

Cukaricki	O	LOCATION

Cukurova	O	PERSON

CVG	O	O

CVRD	O	ORGANIZATION

Cyprus	O	LOCATION
Grain	O	O
Commission	O	O

Czech	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

DAC	O	O
Dunajska	O	PERSON
Streda	O	PERSON

Dacom	O	ORGANIZATION

Dacom	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Dacom	O	ORGANIZATION
International	O	ORGANIZATION

Dadabhoy	O	O
Investment	O	O
(	O	O
pvt	O	O
)	O	O
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION
Dacom	O	ORGANIZATION
Communications	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION
Information	O	ORGANIZATION

Daewoo	O	ORGANIZATION
Information	O	ORGANIZATION
Systems	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

DAILY	O	O
NEWS	O	O

Daily	O	O
Telegraph	O	O

Daily	O	O
Variety	O	O

Darlington	O	LOCATION

DAWN	O	O

DBRS	O	ORGANIZATION

Debrecen	O	LOCATION

DECATUR	O	O

Defence	O	O

Defence	O	O
and	O	O
Aviation	O	O

Defence	O	O
Ministry	O	O

Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Karen	O	ORGANIZATION
Buddhist	O	ORGANIZATION
Army	O	ORGANIZATION

Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Democrat	O	O
National	O	O
Convention	O	O

Den	O	O
Norske	O	O
Stats	O	O
Oljeselskap	O	O
AS	O	O

Department	O	O
of	O	O
Humanitarian	O	O
affairs	O	O

Department	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Transport	O	ORGANIZATION

Department	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Transportation	O	ORGANIZATION

Deportivo	O	ORGANIZATION
Espanol	O	ORGANIZATION

Derby	O	LOCATION

Derbyshire	O	LOCATION

Detroit	O	LOCATION

DETROIT	O	LOCATION

Detroit	O	ORGANIZATION
Tigers	O	ORGANIZATION

Deutsche	O	ORGANIZATION
Bahn	O	ORGANIZATION

Deutsche	O	ORGANIZATION
Bahn	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Deutsche	O	ORGANIZATION
Lufthansa	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

DHA	O	O

Dhaka	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Dia	O	O

Diamond	O	ORGANIZATION
Shamrock	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

DIARIO	O	ORGANIZATION
16	O	O

DINAMINA	O	LOCATION

Dinamo	O	LOCATION

DINAMO	O	ORGANIZATION

Dinamo	O	ORGANIZATION
Bucharest	O	ORGANIZATION

Disney	O	O

Distillers	O	O

DIVAINA	O	LOCATION

DKBA	O	ORGANIZATION

DLJ	O	ORGANIZATION
Merchant	O	ORGANIZATION
Banking	O	ORGANIZATION
Partners	O	ORGANIZATION
LP	O	ORGANIZATION

Dnevi	O	O
Avaz	O	O

DNEVNI	O	O
AVAZ	O	O

Dnipro	O	O

Dnipro	O	PERSON
Dnipropetrovsk	O	PERSON

DNUM	O	ORGANIZATION

Dodgers	O	O

DODGERS	O	O

Doe	O	PERSON
Run	O	PERSON

Doetinchem	O	LOCATION

Dole	O	PERSON
White	O	O
House	O	O

Dominion	O	O
Bond	O	O
Rating	O	O
Service	O	O

Donaldson	O	ORGANIZATION
Lufkin	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Jenrette	O	ORGANIZATION

Doncaster	O	O

Dortmund	O	O

Doubletree	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Dream	O	O
Team	O	O

Dreyfus	O	ORGANIZATION
Strategic	O	ORGANIZATION
Municipals	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Dreyfus	O	O
Strategic	O	O
Munis	O	O

DSE	O	O

Dublin	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Ducati	O	PERSON

Duff	O	PERSON
and	O	O
Phelps	O	LOCATION

Duff	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Phelps	O	ORGANIZATION

Duisburg	O	LOCATION

Dukla	O	PERSON
Banska	O	PERSON
Bystrica	O	PERSON

Duma	O	O

Dumbarton	O	LOCATION

Dundee	O	LOCATION

Dundee	O	ORGANIZATION
United	O	ORGANIZATION

Dunfermline	O	ORGANIZATION

Dunnes	O	O
Stores	O	O

Durham	O	LOCATION

Dutch	O	O
PTT	O	O

Dynamo	O	O

Dynamo	O	O
Batumi	O	LOCATION

Dynamo	O	ORGANIZATION
Kiev	O	ORGANIZATION

Dynamo	O	LOCATION
Moscow	O	LOCATION

Earth	O	O
First	O	O

Eastern	O	O
Cables	O	O

Eastern	O	O
Region	O	O
Brigade	O	O

East	O	O
Fife	O	O

East	O	O
Stirling	O	O

Eau	O	PERSON
Claire	O	PERSON

EC	O	ORGANIZATION

ECOMOG	O	ORGANIZATION

Ecuadorian	O	O
Oriente	O	O

EEC	O	O

EgyptAir	O	ORGANIZATION

Ek	O	ORGANIZATION
Chor	O	ORGANIZATION
China	O	ORGANIZATION
Motorcycle	O	ORGANIZATION

Ekeren	O	LOCATION

Eksportfinans	O	O

Electoral	O	ORGANIZATION
Research	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Elect	O	O
Res	O	O

Eletropaulo	O	ORGANIZATION

Eleusis	O	O

Elf	O	O

Eli	O	PERSON
Lilly	O	PERSON

Eli	O	ORGANIZATION
Lilly	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

El	O	PERSON
Jadida	O	PERSON

El	O	PERSON
Mundo	O	PERSON

EL	O	O
MUNDO	O	O

El	O	PERSON
Nuevo	O	PERSON
Diario	O	PERSON

EL	O	O
PAIS	O	O

El-Watan	O	O

Emeraud	O	O

EMKAM	O	O

Emnid	O	O

Empoli	O	LOCATION

Empresa	O	ORGANIZATION
Nacional	O	ORGANIZATION
del	O	ORGANIZATION
Petroleo	O	ORGANIZATION

ENAP	O	ORGANIZATION

Environment	O	O
Canada	O	O

EOE	O	O

EPA	O	O

EPR	O	O

Equitas	O	ORGANIZATION

ERP	O	O

Escravos	O	O

Espinho	O	O

Essendon	O	LOCATION

Essex	O	LOCATION

ESSEX	O	LOCATION

Essilor	O	O

Essilor	O	ORGANIZATION
International	O	ORGANIZATION

Estudiantes	O	O

ETA	O	O

Eternit	O	O

EU	O	ORGANIZATION

EU	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Eugene	O	PERSON

Eurobourses	O	O

EUROLIRA	O	O

Europe	O	LOCATION
1	O	O

European	O	O
Coal	O	O
and	O	O
Steel	O	O
Community	O	O

European	O	O
Commission	O	O

European	O	ORGANIZATION
Court	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Rights	O	ORGANIZATION

European	O	LOCATION
Union	O	LOCATION

Eurostat	O	O

EUROSWISS	O	O

Eva	O	PERSON
Tremila	O	PERSON

EVEREN	O	ORGANIZATION

EVEREN	O	ORGANIZATION
Securities	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Everton	O	LOCATION

Exeter	O	LOCATION

EXPANSION	O	O

Expos	O	O

EXPRESS	O	O

Fahnestock	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

F.A.I.	O	O

Falkir	O	O

Falkirk	O	LOCATION

FARC	O	ORGANIZATION

Faulding	O	O

Faulding	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

FBI	O	ORGANIZATION

F.B.I.	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
Arges	O	ORGANIZATION
Dacia	O	ORGANIZATION
Pitesti	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Bohemians	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	PERSON
Brasov	O	PERSON

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
Chindia	O	ORGANIZATION
Tirgoviste	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	PERSON
Farul	O	PERSON
Constanta	O	PERSON

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Karvina	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Kosice	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
La	O	ORGANIZATION
Valletta	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Linz	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Bucharest	O	LOCATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Nitra	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
Petrolul	O	ORGANIZATION
Ploiesti	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Porto	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Rimavska	O	ORGANIZATION
Sobota	O	ORGANIZATION

FC	O	ORGANIZATION
Tirol	O	ORGANIZATION
Innsbruck	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
Valletta	O	ORGANIZATION

F.C.	O	ORGANIZATION
VALLETTA	O	ORGANIZATION

FDA	O	O

FDP	O	O

Federation	O	O
Syndicale	O	O
Unitaire	O	O

Fenerbahce	O	O

Ferencvaros	O	ORGANIZATION

FERENCVAROS	O	ORGANIZATION

Ferrari	O	PERSON

Ferris	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Baker	O	PERSON
Watts	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Inc.	O	O

Ferro	O	PERSON
Carril	O	PERSON
Oeste	O	PERSON

Feyenoord	O	ORGANIZATION

Feyenoord	O	ORGANIZATION
Rotterdam	O	ORGANIZATION

FFK	O	O

F.H.	O	ORGANIZATION
Faulding	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Fidelis	O	PERSON
Andria	O	PERSON

FIFA	O	ORGANIZATION

Finance	O	O

Finance	O	O
Ministry	O	O

FINANCIAL	O	O
KATHIMERINI	O	O

FINANCIAL	O	O
POST	O	O

Financial	O	O
Security	O	O
Assurance	O	O

Fiorentina	O	ORGANIZATION

FIORENTINA	O	ORGANIZATION

First	O	O
Alliance	O	O

First	O	ORGANIZATION
Capital	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

First	O	O
Pacific	O	O

First	O	O
Union	O	O

First	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

First	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Fla.	O	ORGANIZATION

First	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Florida	O	ORGANIZATION

FIS	O	O

Fitzroy	O	PERSON

FK	O	O
Jablonec	O	O

FK	O	O
Teplice	O	O

Flamengo	O	LOCATION

Flamurtari	O	LOCATION
Vlore	O	LOCATION

FLNC	O	ORGANIZATION

Florida	O	LOCATION

FLORIDA	O	LOCATION

Florida	O	ORGANIZATION
Marlins	O	ORGANIZATION

Fluminense	O	LOCATION

Fokker	O	ORGANIZATION
Aviation	O	ORGANIZATION

Fontaine	O	PERSON

Fontaine	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Football	O	O
Association	O	O
of	O	O
Ireland	O	LOCATION

Footscray	O	LOCATION

Ford	O	ORGANIZATION

Ford	O	ORGANIZATION
China	O	ORGANIZATION

Ford	O	ORGANIZATION
Motor	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Foreign	O	O
Affairs	O	O

Foreign	O	O
Ministry	O	O

Foreign	O	O
Office	O	O

Foreldorado	O	O

Forfar	O	O

Formula	O	O
Shell	O	O

FORMULA	O	O
SHELL	O	O

Forsa	O	O

Forschungsgruppe	O	O
Wahlen	O	O

Fortuna	O	PERSON
Duesseldorf	O	PERSON

Fortuna	O	ORGANIZATION
Sittard	O	ORGANIZATION

Four	O	O
Nations	O	O
TV	O	O
Committee	O	O

Fourth	O	O
Circuit	O	O

Fox	O	ORGANIZATION
Broadcasting	O	ORGANIZATION

France-Soir	O	O

France	O	ORGANIZATION
Telecom	O	ORGANIZATION

Frankfurt	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

FRATERNITE	O	PERSON
MATIN	O	PERSON

Freedom	O	O
Front	O	O

Freiburg	O	LOCATION

Fremantle	O	LOCATION

French	O	O
Archaeological	O	ORGANIZATION
Society	O	ORGANIZATION

Frontier	O	O

FSA	O	O

FSU	O	O

FTC	O	O

Fulham	O	LOCATION

Fulmar	O	O

GACETA	O	ORGANIZATION
DE	O	O
LOS	O	O
NEGOCIOS	O	O

GAK	O	O

GAL	O	O

Galatasaray	O	LOCATION

GAN	O	O

Gartner	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Gateway	O	O
Data	O	O
Sciences	O	O

Gazeta	O	ORGANIZATION
Shqiptare	O	ORGANIZATION

Gazeta	O	ORGANIZATION
Wyborcza	O	ORGANIZATION

Gazprom	O	ORGANIZATION

Geelong	O	O

Gencor	O	ORGANIZATION

Gencor	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

General	O	O
Motors	O	O

Genk	O	O

Genoa	O	LOCATION

GENOA	O	LOCATION

Gente	O	O

Gentext	O	ORGANIZATION
Optics	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Ghent	O	O

Giants	O	O

GIANTS	O	O

Gift	O	O
of	O	O
Love	O	O

Giga	O	ORGANIZATION
Information	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Gillingham	O	LOCATION

Gil	O	PERSON
Vicente	O	PERSON

Gimnasia-Jujuy	O	O

Gimnasia-La	O	ORGANIZATION
Plata	O	ORGANIZATION

Ginebra	O	LOCATION
San	O	LOCATION
Miguel	O	LOCATION

Gingrich	O	ORGANIZATION
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Gingrich	O	PERSON
/	O	O
Dole	O	O
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

GKS	O	O
Belchatow	O	O

GKS	O	O
Katowice	O	O

Glamorgan	O	LOCATION

Glasgow	O	ORGANIZATION
Rangers	O	ORGANIZATION

Glentoran	O	O

Globo	O	O

Gloria	O	PERSON
Bistrita	O	PERSON

GLORIA	O	PERSON
BISTRITA	O	PERSON

Gloucestershire	O	LOCATION

Goias	O	LOCATION

Gold	O	O
Coast	O	O

Golden	O	O
Crescent	O	O

Goldman	O	ORGANIZATION
Sachs	O	ORGANIZATION

Goldman	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Sachs	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
.	O	O

Goldman	O	ORGANIZATION
,	O	ORGANIZATION
Sachs	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Goldman	O	ORGANIZATION
Sachs	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Goldman	O	ORGANIZATION
Sachs	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Wertpapier	O	ORGANIZATION
GmbH	O	ORGANIZATION

Gornik	O	ORGANIZATION
Zabrze	O	ORGANIZATION

Government	O	O
Housing	O	O
Bank	O	O

GPG	O	O

Graafschap	O	PERSON

Graafschap	O	PERSON
Doetinchem	O	PERSON

Grasshopper	O	PERSON

Grasshoppers	O	O

Greenock	O	PERSON

Greenock	O	PERSON
Morton	O	PERSON

Greens	O	O

Greenville	O	LOCATION

Gremio	O	LOCATION

Grimsby	O	LOCATION

Griqualand	O	LOCATION
West	O	LOCATION

Groningen	O	LOCATION

GRONINGEN	O	ORGANIZATION

GTE	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

GTE	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

Guadalajara	O	LOCATION

Guarani	O	LOCATION

Guimaraes	O	LOCATION

Guingamp	O	LOCATION

Guinness	O	O
Peat	O	O

Guinness	O	ORGANIZATION
Peat	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Gyor	O	O

HAARETZ	O	O

Haitai	O	PERSON

Hajduk	O	LOCATION

Haladas	O	O

Halifax	O	LOCATION

Hamas	O	ORGANIZATION

Hambrecht	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Quist	O	ORGANIZATION

Hamburg	O	LOCATION

Hamilton	O	PERSON

Hammerson	O	ORGANIZATION

Hampshire	O	LOCATION

Handgun	O	ORGANIZATION
Control	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Hansa	O	PERSON
Rostock	O	PERSON

Hanson	O	PERSON

Hanson	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Hanwha	O	LOCATION

Hapoel	O	PERSON
Beersheva	O	PERSON

Hapoel	O	O
Beit	O	O
She'an	O	O

Hapoel	O	PERSON
Haifa	O	PERSON

Hapoel	O	O
Ironi	O	O

Hapoel	O	PERSON
Ironi	O	PERSON
Rishon	O	PERSON

Hapoel	O	O
Jerusalem	O	LOCATION

Hapoel	O	O
Kfar	O	O
Sava	O	O

Hapoel	O	ORGANIZATION
Petah	O	ORGANIZATION
Tikva	O	ORGANIZATION

Hapoel	O	ORGANIZATION
Taibe	O	ORGANIZATION

Hapoel	O	O
Tel	O	O
Aviv	O	O

Hapoel	O	O
Zafririm	O	O
Holon	O	O

Harelbeke	O	PERSON

Harleysville	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Harper-Collins	O	O

Hartlepool	O	LOCATION

Hassania	O	O
Agadir	O	O

Havnar	O	O
Boltfelag	O	O

Hawthorn	O	LOCATION

HCFA	O	ORGANIZATION

Health	O	O
Care	O	O
Financing	O	O
Administration	O	O

Health	O	O
Insurance	O	O
of	O	O
Vermont	O	LOCATION

Hearts	O	O

Hebrew	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

Heerenveen	O	O

Helsinki	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Hemina	O	PERSON

Hereford	O	LOCATION

Hess	O	PERSON

Hezb-i-Islami	O	ORGANIZATION

Hibernian	O	LOCATION

Hina	O	PERSON

HINA	O	ORGANIZATION

Hizbollah	O	O

HMG	O	O

Hoechst	O	ORGANIZATION
Marion	O	ORGANIZATION
Roussel	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

HOEK	O	O
LOOS	O	O

Hoek	O	ORGANIZATION
Loos	O	ORGANIZATION
NV	O	ORGANIZATION

Holdings	O	O

Honam	O	ORGANIZATION

Honda	O	ORGANIZATION

HONG	O	O
KONG	O	O
ECONOMIC	O	O
TIMES	O	O

Hong	O	ORGANIZATION
Kong	O	ORGANIZATION
Interbank	O	ORGANIZATION

Hong	O	ORGANIZATION
Kong	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Hong	O	LOCATION
Kong	O	LOCATION
News	O	O
Room	O	O

House	O	O

Housecall	O	ORGANIZATION

Housecall	O	ORGANIZATION
Medical	O	ORGANIZATION
Resources	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

House	O	O
of	O	O
Commons	O	O

House	O	O
of	O	O
Representatives	O	O

Houston	O	LOCATION

HOUSTON	O	LOCATION

Houston	O	ORGANIZATION
Astros	O	ORGANIZATION

H&R	O	O
Block	O	O
Inc	O	O

HSBC	O	ORGANIZATION
Markets	O	ORGANIZATION

Huddersfield	O	LOCATION

Hull	O	PERSON

Human	O	O
Gene	O	O
Therapy	O	O

Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Rights	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Observatory	O	ORGANIZATION

Huracan	O	O

Huracan-Corrientes	O	O

Husaberg	O	PERSON

Husqvarna	O	PERSON

Hutnik	O	LOCATION
Krakow	O	LOCATION

Hwa	O	ORGANIZATION
Kay	O	ORGANIZATION
Thai	O	ORGANIZATION
Holdings	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Hyundai	O	ORGANIZATION

IBCA	O	ORGANIZATION

Iberia	O	ORGANIZATION

ICAC	O	ORGANIZATION

IFK	O	ORGANIZATION
Gothenburg	O	ORGANIZATION

IFOR	O	ORGANIZATION

IHC	O	O

IHC	O	O
Caland	O	O

Ihlas	O	PERSON

III.ker.TVE	O	O

Illawarra	O	LOCATION

Iltalehti	O	O

IMED	O	ORGANIZATION

IMED	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

IMERISIA	O	O

Immigration	O	O
Service	O	O

Immuno	O	ORGANIZATION
International	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Impala	O	PERSON

Impala	O	ORGANIZATION
Platinum	O	ORGANIZATION
Holdings	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Imphold	O	O

Implats	O	O

INA	O	O

Inc	O	O

Independiente	O	O

Indian	O	O
Fisheries	O	O
Department	O	O

Indian	O	O
Oil	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Indians	O	O

INDIANS	O	O

Individual	O	O

Indonesian	O	ORGANIZATION
Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Indusind	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Information	O	O
Ministry	O	O

ING	O	O

ING	O	ORGANIZATION
Barings	O	ORGANIZATION

ING	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Ingwe	O	O

Ingwe	O	ORGANIZATION
Coal	O	ORGANIZATION
Corporation	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

In	O	O
Home	O	O
Health	O	O

In	O	ORGANIZATION
Home	O	ORGANIZATION
Health	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Institute	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	ORGANIZATION
Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Gene	O	ORGANIZATION
Therapy	O	ORGANIZATION

Inter	O	O

Interacciones	O	O

Interbank	O	O

Inter	O	O
Bratislava	O	LOCATION

Interfax	O	ORGANIZATION

Interior	O	O

interior	O	O
ministry	O	O

Interior	O	ORGANIZATION
Ministry	O	ORGANIZATION

Inter	O	ORGANIZATION
Milan	O	ORGANIZATION

Internacional	O	O

International	O	O
Bonds	O	O

International	O	O
Petroleum	O	O
Exchange	O	O

International	O	O
Philippine	O	O

International	O	ORGANIZATION
Red	O	ORGANIZATION
Crescent	O	ORGANIZATION

Internazionale	O	ORGANIZATION

Internet	O	O
Startup	O	O

Interpol	O	ORGANIZATION

Inverness	O	LOCATION

IOC	O	O

IPE	O	O

IPO	O	O

Ipsos	O	O

Ipswich	O	LOCATION

Iraqi	O	O
Community	O	O
Association	O	O

IRISH	O	O
INDEPENDENT	O	O

Irish	O	O
Navy	O	ORGANIZATION

Irish	O	O
Permanent	O	O

IRISH	O	O
TIMES	O	O

IRNA	O	ORGANIZATION

Isbank	O	PERSON

Iscor	O	O

Islamic	O	O
Revolutionary	O	O
Court	O	O

Islamic	O	O
Salvation	O	O
Front	O	O

Israel	O	ORGANIZATION
Radio	O	ORGANIZATION

ISS	O	O

ISS	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Istanbul	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Itar-Tass	O	O

IVAC	O	ORGANIZATION

IVAC	O	ORGANIZATION
Medical	O	ORGANIZATION

IVAC	O	ORGANIZATION
Medical	O	ORGANIZATION
Systems	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Ivernia	O	LOCATION

Jakarta	O	ORGANIZATION
Post	O	ORGANIZATION

Jamaat-i-Islami	O	O

Janakantha	O	PERSON

Japan	O	LOCATION
Aluminium	O	O
Federation	O	O

Japan	O	LOCATION
Credit	O	O
Rating	O	O
Agency	O	O

Japanese	O	O
Food	O	O
Agency	O	O

JAS	O	O
Bardejov	O	O

JavaSoft	O	ORGANIZATION

Javedan	O	O
Cement	O	O

JD	O	O
Group	O	O

JERUSALEM	O	O
POST	O	O

Jeunesse	O	PERSON
Massira	O	PERSON

Jiangling	O	ORGANIZATION
Motors	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Jiangling	O	ORGANIZATION
Motors	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

Jiul	O	O
Petrosani	O	O

J.J.	O	PERSON
KENNY	O	PERSON

Jockey	O	O
Club	O	O

JOHNSON	O	ORGANIZATION
CO	O	ORGANIZATION

Jomhuri	O	ORGANIZATION
Eslami	O	ORGANIZATION

Jomo	O	PERSON

Jordan	O	LOCATION

Judicial	O	O
Police	O	O

Jumbish-i-Milli	O	PERSON

JUMHOURIYA	O	O

Jungle	O	O
Command	O	O

Justice	O	O

Juventude	O	O

Juventus	O	O

KABLO	O	ORGANIZATION
KLADNO	O	ORGANIZATION

Kabul	O	LOCATION
Radio	O	O

Kalf	O	PERSON
,	O	O
Voorhis	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Kamaz	O	ORGANIZATION
Naberezhnye	O	O
Chelny	O	O

KANSAS	O	LOCATION
CITY	O	LOCATION

Kansas	O	ORGANIZATION
City	O	ORGANIZATION
Royals	O	ORGANIZATION

Karabach	O	LOCATION
Agdam	O	LOCATION

Karachi	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Kareda	O	PERSON
Siauliai	O	PERSON

Karen	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

Karlsruhe	O	LOCATION

Karpaty	O	O

Karpaty	O	PERSON
Lviv	O	PERSON

Kathmandu	O	ORGANIZATION
Post	O	ORGANIZATION

Kaucuk	O	O
Opava	O	O

Ka	O	ORGANIZATION
Wah	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Kawasaki	O	LOCATION

KDP	O	O

KDPI	O	ORGANIZATION

Keane	O	PERSON

Keane	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Kekkila	O	LOCATION

KEKKILA	O	ORGANIZATION

Kekkila	O	ORGANIZATION
Oy	O	ORGANIZATION

Kent	O	PERSON

Kerametal	O	PERSON
Dubnica	O	PERSON

KERDOS	O	O

Khmer	O	O

Khmer	O	ORGANIZATION
Rouge	O	ORGANIZATION

Khouribga	O	O

Kilmarnock	O	LOCATION

KinderCare	O	ORGANIZATION
Learning	O	ORGANIZATION
Centers	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Kingston	O	LOCATION

Kingston	O	ORGANIZATION
Technology	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Kinross	O	PERSON

Kinross	O	ORGANIZATION
Gold	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Kispest	O	LOCATION

Kispest	O	O
Honved	O	O

Kleiner	O	PERSON
Perkins	O	PERSON

Kleiner	O	ORGANIZATION
Perkins	O	ORGANIZATION
Caufield	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Byers	O	ORGANIZATION

KNU	O	O

Koha	O	O
Jone	O	O

Kolbenschmidt	O	PERSON

KOMERCNI	O	O
BANKA	O	O

Kongsvinger	O	O

Koninklijke	O	ORGANIZATION
Boskalis	O	ORGANIZATION
Westminster	O	ORGANIZATION
NV	O	ORGANIZATION

Koninklijke	O	ORGANIZATION
PTT	O	ORGANIZATION
Nederland	O	ORGANIZATION
NV	O	ORGANIZATION

Konpolis	O	LOCATION

Kotaik	O	PERSON
Abovyan	O	PERSON

Kpaitan	O	O
Stankov	O	O

KPC	O	O

Kredietbank	O	ORGANIZATION

Kremin	O	O

Kremin	O	O
Kremenchuk	O	O

Krpaco	O	ORGANIZATION

Krpaco	O	ORGANIZATION
a.s.	O	ORGANIZATION

Krylya	O	PERSON
Sovetov	O	PERSON
Samara	O	PERSON

Kryvbas	O	O

Kryvbas	O	PERSON
Kryvy	O	PERSON
Rig	O	PERSON

KSE	O	O

KTM	O	O

Kurdistan	O	ORGANIZATION
Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Iran	O	ORGANIZATION

Kurdistan	O	ORGANIZATION
Workers	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Labor	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Labour	O	O

La	O	O
Corse	O	O

Lada	O	PERSON
Togliatti	O	PERSON

La	O	PERSON
Jornada	O	PERSON

Lamonts	O	O

Lamonts	O	O
Apparel	O	O

Lamonts	O	ORGANIZATION
Apparel	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

La	O	O
Nacion	O	O

Lancashire	O	LOCATION

Lancet	O	O

Land	O	O
Securities	O	O

LANKADEEPA	O	LOCATION

Lanus	O	O

LA	O	O
PRESSE	O	O

Lausanne	O	LOCATION

La	O	O
Voie	O	O

LA	O	O
VOIE	O	O

Lazio	O	PERSON

LDP	O	O

Lebanon	O	LOCATION
First	O	LOCATION

Le	O	ORGANIZATION
Canard	O	ORGANIZATION
Enchaine	O	ORGANIZATION

Lecce	O	LOCATION

Lech	O	PERSON
Poznan	O	PERSON

LECIVA	O	ORGANIZATION
PRAHA	O	ORGANIZATION

Leeds	O	LOCATION

LEEDS	O	ORGANIZATION

Leeds	O	ORGANIZATION
United	O	ORGANIZATION

Le	O	PERSON
Figaro	O	PERSON

Legal	O	O
Department	O	O

Legia	O	ORGANIZATION
Warsaw	O	ORGANIZATION

Le	O	PERSON
Havre	O	PERSON

Lehman	O	PERSON

Lehman	O	ORGANIZATION
Brothers	O	ORGANIZATION
International	O	ORGANIZATION

Leicester	O	LOCATION

Leicestershire	O	LOCATION

LE	O	O
JOUR	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Matin	O	PERSON

Le	O	PERSON
Monde	O	PERSON

LE	O	O
MONDE	O	O

Lens	O	O

LENS	O	O

Lenzing	O	O

Lenzing	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Leon	O	PERSON

Le	O	PERSON
Populaire	O	PERSON

Les	O	PERSON
Echos	O	PERSON

LE	O	O
TEMPS	O	O

Leverkusen	O	PERSON

Levski	O	O
Sofia	O	LOCATION

Leyton	O	O
Orient	O	O

LG	O	ORGANIZATION

LG	O	ORGANIZATION
Caltex	O	ORGANIZATION

LG	O	ORGANIZATION
Electronics	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Liberal	O	ORGANIZATION
Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Liberal	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Liberation	O	ORGANIZATION
Tigers	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Tamil	O	ORGANIZATION
Eelam	O	ORGANIZATION

Liberia	O	ORGANIZATION
Council	O	ORGANIZATION

Liberte	O	O

Lichtwer	O	ORGANIZATION
Pharma	O	ORGANIZATION
GmbH	O	ORGANIZATION

Lidl	O	PERSON

Lierse	O	LOCATION

Life	O	ORGANIZATION
Insurance	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	O
Georgia	O	LOCATION

Life	O	O
of	O	O
Georgia	O	LOCATION

LIFFE	O	O

Ligier	O	O

Lihir	O	PERSON

Likud	O	O

Lille	O	LOCATION

Lillestrom	O	O

Lincoln	O	PERSON

Linzer	O	O
ASK	O	O

LIONS	O	O

Lisbon	O	LOCATION

Liu	O	PERSON
Chong	O	PERSON
Hing	O	PERSON

Liu	O	ORGANIZATION
Chong	O	ORGANIZATION
Hing	O	ORGANIZATION
Investment	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Liverpool	O	LOCATION

Livingston	O	PERSON

LKS	O	ORGANIZATION
Lodz	O	ORGANIZATION

Llansantffraid	O	O

Lloyd	O	PERSON
's	O	O

Lloyd	O	PERSON
's	O	O
of	O	O
London	O	LOCATION

Lloyds	O	ORGANIZATION
Shipping	O	ORGANIZATION

Lloyds	O	ORGANIZATION
Shipping	O	ORGANIZATION
Intelligence	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION

LME	O	O

Lockhart	O	PERSON

Lockhart	O	ORGANIZATION
Industries	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Lokeren	O	O

Lokomotiva	O	O
Kosice	O	LOCATION

Lokomotiv	O	ORGANIZATION
Moscow	O	ORGANIZATION

Lokomotiv	O	PERSON
Nizhny	O	PERSON
Novgorod	O	PERSON

Lommel	O	LOCATION

London	O	LOCATION

London	O	ORGANIZATION
Broncos	O	ORGANIZATION

Lonrho	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Los	O	LOCATION
Angeles	O	LOCATION

LOS	O	LOCATION
ANGELES	O	LOCATION

Los	O	ORGANIZATION
Angeles	O	ORGANIZATION
Dodgers	O	ORGANIZATION

Lotte	O	PERSON

Louis	O	PERSON
Dreyfus	O	PERSON
Corp	O	PERSON

Loxley	O	LOCATION

Loxley	O	ORGANIZATION
Publications	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Loznica	O	LOCATION

Ltd	O	O

LTTE	O	ORGANIZATION

Lucchese	O	O

Lucerne	O	LOCATION

Lufthansa	O	ORGANIZATION

Lufthansa	O	ORGANIZATION
Cargo	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Lufthanseat	O	PERSON

Lugano	O	LOCATION

LUKoil	O	O

Luton	O	LOCATION

Lyngby	O	LOCATION

Lyon	O	LOCATION

MAARIV	O	O

Maccabi	O	LOCATION
Haifa	O	LOCATION

Maccabi	O	LOCATION
Herzliya	O	LOCATION

Maccabi	O	O
Petah	O	ORGANIZATION
Tikva	O	ORGANIZATION

Macedonian	O	O
Communist	O	O
Party	O	O

Madrid	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

MainStay	O	O
International	O	O
Funds	O	O

Malbak	O	PERSON

Malbak	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Mallinckrodt	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Manchester	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

MANCHESTER	O	LOCATION
CITY	O	LOCATION

Manchester	O	ORGANIZATION
United	O	ORGANIZATION

Man	O	O
City	O	O

Manly	O	O

Mansfield	O	PERSON

Mapei	O	O

Mariners	O	O

Marines	O	O

Marion	O	ORGANIZATION
County	O	ORGANIZATION
Board	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Education	O	ORGANIZATION

Marlins	O	O

Maronite	O	O

Marrakesh	O	LOCATION

Marseille	O	LOCATION

MARSEILLE	O	LOCATION

Marubeni	O	LOCATION

Matahari	O	LOCATION

M'bishi	O	O
Gas	O	O

MCC	O	O

McCarthy	O	PERSON

McLaren	O	O

MDS	O	O

Mechelen	O	O

Mediaset	O	ORGANIZATION

Meknes	O	LOCATION

Melbourne	O	LOCATION

Mentmore	O	O

Mentmore	O	ORGANIZATION
Abbey	O	ORGANIZATION

Mercantile	O	O
&	O	O
General	O	O

Merrill	O	ORGANIZATION
Lynch	O	ORGANIZATION

Merrion	O	ORGANIZATION
Insurance	O	ORGANIZATION
Company	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Metalurg	O	O

Metalurg	O	O
Zaporizhya	O	O

Metro	O	O

Metro	O	ORGANIZATION
Holdings	O	ORGANIZATION

METROSTAV	O	O

Mets	O	O

Metz	O	PERSON

Mexican	O	ORGANIZATION
Army	O	ORGANIZATION

MFS	O	O

MFS	O	ORGANIZATION
Communications	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

MG-Technogym	O	O

Miami	O	ORGANIZATION
Herald	O	ORGANIZATION

Microsoft	O	ORGANIZATION

Microsoft	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

Middlesbrough	O	ORGANIZATION

Middlesex	O	LOCATION

Mid-East	O	ORGANIZATION
Minerals	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Milan	O	LOCATION

MILAN	O	LOCATION

Military	O	O
College	O	O

Millwall	O	ORGANIZATION

Milwaukee	O	LOCATION

MILWAUKEE	O	LOCATION

Milwaukee	O	ORGANIZATION
Brewers	O	ORGANIZATION

Minardi	O	LOCATION

MING	O	O
PAO	O	O
DAILY	O	O
NEWS	O	O

Ministry	O	O
of	O	O
Commerce	O	O

Ministry	O	O
of	O	O
Finance	O	O

Ministry	O	O
of	O	O
Petroleum	O	O
and	O	O
Minerals	O	O

Minnesota	O	LOCATION

MINNESOTA	O	LOCATION

Minnesota	O	ORGANIZATION
Twins	O	ORGANIZATION

Minorco	O	O

Mironivka	O	LOCATION

Mironivka	O	ORGANIZATION
Wheat	O	ORGANIZATION
Institute	O	ORGANIZATION

Missionaries	O	O
of	O	O
Charity	O	O

Miss	O	O
Universe	O	O
Inc	O	O

Miss	O	O
Universe	O	O
Inc.	O	O

Miss	O	O
Venezuela	O	O
Organisation	O	O

MIT	O	O

Mitsubishi	O	ORGANIZATION

Mitsubishi	O	ORGANIZATION
Gas	O	ORGANIZATION
Chemical	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Mitsui	O	ORGANIZATION

Mladost	O	O
(	O	O
BJ	O	O
)	O	O

Mladost	O	O
(	O	O
L	O	O
)	O	O

MOF	O	O

Mohajir	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Movement	O	ORGANIZATION

Mohammedia	O	O

Mohib	O	O
Textile	O	O
Mills	O	O

Molde	O	O

Molenbeek	O	O

Monaco	O	LOCATION

Monstrose	O	O

Monterrey	O	LOCATION

Montpellier	O	LOCATION

Montreal	O	LOCATION

MONTREAL	O	O

Montreal	O	O
Expos	O	O

Montrose	O	LOCATION

Monza	O	LOCATION

Moody	O	ORGANIZATION
's	O	O

MOODY	O	ORGANIZATION
'S	O	ORGANIZATION

Moody	O	ORGANIZATION
's	O	ORGANIZATION
Investors	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION

MORAV.CHEMIC.	O	O
ZAV	O	O

Morelia	O	LOCATION

Morgan	O	PERSON
Stanley	O	PERSON

Morgan	O	ORGANIZATION
Stanley	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Morton	O	PERSON

Moscow	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Mosenergo	O	O

Moss	O	PERSON

Moss	O	ORGANIZATION
Landing	O	ORGANIZATION
Marine	O	ORGANIZATION
Laboratories	O	ORGANIZATION

Mostostal	O	ORGANIZATION

Mostostal	O	ORGANIZATION
Z	O	O

Mostostal	O	ORGANIZATION
Zabrze	O	ORGANIZATION
Holding	O	ORGANIZATION
SA	O	ORGANIZATION

Motherwell	O	LOCATION

Motorola	O	ORGANIZATION

Mouscron	O	O

Movement	O	O
of	O	O
Socialist	O	O
Democrats	O	O

MQM	O	O

M&R	O	O

MSK	O	O
Zilina	O	O

MSV	O	O
Duisberg	O	LOCATION

MSV	O	O
Duisburg	O	O

MTK	O	O

Mujahideen	O	ORGANIZATION
Khalq	O	ORGANIZATION

Munich	O	LOCATION
1860	O	O

Muslim	O	ORGANIZATION
Commercial	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

MX	O	O
Onda	O	O

Mypa-47	O	O

MyPa-47	O	O

NAC	O	O

NAC	O	O
Breda	O	PERSON

NAN	O	O

Nancy	O	PERSON

Nantes	O	LOCATION

Napoli	O	LOCATION

Nasr	O	PERSON

National	O	O

National	O	O
Customs	O	O
Board	O	O

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Democratic	O	ORGANIZATION
Alliance	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Election	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Farmers	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	O
Guard	O	O

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Rights	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	O
Hurricane	O	O
Center	O	O

National	O	O
Islamic	O	O
Front	O	O

National	O	O
Park	O	O
Service	O	O

National	O	O
Party	O	O

National	O	O
Rifle	O	O
Association	O	O

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Security	O	ORGANIZATION
Council	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Socialist	O	ORGANIZATION
Battle	O	ORGANIZATION
Cry	O	ORGANIZATION

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Unity	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

NATO	O	ORGANIZATION

Natural	O	O
Law	O	O
Party	O	O

Nature	O	O

Navy	O	ORGANIZATION

NBA	O	O

NBC	O	ORGANIZATION

NBH	O	O

NCB	O	O

ND	O	O

Necaxa	O	LOCATION

NEC	O	ORGANIZATION
Nijmegen	O	ORGANIZATION

Nepali	O	ORGANIZATION
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Neptune	O	O
Crux	O	O

Networks	O	O
Services	O	O
Division	O	O

Neuchatel	O	O

NEUCHATEL	O	O

Neuchatel	O	O
Xamax	O	O

New	O	O
Aspiration	O	O
Party	O	O

Newcastle	O	LOCATION

NEWCASTLE	O	ORGANIZATION

Newcrest	O	LOCATION

Newcrest	O	ORGANIZATION
Mining	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Newcrest	O	ORGANIZATION
Q4	O	O

New	O	O
democracy	O	O

New	O	O
Democracy	O	O

Newell	O	ORGANIZATION
Old	O	ORGANIZATION
Boys	O	ORGANIZATION

Newell	O	PERSON
's	O	O
Old	O	O
Boys	O	O

New	O	O
Media	O	O

New	O	O
Party	O	O
Sakigake	O	O

News	O	O

News	O	O
Agency	O	O
of	O	O
Nigeria	O	LOCATION

New	O	O
Scientist	O	O

News	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

News	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	LOCATION
York	O	LOCATION

NEW	O	O
YORK	O	O

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Commodities	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Energy	O	ORGANIZATION
Desk	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Mets	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsdesk	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Post	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Power	O	ORGANIZATION
Desk	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Times	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Yankees	O	ORGANIZATION

New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION
Press	O	O
Association	O	O

Neza	O	PERSON

NFU	O	ORGANIZATION

Nice	O	O

NICE	O	O

NIDA'A	O	O
AL-WATAN	O	O

Nijmeh	O	PERSON

Ninth	O	O
Circuit	O	O

Niugini	O	LOCATION

Niugini	O	ORGANIZATION
Mining	O	ORGANIZATION

Niugini	O	ORGANIZATION
Mining	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Nocerina	O	LOCATION

Nomura	O	ORGANIZATION

Nomura	O	ORGANIZATION
Research	O	ORGANIZATION
Institute	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Nomura	O	ORGANIZATION
Securities	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Noranda	O	ORGANIZATION

Northampton	O	LOCATION

Northamptonshire	O	LOCATION

North	O	ORGANIZATION
Atlantic	O	ORGANIZATION
Treaty	O	ORGANIZATION
Organisation	O	ORGANIZATION

Northcote	O	ORGANIZATION
College	O	ORGANIZATION

Northern	O	O
League	O	O

Northern	O	O
States	O	O
Power	O	O
Co	O	O

Northern	O	O
Transvaal	O	O

North	O	O
Melbourne	O	LOCATION

North	O	O
Queensland	O	LOCATION

Northsea	O	O
Chaser	O	O

North	O	O
Sydney	O	LOCATION

Norwich	O	LOCATION

Noticias	O	O

NOTICIAS	O	O

Nottingham	O	LOCATION
Forest	O	LOCATION

Nottinghamshire	O	LOCATION

Notts	O	O

Notts	O	LOCATION
County	O	LOCATION

NSDAP-AO	O	ORGANIZATION

NS	O	ORGANIZATION
Kampfruf	O	ORGANIZATION

NTB	O	O

NTV	O	O

Nutricia	O	ORGANIZATION

Nyva	O	O

Nyva	O	O
Ternopil	O	O

Nyva	O	ORGANIZATION
Vinnytsya	O	ORGANIZATION

NZPA	O	ORGANIZATION

Oakland	O	LOCATION

OAKLAND	O	LOCATION

Oakland	O	ORGANIZATION
Athletics	O	ORGANIZATION

Oakley	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Oasis	O	O

OB	O	O

Obilic	O	O

OCEI	O	ORGANIZATION

Odra	O	PERSON

Odra	O	ORGANIZATION
Wodzislaw	O	ORGANIZATION

OFFICIAL	O	O
JOURNAL	O	O

OFK	O	O
Beograd	O	O

OFK	O	O
Kikinda	O	O

O	O	O
Globo	O	O

OHIO	O	O
BUILDING	O	O
AUTHORITY	O	O

OIC	O	O

OJ	O	O

OKD	O	O

Oklahoma	O	ORGANIZATION
State	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

Oklahoma	O	ORGANIZATION
Wheat	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Oldham	O	LOCATION

Olimpija	O	LOCATION

Olympiakos	O	O

OLYMPIAKOS	O	ORGANIZATION

OM	O	O

OM	O	ORGANIZATION
Gruppen	O	ORGANIZATION

OM	O	ORGANIZATION
Gruppen	O	ORGANIZATION
AB	O	ORGANIZATION

OMLX	O	ORGANIZATION

OM	O	ORGANIZATION
Stockholm	O	ORGANIZATION

ONIC	O	O

Opel	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Oppenheimer	O	O
Capital	O	O

Oppenheimer	O	ORGANIZATION
Capital	O	ORGANIZATION
LP	O	ORGANIZATION

Oracle	O	O
Systems	O	O

Oriente	O	O

Orii	O	ORGANIZATION

Orii	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Orioles	O	O

ORIOLES	O	O

OSCE	O	ORGANIZATION

OSLOBODJENJE	O	O

Otelul	O	PERSON
Galati	O	PERSON

Oujda	O	O

Overseas	O	O
Development	O	O
Administration	O	O

Oxford	O	LOCATION

Oxford	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

PA	O	O

Pachuca	O	LOCATION

Pacific	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Padres	O	O

Pakistan	O	LOCATION
Muslim	O	O
League	O	O

Pakistan	O	LOCATION
People	O	O
's	O	O
Party	O	O

Palermo	O	LOCATION

Palestinian	O	LOCATION
Authority	O	LOCATION

Palestinian	O	O
Information	O	O
Ministry	O	O

Palestinian	O	O
self-rule	O	O
Authority	O	O

Palmans	O	O

Palmeiras	O	LOCATION

PAO	O	O

Pao	O	O
de	O	O
Acucar	O	O

PAP	O	O

Paramount	O	O

Paramount	O	O
Pictures	O	O

Parana	O	LOCATION

Paribas	O	ORGANIZATION

Paribas	O	ORGANIZATION
Capital	O	ORGANIZATION
Markets	O	O
OTC	O	O

Paris	O	LOCATION

Paris	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Paris	O	LOCATION
Saint-Germain	O	O

Paris	O	LOCATION
SG	O	O

Paris	O	LOCATION
St	O	LOCATION
Germain	O	LOCATION

Parkway	O	ORGANIZATION
Middle	O	ORGANIZATION
School	O	ORGANIZATION

Parma	O	LOCATION

PARMA	O	ORGANIZATION

Parmalat	O	ORGANIZATION
/	O	O
Fehervar	O	O
FC	O	O

Parramatta	O	LOCATION

Partick	O	LOCATION

Partizan	O	O

Party	O	O
of	O	O
Social	O	O
Democracy	O	O

Pasok	O	O

Patriotic	O	O
Salvation	O	O
Movement	O	O

Patriotic	O	O
Union	O	O
of	O	O
Kurdistan	O	LOCATION

PBR	O	O

PC	O	ORGANIZATION
Data	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

PDI	O	O

PDS	O	O

PDSR	O	ORGANIZATION

PEC	O	O

Pecs	O	O

Penn	O	ORGANIZATION
Treaty	O	ORGANIZATION

Penn	O	ORGANIZATION
Treaty	O	ORGANIZATION
American	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Penrith	O	LOCATION

Pentagon	O	O

People	O	O
's	O	O
Daily	O	O

Peronists	O	O

Perugia	O	LOCATION

Pescara	O	LOCATION

Peterborough	O	LOCATION

Petra	O	PERSON

Petra	O	PERSON
Drnovice	O	PERSON

Petrimex	O	O
Prievidza	O	O

Petrobulk	O	O
Rainbow	O	O

Petroecuador	O	O

PF	O	O
IKS	O	O
KB	O	O
PLUS	O	O

Philadelphia	O	LOCATION
Phillies	O	LOCATION

Philip	O	PERSON
Morris	O	PERSON

Philip	O	ORGANIZATION
Morris	O	ORGANIZATION
Cos	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Phillies	O	O

PHILLIES	O	O

Physicians	O	O
Insurance	O	O
Co	O	O

Piacenza	O	LOCATION

Piper	O	PERSON
Jaffray	O	PERSON

Piper	O	ORGANIZATION
Jaffray	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Pittsburgh	O	LOCATION

PITTSBURGH	O	LOCATION

Pittsburgh	O	LOCATION
Pirates	O	LOCATION

PKK	O	O

Platense	O	O

Platignum	O	O

PLO	O	O

PLO	O	ORGANIZATION
Council	O	ORGANIZATION

Plymouth	O	LOCATION

Plymouth	O	ORGANIZATION
Argyle	O	ORGANIZATION

PMC	O	O

PMC-Sierra	O	O

PNW	O	O

Pohang	O	O

Polish	O	O
Development	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Politehnica	O	LOCATION
Timisoara	O	LOCATION

Polonia	O	PERSON
Warsaw	O	PERSON

Polonia	O	PERSON
Warszawa	O	PERSON

Polti	O	O

Popular	O	O
Party	O	O

Popular	O	O
Revolutionary	O	O
Army	O	O

Porsche	O	O

Port	O	O
Christine	O	PERSON

Porto	O	LOCATION

PORTO	O	LOCATION

Portsmouth	O	LOCATION

Portuguesa	O	LOCATION

Port	O	O
Vale	O	O

Post	O	O

Power	O	O

Power	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Power	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Canada	O	ORGANIZATION

Power	O	ORGANIZATION
Financial	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Power	O	O
New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION

Power	O	O
NZ	O	O
ODV	O	O

PP	O	O

Prague	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Prague	O	ORGANIZATION
Stock	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION

Prem	O	PERSON
Dan	O	PERSON

Press	O	O
Trust	O	O
of	O	O
India	O	LOCATION

Preston	O	PERSON

Primedia	O	ORGANIZATION

Privatisation	O	O
Commission	O	O

Proleter	O	O

Promodes	O	O

Property	O	O
Capital	O	O

Property	O	O
Capital	O	O
Trust	O	O

Provisional	O	O
Election	O	O
Commission	O	O

Prudential	O	O

Prykarpattya	O	O

Prykarpattya	O	O
Ivano-Frankivsk	O	O

PSA	O	O

PSC	O	O

PSE	O	O

PSG	O	O

PSI	O	O
Net	O	O

PSV	O	O

PSV	O	ORGANIZATION
Eindhoven	O	ORGANIZATION

PT	O	O
Matahari	O	ORGANIZATION
Putra	O	ORGANIZATION
Prima	O	ORGANIZATION

PTT	O	O

PT	O	O
VDH	O	O
Teguh	O	PERSON
Sakti	O	PERSON

Public	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION
Association	O	ORGANIZATION

Public	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Public	O	ORGANIZATION
Service	O	ORGANIZATION
,	O	O
Labour	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Social	O	ORGANIZATION
Welfare	O	ORGANIZATION

Public	O	ORGANIZATION
Transport	O	ORGANIZATION
Corporation	O	ORGANIZATION

Puchon	O	LOCATION

Puebla	O	LOCATION

PUK	O	ORGANIZATION

PULPEX	O	ORGANIZATION

PUNR	O	ORGANIZATION

Purdue	O	ORGANIZATION
Frederick	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Purefoods	O	ORGANIZATION
Hotdogs	O	ORGANIZATION

Purepac	O	O

Purepac	O	ORGANIZATION
Pharamceutical	O	ORGANIZATION

Pusan	O	LOCATION

QADISSIYA	O	O

Queen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O

Queen	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
South	O	LOCATION

Queen	O	O
's	O	O
Park	O	O

Queens	O	O
Park	O	O
Rangers	O	O

Rabobank	O	ORGANIZATION

RABOBANK	O	ORGANIZATION

Rabobank	O	ORGANIZATION
Nederland	O	ORGANIZATION
BA	O	O

Racing	O	O
Club	O	O

Rad	O	O

Radical	O	O
Cause	O	O

Radio	O	O
New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION

Radnicki	O	PERSON

Radnicki	O	O
(	O	O
N	O	O
)	O	O

RAF	O	ORGANIZATION
Riga	O	ORGANIZATION

Raith	O	LOCATION

Raith	O	ORGANIZATION
Rovers	O	ORGANIZATION

RAITH	O	ORGANIZATION
ROVERS	O	ORGANIZATION

Raith	O	ORGANIZATION
Rovers	O	ORGANIZATION
FC	O	O

Raja	O	PERSON
Casablanca	O	PERSON

Rajapat	O	ORGANIZATION
Institute	O	ORGANIZATION

Rangers	O	O

RAO	O	O
Gazprom	O	O

Rapid	O	O
Bucharest	O	LOCATION

Rapid	O	O
Vienna	O	LOCATION

Rapid	O	O
Wien	O	PERSON

Ravenna	O	LOCATION

RBA	O	O

RBI	O	O

RDR	O	O

Re	O	O

Reading	O	O

Real	O	O
Madrid	O	O

Red	O	O
Brigade	O	O

Red	O	O
Cross	O	O

Red	O	ORGANIZATION
Lion	O	ORGANIZATION
Hotels	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Reds	O	O

Red	O	O
Sox	O	O

Red	O	O
Star	O	O

RED	O	O
STAR	O	O

Red	O	O
Star	O	O
Belgrade	O	O

Reform	O	O
Party	O	O

Reggiana	O	LOCATION

Rennes	O	LOCATION

RENNES	O	ORGANIZATION

Repsol	O	O

Republican	O	O
Front	O	O

Republican	O	O
House	O	O

Republican	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Resalat	O	O

Reserve	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Australia	O	ORGANIZATION

Reserve	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
India	O	ORGANIZATION

Resistance	O	O

Reuter	O	ORGANIZATION
London	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Reuters	O	ORGANIZATION

Reuters	O	ORGANIZATION
Chicago	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsdesk	O	ORGANIZATION

Reuters	O	ORGANIZATION
Ottawa	O	ORGANIZATION
Burea	O	ORGANIZATION

Reuters	O	ORGANIZATION
Television	O	ORGANIZATION

Reuters	O	ORGANIZATION
Toronto	O	ORGANIZATION
Bureau	O	ORGANIZATION

Revolutionary	O	ORGANIZATION
United	O	ORGANIZATION
Front	O	ORGANIZATION

Revolutionary	O	O
Workers	O	O
'	O	O
Party	O	O

Rewe	O	ORGANIZATION

Rewe-Handelsgruppe	O	O

Rhone	O	LOCATION
Poulenc	O	LOCATION

RIA	O	O

Richmond	O	LOCATION

RIF	O	O

Rishon	O	PERSON

River	O	ORGANIZATION
Medical	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

River	O	O
Plate	O	O

RKC	O	O

RKC	O	O
Waalijk	O	O

RKC	O	O
Waalwijk	O	O

RMT	O	O

Road	O	O
Alert	O	O

Roberston	O	ORGANIZATION
Stephens	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Robert	O	PERSON
W.	O	PERSON
Baird	O	PERSON

Robert	O	ORGANIZATION
W.	O	ORGANIZATION
Baird	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
.	O	O

Rochdale	O	LOCATION

Roda	O	PERSON
JC	O	PERSON

Roda	O	PERSON
JC	O	PERSON
Kerkrade	O	PERSON

Roma	O	ORGANIZATION

ROMA	O	ORGANIZATION

Romanian	O	O
Soccer	O	O
Federation	O	O

Rosario	O	PERSON
Central	O	PERSON

Rosenborg	O	LOCATION

Ross	O	LOCATION
County	O	LOCATION

Rostelekom	O	PERSON

Rostselmash	O	PERSON
Rostov	O	PERSON

Rotherham	O	LOCATION

Rothschild	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Cie	O	ORGANIZATION

Rotor	O	O
Volgograd	O	LOCATION

Rovers	O	O

Royal	O	O
Armed	O	O
Forces	O	O

Royal	O	ORGANIZATION
Meteorological	O	ORGANIZATION
Institute	O	ORGANIZATION

Royal	O	O
Oak	O	O

Royal	O	ORGANIZATION
Oak	O	ORGANIZATION
Mines	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Royals	O	O

RSA	O	O
Data	O	O
Security	O	O

RSR	O	O

RTRS	O	ORGANIZATION

Ruch	O	ORGANIZATION
Chorzow	O	ORGANIZATION

Rudar	O	O

RUF	O	O

Rugby	O	ORGANIZATION
Football	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

RUGBY	O	O
UNION	O	O

Ruhunu	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

Russian	O	O
Weather	O	O
Service	O	O

Sakigake	O	O

Salomon	O	PERSON

Salomon	O	ORGANIZATION
Brothers	O	ORGANIZATION

Salomon	O	ORGANIZATION
Brothers	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Salomon	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Taylor	O	ORGANIZATION

Salomon	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Taylor	O	ORGANIZATION
Made	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Sampdoria	O	LOCATION

Samsung	O	ORGANIZATION

San	O	LOCATION
Diego	O	LOCATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
DIEGO	O	LOCATION

San	O	ORGANIZATION
Diego	O	ORGANIZATION
Padres	O	ORGANIZATION

SAN	O	LOCATION
FRANCISCO	O	LOCATION

San	O	ORGANIZATION
Francisco	O	ORGANIZATION
Giants	O	ORGANIZATION

San	O	LOCATION
Lorenzo	O	LOCATION

Santos	O	PERSON

Sao	O	LOCATION
Paulo	O	LOCATION

Saskatchewan	O	LOCATION
Wheat	O	O
Pool	O	O

Sauber	O	O

Saudi	O	O
Press	O	O
Agency	O	O

SBC	O	ORGANIZATION
Communications	O	ORGANIZATION

SBC	O	ORGANIZATION
Warburg	O	ORGANIZATION

S.B.K-	O	O
Brooks	O	ORGANIZATION
Investment	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

SC	O	O

Scac	O	PERSON
Delmas	O	PERSON
Vileujeux	O	PERSON

Scarborough	O	PERSON

SC	O	ORGANIZATION
Espinho	O	ORGANIZATION

Schalke	O	ORGANIZATION

Schalke	O	ORGANIZATION
04	O	O

Schering	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Scor	O	O

Scorpion	O	O

Scorpion	O	ORGANIZATION
Minerals	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Scunthorpe	O	O

SDA	O	ORGANIZATION

SDV	O	O

Seasongood	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Mayer	O	ORGANIZATION

Seat	O	O

Seattle	O	LOCATION

SEATTLE	O	LOCATION

Seattle	O	ORGANIZATION
Mariners	O	ORGANIZATION

Securities	O	O
and	O	O
Exchnage	O	O
Commission	O	O

Securities	O	O
Products	O	O
Business	O	O

Security	O	O
Council	O	O

Security	O	ORGANIZATION
Dynamics	O	ORGANIZATION
Technologies	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Security	O	O
Ministry	O	O

Selection	O	O
Committee	O	O

SELIKO	O	O

Senate	O	O

Seoul	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Servette	O	PERSON

Settat	O	O

Setubal	O	O

Shakhtar	O	O

Shakhtar	O	PERSON
Donetsk	O	PERSON

Shanghai	O	ORGANIZATION
Automobile	O	ORGANIZATION
Corporation	O	ORGANIZATION

Shanghai	O	ORGANIZATION
Ek	O	ORGANIZATION
Chor	O	ORGANIZATION

Shanghai-Ek	O	O
Chor	O	O

Shanghai-Ek	O	ORGANIZATION
Chor	O	ORGANIZATION
Motorcycle	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Shanghai	O	ORGANIZATION
Post	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	O
Telecomm	O	O

Shanghai	O	ORGANIZATION
Posts	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Telecommunications	O	ORGANIZATION
Equipment	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Sheffield	O	LOCATION

Sheffield	O	ORGANIZATION
United	O	ORGANIZATION

Sheffield	O	O
Wednesday	O	O

Shelbourne	O	O

Shell	O	O

Shen	O	O

Shining	O	O
Path	O	O

Shishu	O	PERSON
Bhavan	O	PERSON

Shrewsbury	O	LOCATION

Siam	O	O
Commercial	O	O

Siam	O	ORGANIZATION
Commercial	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Siam	O	ORGANIZATION
Commercial	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Sibonina	O	PERSON

Sidi	O	PERSON
Kacem	O	PERSON

Sidor	O	ORGANIZATION

Sidwell	O	ORGANIZATION
Friends	O	ORGANIZATION
School	O	ORGANIZATION

Sierra	O	LOCATION

Sierra	O	LOCATION
Semiconductor	O	LOCATION

Sierra	O	ORGANIZATION
Semiconductor	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Sietco	O	O

Sigma	O	O
Olomouc	O	O

SIMEX	O	O

SIMEX	O	ORGANIZATION
Brent	O	ORGANIZATION

Sindh	O	O
High	O	O
Court	O	O

Singapore	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Singapore	O	ORGANIZATION
Petroleum	O	ORGANIZATION
Company	O	ORGANIZATION

Singapore	O	LOCATION
Refining	O	O
Company	O	O

Sino-Thai	O	O

Sint	O	LOCATION
Truiden	O	LOCATION

Siofok	O	O

Sion	O	ORGANIZATION

SK	O	ORGANIZATION
Ceske	O	ORGANIZATION
Budejovice	O	ORGANIZATION

Skeid	O	O

SK	O	ORGANIZATION
Hradec	O	ORGANIZATION
Kralove	O	ORGANIZATION

SKODA	O	ORGANIZATION
PLZEN	O	ORGANIZATION

SK	O	ORGANIZATION
Slavia	O	ORGANIZATION
Praha	O	ORGANIZATION

SKS	O	O
Tana	O	PERSON

Sky	O	O

Slask	O	O
Wroclaw	O	O

Sloboda	O	O

Sloga	O	O
Jugomagnat	O	O

Slough	O	O

Slough	O	ORGANIZATION
Estates	O	ORGANIZATION

Slough	O	ORGANIZATION
Estates	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Slovan	O	O
Bratislava	O	LOCATION

Slovan	O	O
Liberec	O	O

SNCF	O	ORGANIZATION

SNET	O	ORGANIZATION

SoCal	O	ORGANIZATION
Edison	O	ORGANIZATION

Social	O	O
Democratic	O	O
Party	O	O

Socialist	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION

Sofia	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Softbank	O	ORGANIZATION

Softbank	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

SOKOLOVSKA	O	ORGANIZATION
UHELNA	O	ORGANIZATION

Sokol	O	PERSON
Tychy	O	PERSON

SOLIDERE	O	ORGANIZATION

Somerset	O	LOCATION

Somerset	O	O
Jewellers	O	O

Soundview	O	ORGANIZATION
Financial	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION

South	O	O

South	O	O
African	O	O
Hockey	O	O
Association	O	O

Southampton	O	LOCATION

SOUTH	O	O
CHINA	O	O
MORNING	O	O
POST	O	O

Southend	O	LOCATION

Southern	O	ORGANIZATION
California	O	ORGANIZATION
Edison	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Southland	O	ORGANIZATION
Life	O	ORGANIZATION

Southland	O	ORGANIZATION
Life	O	ORGANIZATION
Insurance	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

South	O	O
Queensland	O	LOCATION

South	O	O
Sydney	O	LOCATION

S&P	O	ORGANIZATION

Spal	O	O

Spar	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Sparta	O	LOCATION

Spartak	O	LOCATION

Spartak	O	LOCATION
Moscow	O	LOCATION

Spartak	O	ORGANIZATION
Trnava	O	ORGANIZATION

Sparta	O	ORGANIZATION
Prague	O	ORGANIZATION

Sparta	O	ORGANIZATION
Rotterdam	O	ORGANIZATION

SPD	O	O

Specia	O	PERSON

SPIF	O	O
CESKY	O	O

SPLA	O	ORGANIZATION

Sporting	O	O

SPORTING	O	O

Sporting	O	O
Sale	O	O

Sport	O	O
Recife	O	O

Sportul	O	O
Studentesc	O	O

Springbok	O	LOCATION

Springboks	O	O

SPT	O	O
TELECOM	O	O

SRC	O	O

Ssangbangwool	O	O

St.	O	O

Stabaek	O	O

Stadler	O	PERSON

Stagecoach	O	O

Stagecoach	O	ORGANIZATION
Holdings	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Standard	O	O
Liege	O	LOCATION

Star	O	O
magazine	O	O

Start	O	O

State	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

State	O	O
Council	O	O

State	O	O
Customs	O	O
Committee	O	O

State	O	O
Department	O	O

State	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Greece	O	ORGANIZATION

State	O	O
Planning	O	O
Commission	O	O

Statistics	O	O
Canada	O	O

Statoil	O	O

Status	O	O
Weekly	O	O

Steaua	O	PERSON
Bucharest	O	PERSON

Steel	O	O
Industry	O	O
Center	O	O

Stenhousemuir	O	O

Stentex	O	O

Steptoe	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Johnson	O	ORGANIZATION

St	O	LOCATION
Gallen	O	LOCATION

St	O	O
George	O	PERSON

St	O	O
Helens	O	O

ST	O	LOCATION
HELENS	O	LOCATION

Stinnes	O	O

Stirling	O	O

St	O	PERSON
Johnstone	O	PERSON

St	O	LOCATION
Kilda	O	LOCATION

St	O	O
Leger	O	O

St	O	LOCATION
Louis	O	LOCATION

ST	O	LOCATION
LOUIS	O	LOCATION

St.	O	ORGANIZATION
Louis	O	ORGANIZATION
Cardinals	O	ORGANIZATION

St	O	O
Mirren	O	O

Stock	O	O
Exchange	O	O

Stockport	O	LOCATION

Stoke	O	O

Stomil	O	PERSON
Olsztyn	O	PERSON

Stork	O	ORGANIZATION

St	O	LOCATION
Pauli	O	LOCATION

ST	O	LOCATION
PAULI	O	LOCATION

Stranraer	O	O

Strasbourg	O	LOCATION

Stromsgodset	O	O

Sturm	O	PERSON
Graz	O	PERSON

Stuttgart	O	LOCATION

Subaru	O	PERSON

Sudan	O	LOCATION
Airways	O	O

Sudan	O	LOCATION
People	O	O
's	O	O
Liberation	O	ORGANIZATION
Army	O	ORGANIZATION

Suedwest	O	O
LB	O	O

Sui	O	O
Northern	O	O
Gas	O	O

Sui	O	O
Southern	O	O
Gas	O	O

Sumitomo	O	O

Sumitomo	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Sun	O	O
Co	O	O

Sunderland	O	LOCATION

SunGard	O	ORGANIZATION

SunGard	O	ORGANIZATION
Data	O	ORGANIZATION
Systems	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

SunGard	O	ORGANIZATION
Shareholder	O	ORGANIZATION
Systems	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Sun	O	ORGANIZATION
Microsystems	O	ORGANIZATION

Sun	O	ORGANIZATION
Microsystems	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc.	O	ORGANIZATION

Super	O	O
Indah	O	O
Makmur	O	O

Supreme	O	ORGANIZATION
Court	O	ORGANIZATION

Supreme	O	O
Federal	O	O
Tribunal	O	O

Surrey	O	LOCATION

Sussex	O	ORGANIZATION

Sutjeska	O	LOCATION

Suwon	O	LOCATION

Suzuki	O	PERSON

SVCD	O	ORGANIZATION
Bulgaria	O	ORGANIZATION

SV	O	O
Hamburg	O	LOCATION

SV	O	O
Ried	O	O

SV	O	O
Salzburg	O	LOCATION

Swansea	O	LOCATION

Swebus	O	O

Swebus	O	ORGANIZATION
AB	O	ORGANIZATION

Swindon	O	LOCATION

Swiss	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

SWP	O	O

Sydney	O	LOCATION

Sydney	O	LOCATION
Bulldogs	O	O

Sydney	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION

Sydney	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Sydney	O	ORGANIZATION
Tigers	O	ORGANIZATION

Symantec	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

TABAK	O	O

Tafawa	O	PERSON
Balewa	O	PERSON
University	O	O

Taibe	O	LOCATION

Taichung	O	LOCATION
division	O	O

Taipei	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Taiwan	O	LOCATION
Flour	O	O
Mills	O	O
Assn	O	O

Tallinna	O	PERSON
Sadam	O	PERSON

Tamil	O	O
Tiger	O	O

Tanjug	O	LOCATION

Tankan	O	O

Tarmac	O	O

Tarmac	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Tass	O	ORGANIZATION

Tatran	O	O
Presov	O	O

Tavria	O	O

Taylor	O	ORGANIZATION
Asset	O	ORGANIZATION
Managers	O	ORGANIZATION

TBC	O	O

TBN	O	O

Tekstilshchik	O	PERSON
Kamyshin	O	PERSON

Tekstilshik	O	PERSON
Kamyshin	O	PERSON

Tel	O	LOCATION
Aviv	O	LOCATION

Telekom	O	PERSON

Television	O	O
New	O	LOCATION
Zealand	O	LOCATION

TELO	O	ORGANIZATION

Telstra	O	LOCATION

Tenacity	O	O

Tetouan	O	O

Texaco	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Texas	O	LOCATION

TEXAS	O	LOCATION

Texas	O	ORGANIZATION
Rangers	O	ORGANIZATION

Texas	O	LOCATION
Wheat	O	O
Producers	O	O

THAWRA	O	O

The	O	O
Canaries	O	O

THE	O	O
ISLAND	O	O

The	O	O
Land	O	O
is	O	O
Ours	O	O

THE	O	O
MUSLIM	O	O

THE	O	O
NATION	O	O

The	O	O
Natural	O	O
Law	O	O
Party	O	O

THE	O	O
NEWS	O	O

The	O	O
New	O	ORGANIZATION
York	O	ORGANIZATION
Times	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Statesman	O	O

The	O	O
Sun	O	O

The	O	O
Times	O	O

THE	O	O
TIMES	O	O

The	O	O
Wall	O	O
Street	O	O
Journal	O	O

The	O	O
Walt	O	ORGANIZATION
Disney	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Washington	O	O
Post	O	O

THINAKARAN	O	LOCATION

Thomson	O	PERSON
BankWatch	O	PERSON

Tiber	O	O

Tigers	O	O

Tilcon	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Times	O	O
of	O	O
London	O	LOCATION

TM	O	O

T&N	O	O

T&N	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Tokyo	O	ORGANIZATION
Commodities	O	ORGANIZATION
Desk	O	ORGANIZATION

Tokyo-Mitsubishi	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Tokyo	O	LOCATION
Soir	O	O

Tokyo	O	ORGANIZATION
Soir	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Toluca	O	LOCATION

Torino	O	LOCATION

Toronto	O	LOCATION

TORONTO	O	LOCATION

Toronto	O	ORGANIZATION
Blue	O	ORGANIZATION
Jays	O	ORGANIZATION

Torpedo	O	O

Torpedo	O	O
Moscow	O	LOCATION

Torpedo	O	O
Zaporizhya	O	O

Torquay	O	LOCATION

Tosco	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Total	O	O
Petroleum	O	O
(	O	O
North	O	LOCATION
America	O	LOCATION
)	O	O
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Tottenham	O	LOCATION

Tottenham	O	ORGANIZATION
Hotspur	O	ORGANIZATION

Touchstone	O	ORGANIZATION
Software	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp.	O	ORGANIZATION

Towers	O	O
Perrin	O	O

Toyota	O	O

Toyota	O	O
Australia	O	LOCATION

Trade	O	O
and	O	O
Industry	O	O

Tranmere	O	O

Transkaryotic	O	ORGANIZATION
Therapies	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Transportation	O	ORGANIZATION
Ministry	O	ORGANIZATION

Trax	O	ORGANIZATION
Petroleums	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Treasuries	O	O

Treasury	O	O

Treasury	O	O
Department	O	O

TRINECKE	O	O
ZELEZARNY	O	O

Triple-A	O	O
Columbus	O	O

TV	O	O
Globo	O	O

TV	O	O
Guide	O	O

TVM	O	O

TVX	O	O

TVX	O	ORGANIZATION
Gold	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

TWA	O	ORGANIZATION

Twente	O	O
Enschede	O	O

Twins	O	O

Tyndall	O	ORGANIZATION
Australia	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

Tyrrell	O	PERSON

UAG	O	O

UBS	O	O

Udinese	O	LOCATION

UDINESE	O	ORGANIZATION

UEFA	O	ORGANIZATION

UES	O	O

UIC	O	O

Ujpest	O	LOCATION

Ujpest	O	LOCATION
TE	O	O

UKCM	O	ORGANIZATION

Ukrainian	O	O
Academy	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Agrarian	O	ORGANIZATION
Sciences	O	ORGANIZATION

ULIMO-J	O	O

Ulsan	O	LOCATION

Ulster	O	ORGANIZATION
Petroleums	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

UML	O	O

UN	O	ORGANIZATION

U.N.	O	ORGANIZATION

UNAM	O	ORGANIZATION

U.N.	O	ORGANIZATION
General	O	O
Assembly	O	O

U.N.	O	ORGANIZATION
Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Rights	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Uniceramic	O	O

Union	O	O

Unita	O	ORGANIZATION

United	O	O

United	O	O
Daughters	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Confederacy	O	O

United	O	ORGANIZATION
Nations	O	ORGANIZATION
Human	O	ORGANIZATION
Rights	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

United	O	ORGANIZATION
Nations	O	ORGANIZATION
Special	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

United	O	ORGANIZATION
News	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
India	O	ORGANIZATION

United	O	ORGANIZATION
People	O	ORGANIZATION
's	O	ORGANIZATION
Front	O	ORGANIZATION
Nepal	O	ORGANIZATION

Unitog	O	ORGANIZATION
Co	O	ORGANIZATION

Universitatea	O	O
Cluj	O	O

Universitatea	O	LOCATION
Craiova	O	LOCATION

University	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Witwatersrand	O	O

UNP	O	O

UNSCOM	O	ORGANIZATION

U.N.	O	ORGANIZATION
Security	O	O
Council	O	O

UN	O	ORGANIZATION
Security	O	ORGANIZATION
Council	O	ORGANIZATION

Uralmash	O	LOCATION
Yekaterinburg	O	LOCATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Court	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Appeals	O	ORGANIZATION

USDA	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Defense	O	ORGANIZATION
Logistics	O	ORGANIZATION
Agency	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
District	O	ORGANIZATION
Court	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
DLA	O	O

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Federal	O	O
District	O	O
Court	O	O

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Food	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Drug	O	ORGANIZATION
Administration	O	ORGANIZATION

US	O	LOCATION
Luxembourg	O	LOCATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Municipal	O	ORGANIZATION
Desk	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Navy	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Postal	O	O

US	O	LOCATION
Postal	O	O

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Securities	O	ORGANIZATION
and	O	ORGANIZATION
Exchange	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Senate	O	ORGANIZATION
Intelligence	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
State	O	ORGANIZATION
Department	O	ORGANIZATION

USTA	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Transportation	O	ORGANIZATION
Department	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	ORGANIZATION
Treasuries	O	ORGANIZATION

U.S.	O	LOCATION
Treasury	O	O

UTI	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

Utrecht	O	O

Vac	O	O

Vale	O	O

Vale	O	O
do	O	O
Rio	O	LOCATION
Doce	O	LOCATION

Valerenga	O	O

Valero	O	ORGANIZATION
Energy	O	ORGANIZATION
Corp	O	ORGANIZATION

Vancouver	O	LOCATION
Sun	O	O

Van	O	PERSON
Der	O	PERSON
Horst	O	PERSON

Varteks	O	ORGANIZATION
Varazdin	O	ORGANIZATION

Vasas	O	O

Vasco	O	PERSON
da	O	PERSON
Gama	O	PERSON

VEERAKESARI	O	LOCATION

Velez	O	PERSON
Sarsfield	O	PERSON

Venalum	O	LOCATION

Venantius	O	O

VENANTIUS	O	ORGANIZATION
AB	O	ORGANIZATION

Veracruz	O	LOCATION

VeriSign	O	O

Verona	O	PERSON

VfB	O	ORGANIZATION
Stuttgart	O	ORGANIZATION

VfL	O	O
Bochum	O	O

Viacom	O	ORGANIZATION

Vicenza	O	LOCATION

Vicorp	O	O
Restaurants	O	O

Vicorp	O	ORGANIZATION
Restaurants	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

Videoton	O	O

Videoton(*	O	O

Viking	O	O

Viktoria	O	PERSON
Plzen	O	PERSON

Viktoria	O	PERSON
Zizkov	O	PERSON

Vital	O	O
Information	O	O
System	O	O

Vitesse	O	O

Vitesse	O	ORGANIZATION
Arnhem	O	ORGANIZATION

Vitoria	O	LOCATION

VNU	O	O

Vnukovo	O	ORGANIZATION
Airlines	O	ORGANIZATION

VODNI	O	O
STAVBY	O	O
PRAHA	O	O

Vogue	O	O

Vojvodina	O	LOCATION

Volendam	O	LOCATION

Volkswagen	O	ORGANIZATION

Volkswagen	O	ORGANIZATION
AG	O	ORGANIZATION

Vorskla	O	O

Vorskla	O	O
Poltava	O	O

VTM	O	O

VW	O	ORGANIZATION

Waalwijk	O	O

wall	O	O
Street	O	O

Wall	O	O
Street	O	O
bureau	O	O

Wall	O	O
Street	O	O
Journal	O	O

Walsall	O	ORGANIZATION

Warrington	O	LOCATION

Warsaw	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Warwickshire	O	ORGANIZATION

WARWICKSHIRE	O	ORGANIZATION

Washington	O	ORGANIZATION
Post	O	ORGANIZATION

Waterworks	O	O
Authority	O	O

Watford	O	LOCATION

WBUR-FM	O	O

Weather	O	O
Services	O	O
Corporation	O	O

Welsh	O	ORGANIZATION
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Farmers	O	ORGANIZATION
'	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

Welspun	O	O

Welspun	O	ORGANIZATION
Stahl	O	ORGANIZATION
Rohren	O	ORGANIZATION
Ltd	O	ORGANIZATION

WEN	O	O
WEI	O	O
PO	O	O

Werder	O	PERSON
Bremen	O	PERSON

WesBanco	O	ORGANIZATION
Bank	O	ORGANIZATION

West	O	LOCATION
Bromwich	O	LOCATION

West	O	LOCATION
Coast	O	LOCATION

Western	O	O
European	O	O
Union	O	O

Western	O	O
Province	O	O

Western	O	O
Reds	O	O

Western	O	O
Suburbs	O	O

West	O	O
Ham	O	O

White	O	O
Sox	O	O

Widad	O	LOCATION
Casablanca	O	LOCATION

Widad	O	O
Fes	O	O

Widzew	O	LOCATION

Widzew	O	ORGANIZATION
Lodz	O	ORGANIZATION

Wigan	O	LOCATION

Willem	O	PERSON
II	O	PERSON
Tilburg	O	PERSON

Williams	O	PERSON

Wimbledon	O	O

Wisla	O	LOCATION
Krakow	O	LOCATION

Wolverhampton	O	LOCATION

Worcestershire	O	O

Workington	O	LOCATION

World	O	O
Bridge	O	O

WorldCom	O	ORGANIZATION

WorldCom	O	ORGANIZATION
Inc	O	ORGANIZATION

World	O	O
XI	O	O

Wrexham	O	LOCATION

Writers	O	O
Association	O	O

WSC-India	O	O

WSRL	O	ORGANIZATION

Wycombe	O	O

x-AEK	O	O
Athens	O	LOCATION

x-Anderlecht	O	O

x-Cercle	O	O
Brugge	O	LOCATION

x-Club	O	O
Brugge	O	ORGANIZATION

Xinhua	O	O

x-Olympiakos	O	O

x-PAO	O	O

Yamaha	O	ORGANIZATION

Yankees	O	ORGANIZATION

YANKEES	O	O

Yedioth	O	O

Yedioth	O	PERSON
Ahronoth	O	PERSON

YEDIOTH	O	O
AHRONOTH	O	O

YMCA	O	ORGANIZATION

Yonsei	O	ORGANIZATION
University	O	ORGANIZATION

York	O	O

Yorkshire	O	LOCATION

Young	O	O
Boys	O	O

Yugo	O	ORGANIZATION
Zastava	O	ORGANIZATION

Zaglebie	O	PERSON
Lubin	O	PERSON

Zagreb	O	LOCATION
Money	O	O
Market	O	O

Zagreb	O	ORGANIZATION
Newsroom	O	ORGANIZATION

Zapatista	O	O

Zastava	O	ORGANIZATION

ZDF	O	O

Zelesnik	O	O

Zeleznik	O	O

Zemun	O	LOCATION

Zeneca	O	ORGANIZATION
Group	O	ORGANIZATION
Plc	O	ORGANIZATION

Zenith	O	ORGANIZATION

Zenit	O	O
St	O	O
Petersburg	O	LOCATION

Zeri	O	O
i	O	O
Popullit	O	O

Zhemchuzhina	O	LOCATION
Sochi	O	LOCATION

ZIFA	O	ORGANIZATION

Zimbabwe	O	LOCATION
Football	O	O
Association	O	O

Zirka-Nibas	O	O

Zirka-Nibas	O	O
Kirovohrad	O	O

ZTE	O	O

Zurich	O	LOCATION

Zurich	O	O
Editorial	O	O

AAA	O	O
Nghe	O	O
An	O	O

ActionAids	O	O
Vietnam	O	LOCATION

Thailand	O	LOCATION
Adidas	O	O

An	O	O
Dong	O	O
Plaza	O	O

Security	O	O
of	O	O
ConDao	O	O
airport	O	O

Housing&Land	O	O
publication	O	O

Hamlet	O	O
4	O	O

Cau	O	PERSON
Trang	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Long	O	O
Phuoc	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Vinh	O	PERSON
Loc	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Vinh	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
Hamlet	O	PERSON

Xeo	O	O
Nhau	O	O
A	O	O
Hamlet	O	O

Lao	O	O
Cai	O	O
Apatite	O	O

Northern	O	LOCATION
Ireland	O	LOCATION

Trang	O	PERSON
Tien	O	PERSON
Grocery	O	PERSON

Hanoi	O	LOCATION
Technology	O	O

Quang	O	O
Khanh	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Phuoc	O	PERSON
Hiep	O	PERSON
No.	O	O
2	O	O
Garbage	O	O
Dump	O	O

Bai	O	O
Tho	O	O
Plaza	O	O

District	O	O
3	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
Safety	O	O

Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

Ninh	O	ORGANIZATION
Kieu	O	ORGANIZATION
District	O	ORGANIZATION
Traffic	O	ORGANIZATION
Safety	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

City	O	ORGANIZATION
Traffic	O	ORGANIZATION
Safety	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Province	O	O
Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

Bac	O	O
Lieu	O	O
Province	O	O
Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

City	O	ORGANIZATION
Traffic	O	ORGANIZATION
Safety	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION

Can	O	O
Tho	O	O
City	O	O
Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

Ho	O	O
Chi	O	O
Minh	O	O
City	O	O
Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

Ho	O	O
Chi	O	O
Minh	O	O
City	O	O
Traffic	O	O
Safety	O	O
Commission	O	O

Committee	O	O
of	O	O
Voluntary	O	O
Social	O	O
Security	O	O

Committee	O	O
to	O	O
Protect	O	O
American	O	O
Value	O	O
Systems	O	O

Committee	O	O
to	O	O
Protect	O	O
Internal	O	O
Politics	O	O

The	O	O
Commitee	O	O
for	O	O
Mother	O	O
-	O	O
Children	O	O
Care	O	O
and	O	O
Protection	O	O

Independent	O	ORGANIZATION
Electoral	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	O
Iraq	O	LOCATION

Electoral	O	O
Commission	O	O
of	O	O
Iraq	O	LOCATION

National	O	ORGANIZATION
Electoral	O	ORGANIZATION
Commission	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	O
Thailand	O	LOCATION

Secretariat	O	O

The	O	O
10th	O	O
Secretariat	O	O
Congress	O	O

Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Secretariat	O	O

Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Secretariat	O	O

Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Secretariat	O	O

The	O	O
10th	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Secretariat	O	O
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Music	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
Ho	O	LOCATION
Chi	O	LOCATION
Minh	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION
TV	O	O
Station	O	O

The	O	O
Provincial	O	O
Party	O	O
Committee	O	O

The	O	O
City	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION

Ho	O	ORGANIZATION
Chi	O	ORGANIZATION
Minh	O	ORGANIZATION
City	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION

Ho	O	ORGANIZATION
Chi	O	ORGANIZATION
Minh	O	ORGANIZATION
City	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION

Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Union	O	O

Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Youth	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Youth	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION
Executive	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Nguyen	O	ORGANIZATION
Thi	O	ORGANIZATION
Minh	O	ORGANIZATION
Khai	O	ORGANIZATION
High	O	ORGANIZATION
School	O	ORGANIZATION

Executive	O	O
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Viet	O	ORGANIZATION
Nam	O	ORGANIZATION
Association	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Photographic	O	ORGANIZATION
Artists	O	ORGANIZATION

Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
4th	O	ORGANIZATION
Viet	O	ORGANIZATION
Nam	O	ORGANIZATION
Journalists	O	ORGANIZATION
Association	O	ORGANIZATION
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
3rd	O	ORGANIZATION
Viet	O	ORGANIZATION
Nam	O	ORGANIZATION
Journalists	O	ORGANIZATION
Association	O	ORGANIZATION
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
1st	O	O
Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

The	O	O
8th	O	ORGANIZATION
Party	O	ORGANIZATION
Central	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
10th	O	O
Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Provincial	O	O
Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O

Bac	O	O
Lieu	O	O
Province	O	O
Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O

The	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

The	O	O
10th	O	O
Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
Congress	O	ORGANIZATION

Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
The	O	O
Union	O	O

Central	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Ho	O	ORGANIZATION
Chi	O	ORGANIZATION
Minh	O	ORGANIZATION
Communist	O	ORGANIZATION
Youth	O	ORGANIZATION
Union	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Interim	O	O
Central	O	O
Executive	O	O
Committee	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
Northern	O	O
Provinces	O	O

Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Administration	O	ORGANIZATION
Reform	O	ORGANIZATION

Central	O	O
Steering	O	O
Comittee	O	O
127	O	O
of	O	O
Preventing	O	O
Smuggling	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
of	O	O
Emergency	O	O
Situations	O	O

Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Agriculture	O	ORGANIZATION
&	O	ORGANIZATION
Rural	O	ORGANIZATION

The	O	O
Central	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
Flood	O	O
and	O	O
Storm	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Influenza	O	O
A	O	O
/	O	O
H1N1	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Human	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Pandemic	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Influenza	O	O
A	O	O
/	O	O
H1N1	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Avian	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Chongqing	O	ORGANIZATION
District	O	ORGANIZATION
Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	O
the	O	O
Avian	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Thach	O	ORGANIZATION
Thanh	O	ORGANIZATION
District	O	ORGANIZATION
Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	O
the	O	O
Pandemic	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Avian	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Tien	O	ORGANIZATION
Giang	O	ORGANIZATION
Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	O
the	O	O
Avian	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Central	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
Flood	O	O
and	O	O
Storm	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
Flood	O	O
and	O	O
Storm	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Central	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
Flood	O	O
and	O	O
Storm	O	O
Prevention	O	O

The	O	O
Central	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
Anti-corruption	O	O

The	O	O
National	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O

The	O	O
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	O
SARS	O	O
Epidemic	O	O
and	O	O
Avian	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Prevention	O	O

The	O	O
National	O	ORGANIZATION
Steering	O	ORGANIZATION
Committee	O	ORGANIZATION
for	O	O
Influenza	O	O
A	O	O
/	O	O
H1N1	O	O
Prevention	O	O

The	O	O
National	O	O
Steering	O	O
Committee	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
Human	O	O
Influenza	O	O
Pandemic	O	O
Prevention	O	O

Flu	O	O
epidemic	O	O
protection	O	O
national	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

A/H1N1	O	O
protection	O	O
national	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Weekly	O	O
ocean	O	O
and	O	O
island	O	O
national	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

National	O	O
assembly	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Centeral	O	O
committee	O	O
for	O	O
directing	O	O
for	O	O
prevention	O	O
and	O	O
anti-corruption	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

South	O	O
west	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Highland	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Education	O	O
and	O	O
Training	O	O
insituition	O	O
of	O	O
examination	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Education	O	O
and	O	O
Training	O	O
insituition	O	O
of	O	O
examination	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Bac	O	O
Ninh	O	O
Province	O	O
of	O	O
Exammination	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
population	O	O
and	O	O
housing	O	O
analysis	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Prevention	O	O
and	O	O
anti-corruption	O	O
of	O	O
Binh	O	ORGANIZATION
Phuoc	O	ORGANIZATION
Province	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Prevention	O	O
and	O	O
anti-corruption	O	O
of	O	O
Can	O	O
tho	O	O
city	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Prevention	O	O
and	O	O
anti-corruption	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Centeral	O	O
committee	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Anti-smuggling,	O	O
commercial	O	O
fraud,	O	O
and	O	O
counterfeit	O	O
centeral	O	O
committee	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Centeral	O	O
committee	O	O
for	O	O
directing	O	O
for	O	O
prevention	O	O
and	O	O
anti-corruption	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

University	O	O
and	O	O
college	O	O
entrance	O	O
examination	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Human	O	O
rights	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Negatively	O	O
land	O	O
handling	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Sanitation	O	O
standard	O	O
food	O	O
operation	O	O
of	O	O
Dong	O	O
anh	O	O
district	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Sanitation	O	O
standard	O	O
food	O	O
operation	O	O
of	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O
city	O	O

Sanitation	O	O
standard	O	O
food	O	O
operation	O	O
of	O	O
ha	O	O
noi	O	O
city	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Sanitation	O	O
standard	O	O
food	O	O
operation	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Population	O	O
and	O	O
housing	O	O
construction	O	O
chanel	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Giang	O	PERSON
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Population	O	O
and	O	O
housing	O	O
construction	O	O
chanel	O	O
of	O	O
An	O	O
Giang	O	PERSON
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

The	O	O
poverty-alleviation	O	O
movement	O	O
and	O	O
unemployment	O	O
of	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O
city	O	O

The	O	O
poverty-alleviation	O	O
movement	O	O
and	O	O
unemployment	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Police	O	O
of	O	O
Thoi	O	PERSON
tam	O	O
mon	O	O
commune	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Quangtrach	O	LOCATION
district	O	O
armed	O	O
forces	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
of	O	O
Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
thua	O	O
thien	O	O
hue	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
cuu	O	O
long	O	O
plain's	O	O
provinces	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
Nam	O	O
Tra	O	O
My	O	O
district	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
Ninh	O	PERSON
Thuan	O	PERSON
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
quang	O	O
Nam	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
of	O	O
provinces	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
of	O	O
Ba	O	ORGANIZATION
Ria-Vung	O	ORGANIZATION
Tau	O	O
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
Nghe	O	O
An	O	O
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O
city	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
Da	O	O
nang	O	O
city	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention	O	O
centeral	O	O
committee	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
city	O	O
of	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
of	O	O
Quang	O	PERSON
Ngai	O	PERSON
province	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
of	O	O
Hai	O	LOCATION
Phong	O	LOCATION
City	O	LOCATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Flood	O	O
and	O	O
storm	O	O
control	O	O
and	O	O
prevention,	O	O
search	O	O
and	O	O
rescue	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Military	O	O
affair	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Blood	O	O
donation	O	O
club	O	O
chairman	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
board	O	O

Sewing	O	O
association	O	O
of	O	O
binh	O	O
duong	O	O
province	O	O
chairman	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
board	O	O

Co-operative	O	O
chairman	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
board	O	O

Ha	O	PERSON
Noi	O	PERSON
literature	O	O
club	O	O
final	O	O
examination	O	O
board	O	O

No	O	O
10	O	O
working	O	O
board	O	O

Parents-teacher	O	O
association	O	O
representative	O	O
board	O	O

Student	O	O
representative	O	O
board	O	O

People's	O	O
apiration	O	O
board	O	O

Lao	O	PERSON
Cai	O	PERSON
ethnic	O	O
board	O	O

Public	O	O
relation	O	O
board	O	O

City	O	O
committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Party	O	O
public	O	O
relation	O	O
board	O	O

City	O	O
committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Party	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
public	O	O
relation	O	O
board	O	O

Centeral	O	O
city	O	O
committee	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Party	O	O
public	O	O
relation	O	O
board	O	O

No	O	O
2	O	O
naval	O	O
area	O	O
public	O	O
relation	O	O

University	O	O
training	O	O
board	O	O

Hue	O	O
university	O	O
training	O	O
board	O	O

Thai	O	O
Nguyen	O	O
university	O	O
training	O	O
board	O	O

International	O	O
training	O	O
board	O	O

Hue	O	O
city	O	O
investment	O	O
and	O	O
construction	O	O
board	O	O

Emigranting	O	O
and	O	O
resettling	O	O
Tuyen	O	PERSON
Quang	O	PERSON
hydropower	O	O
board	O	O

Administration	O	O
board	O	O

Station	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Widenly	O	O
national	O	O
immunization	O	O
program	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

112	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

112	O	O
project	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
administration	O	O
board	O	O

322	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Thu	O	O
Thiem	O	O
bridge	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Thu	O	O
Thiem	O	O
bridge	O	O
and	O	O
Van	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
2	O	O
bridge	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Investment,	O	O
collection,	O	O
prevention,	O	O
translation	O	O
,	O	O
and	O	O
Treasure	O	ORGANIZATION
Trove	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
Tay	O	ORGANIZATION
Nguyen	O	ORGANIZATION
Epics	O	ORGANIZATION
publishing	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Se	O	O
San	O	O
hydropower	O	O
project	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

A	O	O
So	O	O
career-making	O	O
youth	O	O
villages	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

National	O	O
SXH	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

Currency	O	O
administration	O	O
board	O	O

The	O	O
People's	O	O
Aid	O	O
Coordinating	O	O
Committee	O	O

Business	O	O
innovation	O	O
board	O	O

The	O	O
Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

Commission	O	O
for	O	O
Foreign	O	O
Relations	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
Party	O	O
Central	O	O
Committee	O	O

Vietnam	O	LOCATION
Guinness	O	O
book	O	O
initial	O	O
assessment	O	O

Apple	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Cho	O	PERSON
Ray	O	PERSON
hospital	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Erasme	O	O
hospital	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Giadinh	O	PERSON
people	O	O
hospital	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Nai	O	PERSON
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Binhthuan	O	O
province's	O	O
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Dong	O	PERSON
Nai	O	PERSON
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Police	O	O
in	O	O
the	O	O
city	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Da	O	PERSON
Nang	O	PERSON
city	O	O
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
police	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Truong	O	PERSON
Thanh	O	PERSON
wood	O	O
industrial	O	O
company	O	O
limited	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Vedan	O	O
company	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

IAEA	O	ORGANIZATION
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Microsoft	O	ORGANIZATION
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Vietnam	O	LOCATION
Education	O	O
Fund	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Sara-Vinh	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

Education	O	O
and	O	O
Training	O	O
insituition	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
sport	O	O
instituition	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
director	O	O

School	O	O
board	O	O
director	O	O
Wesley	O	PERSON
professional	O	O

Administrator	O	O

Bui	O	PERSON
Van	O	PERSON
Ngu	O	PERSON
school	O	O
management	O	O
board	O	O

University	O	O
of	O	O
technical	O	O
education	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
administrator	O	O

Ly	O	PERSON
Phong	O	PERSON
administrator	O	O

High	O	O
school	O	O
for	O	O
the	O	O
gifted	O	O
administrator	O	O

Bach	O	PERSON
Dang	O	PERSON
seconadry	O	O
school	O	O
administrator	O	O

Nguyen	O	PERSON
Hien	O	PERSON
secondary	O	O
school	O	O
administrator	O	O

Le	O	PERSON
Hong	O	PERSON
Phong	O	PERSON
high	O	O
school	O	O
administrator	O	O

American	O	O
Idol	O	O
jury	O	O

Vietnam	O	LOCATION
Collection	O	O
Grand	O	O
Prix	O	O
competition	O	O
jury	O	O

Pulitzer	O	O
Pize	O	O
jury	O	O

Board	O	O
of	O	O
community	O	O
support	O	O

Board	O	O
of	O	O
student	O	O
Aid	O	O
and	O	O
business	O	O
Cooperation	O	O

Board	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
training	O	O
club	O	O

Training	O	ORGANIZATION
Board	O	ORGANIZATION
of	O	ORGANIZATION
HCM	O	ORGANIZATION
football	O	O
team	O	O

Vietnam	O	LOCATION
national	O	O
team	O	O
coach	O	O

Training	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
Hoang	O	PERSON
Anh	O	PERSON
Gia	O	PERSON
Lai	O	PERSON

Training	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
Newcastle	O	LOCATION

Training	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION

Training	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
German	O	O
team	O	O

Guiding	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
the	O	O
national	O	O
information	O	O
technology	O	O

Science	O	O
and	O	O
education	O	O
committee	O	O
board	O	O

Science	O	O
and	O	O
education	O	O
committee	O	O
television	O	O
Vietnam	O	LOCATION
board	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
militay	O	O
management	O	O
committee	O	O
board	O	O

Headquarter	O	O
board	O	O
of	O	O
supervisor	O	O

The	O	O
business	O	O

Economic-	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic-	O	O
budget	O	O
board	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Economic	O	O
commission	O	O
-	O	O
Ho	O	PERSON
Chi	O	PERSON
Minh	O	PERSON
city	O	O
council	O	O
budget	O	O

Disciplinary	O	O
board	O	O

The	O	O
discipline	O	O
of	O	O
vietnam	O	O
football	O	O
federation	O	O

VFF	O	O
discipline	O	O
board	O	O

Barca	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
boad	O	O

Atletico	O	ORGANIZATION
Madrid	O	ORGANIZATION
club	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Cuba	O	LOCATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

HCMC	O	ORGANIZATION
vietnam	O	O
custom	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Party	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Everton	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Hamas	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Iran	O	LOCATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Khome	O	O
Rouge	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

5	O	O
Ward	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Russia	O	LOCATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Newcastle	O	ORGANIZATION
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Orange	O	O
Dihoxyn	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O

Real	O	O
madrid	O	O
sterring	O	O
board	O	O
